{"idx": 0, "question": "The number of each X4's W2 equals 21. How many WWW does each X4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["X4's W2 = 21. X4's WWW = 21. X3's WWW = 21. X3's WWW = 21. X2's W2 = 21. X2's WWW as i. So i = X2. X2's WWW as Y. So Y = X2. X3's WWW as F. So F = 21. X3's WWW as r. So r = F = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. Y = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. Y = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. Y = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. Y = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. Y = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. Y = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. Y = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. i = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. Y = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. i = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. Y = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. i = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. Y = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. i = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. Y = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. i = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. Y = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. i = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. Y = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. i = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. Y = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. i = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. Y = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. i = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. Y = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. i = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. Y = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. i = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. Y = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. i = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. Y = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. F = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. r = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. i = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. Y = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. F = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. r = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. i = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. Y = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. F = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. r = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. i = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. Y = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. F = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. r = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. i = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. Y = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. F = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. r = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. i = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. Y = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. F = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. r = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. i = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. Y = 21.\nDefine each Y = 21. F = 21.\nDef"], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 1, "question": "The number of each Y3's X6 equals each Z8's Y8. The number of each Z8's Y8 equals 13. The number of each Y8's X7 equals each X6's WWW. The number of each Z4's Y8 equals the difference of each Y3's X6 and each Z8's Y8. The number of each X6's W2 equals 8 times each Z4's Y8. How many X7 does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Z8's Y8 as u. So u = 13.\nDefine each Y3's X6 as S. So S = u = 13.\nDefine each Z4's Y8 as A. So A = S - u = 13 - 13 = 0.\nDefine each X6's W2 as i. So i = 8 * A = 8 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X6's WWW as Y. So Y = i = 0.\nDefine each Y8's X7 as F. So F = Y = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 2, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y2 equals 19 times each Z6's Y3. The number of each Y3's X5 equals 11 times each Z3's Y2. The number of each Z6's Y3 equals 18 more than each Y3's WWW. The number of each X5's W4 equals the difference of each Y3's X5 and each Z3's Y2. The number of each Z3's Y2 equals 17. How many Y2 does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["Z3's Y2 as u. So u = 17.\nDefine each Y3's X5 as S. So S = 11 * u = 11 * 17 = 3.\nDefine each X5's W4 as A. So A = S - u = 3 - 17 = 9.\nDefine each X5's WWW as i. So i = A = 9.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as Y. So Y = S * i = 3 * 9 = 4.\nDefine each Z6's Y3 as F. So F = 18 * Y = 18 * 4 = 3.\nDefine each Z1's Y2 as r. So r = 19 * F = 19 * 3 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 3, "question": "The number of each Y2's X2 equals each Z1's Y2. The number of each Z0's Y4 equals each Z0's Y2. The number of each Z0's Y2 equals the sum of each Y9's X5 and each Z7's Y9. The number of each Y9's X2 equals 6 times each Y9's X5. The number of each Z1's Y9 equals 17 more than each Z7's Y4. The number of each Y4's X5 equals 21 times each Z0's YYY. The number of each Y2's X5 equals the sum of each Z0's Y4, each Y4's X5 and each Z7's Y9. The number of each Z7's Y9 equals 21 times each Y9's XXX. The number of each Z0's Y9 equals the sum of each Y9's XXX and each Z1's Y2. The number of each Y9's X1 equals 21 more than each Z1's Y9. The number of each Z1's Y2 equals 17 more than each Z7's Y9. The number of each Z7's Y4 equals 22. The number of each Y9's X5 equals 4 times each Y9's X1. The number of each Y2's X1 equals each Y2's X5. How many XXX does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Y9's X1 as u. So u = 21 * Z1's Y9 = 21 * 21 = 4.\nDefine each Y9's X5 as S. So S = 4 * u = 4 * 4 = 16.\nDefine each Y9's X2 as A. So A = 6 * S = 6 * 16 = 4.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as i. So i = S + A + u = 16 + 4 + 4 = 1.\nDefine each Z7's Y9 as Y. So Y = 21 * i = 21 * 1 = 21.\nDefine each Z1's Y2 as F. So F = 17 * Y = 17 * 21 = 12.\nDefine each Z0's Y2 as r. So r = S + Y = 16 + 21 = 14.\nDefine each Z0's Y9 as l. So l = i + F = 1 + 12 = 13.\nDefine each Z0's Y4 as V. So V = r = 14.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as q. So q = V + l + r = 14 + 13 + 14 = 18.\nDefine each Y4's X5 as z. So z = 21 * q = 21 * 18 = 10.\nDefine each Y2's X5 as A. So A = (V + Z + Y) = (14 + 10 + 21) = 22.\nDefine each Y2's X2 as i. So i = F = 12.\nDefine each Y2's X1 as Y. So Y = A = 22.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as F. So F = Y + A + i = 22 + 22 + 12 = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 4, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y7 equals 13. The number of each Y7's X6 equals 1 more than each Z9's Y7. How many XXX does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["Z9's Y7 as u. So u = 13.\nDefine each Y7's X6 as S. So S = 1 * u = 1 * 13 = 13.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as A. So A = S = 13.\nDefine each Z9's XXX as i. So i = u * A = 13 * 13 = 8.\nThus, the answer is 8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 5, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y5 equals 17. The number of each Z6's Y1 equals 21 times each Z5's Y5. The number of each Z5's Y8 equals 1 times each Z6's Y1. How many Y8 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["Z5's Y5 = 17. Z6's Y1 = 21 * Z5's Y5 = 21 * 17 = 12.\nDefine each Z5's Y8 as u. So u = 1 * Z6's Y1 = 1 * 12 = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 6, "question": "The number of each X2's W5 equals 9. How many WWW does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["X2's W5 as u. So u = 9.\nDefine each X2's WWW as S. So S = u = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 7, "question": "The number of each Y3's X5 equals 2 times each Z4's Y4. The number of each Z4's Y4 equals 8. How many X5 does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Z4's Y4 as u. So u = 8.\nDefine each Y3's X5 as S. So S = 2 * u = 2 * 8 = 16.\nDefine each lollip0 as A. So A = 20.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as i. So i = S = 16.\nDefine each lollip0 as Y. So Y = 20.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as F. So F = Y = 20.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as r. So r = Z5. So r = 5.\nDefine each X5's WWW as l. So l = r = 5.\nDefine each Y9's WWW as V. So V = F * F = 20 * 20 = 9.\nDefine each Z5's WWW as q. So q = Z5's YYY * r = 5 * 5 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 8, "question": "The number of each Y3's X4 equals the sum of each Y2's WWW and each Y0's X4. The number of each Y2's X6 equals 18 times each Y0's X4. The number of each Y0's X4 equals 14. The number of each Y3's X6 equals each X6's WWW. The number of each X6's W5 equals the sum of each Y2's X6 and each Y0's X4. How many XXX does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Y0's X4 as u. So u = 14.\nDefine each Y2's X6 as S. So S = 18 * u = 18 * 14 = 22.\nDefine each X6's W5 as A. So A = S + u = 22 + 14 = 13.\nDefine each X6's WWW as i. So i = A = 13.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as Y. So Y = S * i = 22 * 13 = 10.\nDefine each Y3's X4 as F. So F = Y + u = 10 + 14 = 1.\nDefine each Y3's X6 as r. So r = i = 13.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as l. So l = r + F = 13 + 1 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 9, "question": "The number of each Y4's X0 equals 13 more than each X3's WWW. The number of each X3's W4 equals 19. How many X0 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["X3's W4 as u. So u = 19.\nDefine each X3's WWW as S. So S = u = 19.\nDefine each Y4's X0 as A. So A = 13 * S = 13 * 19 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 10, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y4 equals 16 more than each Z1's Y9. The number of each Z1's Y5 equals 2 more than each Z1's Y9. The number of each Z1's Y9 equals 5. How many YYY does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Z1's Y9 as u. So u = 5.\nDefine each Z1's Y5 as S. So S = 2 * u = 2 * 5 = 10.\nDefine each Z1's Y4 as A. So A = 16 * u = 16 * 5 = 11.\nDefine each Z1's YYY as i. So i = S + A + u = 10 + 11 + 5 = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 11, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y5 equals 2 more than each Z6's Y9. The number of each Z6's Y9 equals 12. How many Y5 does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Z6's Y9 as u. So u = 12.\nDefine each Z6's Y5 as S. So S = 2 * u = 2 * 12 = 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 12, "question": "The number of each Y0's X9 equals the difference of each Y0's X6 and each Y7's X3. The number of each Y0's X6 equals each Y7's X3. The number of each Y7's X3 equals 12. The number of each Y7's X5 equals 19 more than each Y0's XXX. How many XXX does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Y7's X3 as u. So u = 12.\nDefine each Y0's X6 as S. So S = u = 12.\nDefine each Y0's X9 as A. So A = S - u = 12 - 12 = 0.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as i. So i = S + A + A = 12 + 0 + 0 = 12.\nDefine each Y7's X5 as Y. So Y = 19 * i = 19 * 12 = 21.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as F. So F = Y + u = 21 + 12 = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 13, "question": "The number of each Y7's X0 equals 12 times the difference of each Z1's Y0 and each X6's W4. The number of each Z1's Y0 equals 18. The number of each Z8's Y0 equals 1 more than each Z1's Y0. The number of each X6's W4 equals 22 times the sum of each Z8's YYY and each Z8's Y0. How many X0 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Z1's Y0 as u. So u = 18.\nDefine each Z8's Y0 as S. So S = 1 * u = 1 * 18 = 18.\nDefine each Z8's YYY as A. So A = S = 18.\nDefine each X6's W4 as i. So i = 22 * A + S = 22 * 18 + 18 = 0.\nDefine each Y7's X0 as Y. So Y = 12 * u - i = 12 * 18 - 0 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 14, "question": "The number of each X8's W5 equals 0 more than each Z2's Y3. The number of each Z6's Y9 equals the sum of each Y9's WWW, each Y9's X8, each X8's W5 and each Y3's X8. The number of each Z2's Y3 equals 6 more than the sum of each Z6's Y3 and each Y3's X8. The number of each Y9's X7 equals 5 times each Z2's Y3. The number of each X7's W7 equals the sum of each Y9's X7, each Y3's X8 and each X8's W7. The number of each X7's W5 equals 4. The number of each Z6's Y3 equals 14. The number of each Y3's X8 equals 14 more than each Z6's Y3. The number of each Y9's X8 equals 16 times the sum of each Y3's X8 and each Y9's X7. The number of each X8's W7 equals each Y9's X8. How many Y9 does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["14. Z6's Y3 as u. So u = 14.\nDefine each Y3's X8 as S. So S = 14 * u = 14 * 14 = 12.\nDefine each Z2's Y3 as A. So A = 6 * u + S = 6 * 14 + 12 = 19.\nDefine each Y9's X7 as i. So i = 5 + A = 5 + 19 = 1.\nDefine each Y9's X8 as Y. So Y = 16 * S + i = 16 * 12 + 1 = 8.\nDefine each X8's W7 as F. So F = Y = 8.\nDefine each X7's W7 as r. So r = (i + S + F) = (1 + 12 + 8) = 21.\nDefine each X7's W5 as l. So l = 4.\nDefine each X7's WWW as V. So V = l + r = 4 + 21 = 2.\nDefine each Y9's WWW as q. So q = Y * V + i * V = 8 * 2 + 1 * 2 = 18.\nDefine each Z6's Y9 as z. So z = (q + Y + F + S) = (18 + 8 + 8 + 12) = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 15, "question": "The number of each X1's W6 equals 4 more than the sum of each X7's W6, each X7's W1 and each X7's WWW. The number of each X7's W5 equals 17. The number of each X8's W1 equals the sum of each X8's W6 and each X8's W5. The number of each X1's W1 equals 6 more than the sum of each X7's W6 and each X7's W1. The number of each X7's W1 equals 5 times the difference of each X7's W5 and each X7's W6. The number of each X1's W5 equals each X1's W6. The number of each X7's W6 equals 1 more than each X7's W5. The number of each X8's W5 equals the sum of each X1's W1, each X7's W1 and each X1's W6. The number of each X8's W6 equals the sum of each X1's WWW and each X1's W6. How many WWW does each X8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 16, "question": "The number of each Y8's X3 equals 20. The number of each Y8's X5 equals each Y8's X7. The number of each Y8's X7 equals 16 times each Y8's X3. How many XXX does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Y8's X3 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each Y8's X7 as S. So S = 16 * u = 16 * 20 = 21.\nDefine each Y8's X5 as A. So A = S = 21.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as i. So i = S + A + u = 21 + 21 + 20 = 16.\nDefine each X3's WWW as Y. So Y = u = 20.\nDefine each X5's WWW as F. So F = A = 21.\nDefine each Y8's WWW as r. So r = S * F + A * F = 21 * 21 + 21 * 21 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 17, "question": "The number of each Y8's X2 equals 18 more than each Y8's X8. The number of each Y5's X5 equals each Y8's X5. The number of each Y5's X2 equals 13. The number of each Y8's X8 equals each Y5's X5. The number of each Y8's X5 equals each Y5's X2. How many XXX does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["Y5's X2 as u. So u = 13.\nDefine each Y8's X5 as S. So S = u = 13.\nDefine each Y5's X5 as A. So A = S = 13.\nDefine each Y8's X8 as i. So i = A = 13.\nDefine each Y8's X2 as Y. So Y = 18 * i = 18 * 13 = 4.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as F. So F = Y + S + i = 4 + 13 + 13 = 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 18, "question": "The number of each Y8's X2 equals 4. The number of each X2's W6 equals 6 more than the sum of each Y8's XXX and each X1's W6. The number of each Z4's Y8 equals 13 more than each Y8's XXX. The number of each Z1's Y0 equals 15 more than each Z4's Y8. The number of each Z1's Y8 equals 11 more than each Z4's Y0. The number of each Z4's Y0 equals the sum of each Y8's WWW and each X1's W6. The number of each X1's W6 equals 6 times each Z1's Y0. The number of each X2's W8 equals 5 more than each Z4's Y8. How many Y8 does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["8. Z4's Y8 = 13 * Y8's X2 = 13 * 4 = 6.\nDefine each Z1's Y0 as u. So u = 15 * Z4's Y8 = 15 * 6 = 21.\nDefine each X1's W6 as S. So S = 6 * u = 6 * 21 = 11.\nDefine each Y8's X2 as A. So A = 4.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as i. So i = A = 4.\nDefine each X2's W8 as Y. So Y = 5 * Z4's Y8 = 5 * 6 = 7.\nDefine each X2's W6 as F. So F = 6 * i + S = 6 * 4 + 11 = 18.\nDefine each X2's WWW as r. So r = Y + F = 7 + 18 = 2.\nDefine each Y8's WWW as l. So l = A * r = 4 * 2 = 8.\nDefine each Z4's Y0 as V. So V = l + S = 8 + 11 = 19.\nDefine each Z1's Y8 as q. So q = 11 * V = 11 * 19 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 19, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y5 equals 2 more than each Z0's Y1. The number of each Z0's Y1 equals 20. How many YYY does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["Z0's Y1 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each Z5's Y5 as S. So S = 2 * u = 2 * 20 = 17.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as A. So A = S = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 20, "question": "The number of each Y6's X8 equals 0 more than the sum of each Y6's X1, each Y1's X6 and each Y6's X6. The number of each Y6's X6 equals 9 more than each Y1's X6. The number of each Y6's X0 equals 8. The number of each Y6's X1 equals each Y6's X0. The number of each Y1's X6 equals each Y1's X1. The number of each Y1's X1 equals 0. How many XXX does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Y1's X1 as u. So u = 0.\nDefine each Y1's X6 as S. So S = u = 0.\nDefine each Y6's X6 as A. So A = 9 * S = 9 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y6's X0 as i. So i = 8.\nDefine each Y6's X1 as Y. So Y = i = 8.\nDefine each Y6's X8 as F. So F = 0 * (Y + S + A) = 0 * (8 + 0 + 0) = 0.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as r. So r = Y + i + A + F = 8 + 8 + 0 + 0 = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 21, "question": "The number of each Y4's X4 equals 10 times each Z3's XXX. The number of each Z3's Y9 equals 19 more than each Z3's Y1. The number of each Y9's X4 equals 11 times each Z2's Y4. The number of each Y9's X5 equals 15. The number of each Y1's X4 equals the sum of each Y9's X5, each Z2's Y4 and each Z3's Y1. The number of each Z3's Y1 equals 18. The number of each Y4's X5 equals the difference of each Y9's X4 and each Y4's X4. The number of each Z2's Y1 equals 15. The number of each Z5's Y4 equals each Z2's Y1. The number of each Z2's Y4 equals 0 more than the difference of each Z5's Y4 and each Z2's Y1. How many X5 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Z2's Y1. Z5's Y4 = 15.\nDefine each Z2's Y4 as u. So u = 0 * Z5's Y4 - u = 0 * 15 - 15 = 8.\nDefine each Y9's X4 as S. So S = 11 * u = 11 * 8 = 19.\nDefine each Y9's X5 as A. So A = 15.\nDefine each Y1's X4 as i. So i = (A + u + Z3) = (15 + 8 + 3) = 3.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as Y. So Y = i = 3.\nDefine each Z3's Y1 as F. So F = 18.\nDefine each Z3's Y9 as r. So r = 19 * F = 19 * 18 = 20.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as l. So l = S + A = 19 + 15 = 11.\nDefine each Z3's XXX as V. So V = r * l + F * Y = 20 * 11 + 18 * 3 = 19.\nDefine each Y4's X4 as q. So q = 10 * V = 10 * 19 = 6.\nDefine each Y4's X5 as z. So z = S - q = 19 - 6 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 22, "question": "The number of each Y7's X5 equals 18. How many XXX does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["Y7's X5 = 18. Y7's XXX = 18. Y7's XXX = 18. Y7's XXX = 18. Y7's XXX = 18. Y7's XXX = 18. Y7's XXX = 18. Y7's XXX = 18. Y7's XXX = 18. Y7's XXX = 18. Y7's XXX = 18. Y7's XXX = 18. Y7's XXX = 18. Y7's XXX = 18. Y7's XXX = 18. Y7's XXX = 18. Y7's XXX = 18. Y7's XXX = 18. Y7's XXX = 18. Y7's XXX = 18. Y7's XXX = 18. Y7's XXX = 18. Y7's XXX as u. So u = Y7's X5 = 18. Y7's XXX as S. So S = Y7's XXX = 18. Y7's XXX as A. So A = Y7's X5 = 18. Y7's XXX as i. So i = Y7's XXX as Y. So Y = Y = 18.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as F. So F = Y = 18.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as r. So r = Y = 18.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as l. So l = Y = 18.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as V. So V = Y = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 23, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y4 equals 16. The number of each Z2's Y4 equals 16 more than the sum of each Z5's Y1, each Z2's Y0 and each Z5's Y0. The number of each Z5's Y1 equals 15 more than each Z5's Y4. The number of each Z2's Y0 equals 8 more than the difference of each Z5's Y0 and each Z5's YYY. The number of each Z5's Y0 equals 7 more than the sum of each Z5's Y1 and each Z5's Y4. How many Y4 does each Z2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 24, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y2 equals 6. The number of each Z4's Y9 equals 12 more than each Z4's Y2. The number of each Z4's Y3 equals 8 more than each Z0's YYY. The number of each Z0's Y3 equals 1 times each Z0's Y2. The number of each Z6's Y3 equals 3 times each Z5's Y9. The number of each Z5's Y9 equals the difference of each Z4's Y9 and each Z0's YYY. The number of each Z4's Y2 equals each Z4's Y3. How many YYY does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Z0's Y2 as u. So u = 6.\nDefine each Z0's Y3 as S. So S = 1 * u = 1 * 6 = 6.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 6 + 6 = 12.\nDefine each Z4's Y3 as i. So i = 8 * A = 8 * 12 = 4.\nDefine each Z4's Y2 as Y. So Y = i = 4.\nDefine each Z4's Y9 as F. So F = 12 * Y = 12 * 4 = 2.\nDefine each Z5's Y9 as r. So r = F - A = 2 - 12 = 13.\nDefine each Z6's Y3 as l. So l = 3 + r = 3 + 13 = 16.\nDefine each Z6's YYY as V. So V = l = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 25, "question": "The number of each X3's W3 equals 10. The number of each X3's W8 equals 1 more than each X3's W3. How many WWW does each X3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["X3's W3 as u. So u = 10.\nDefine each X3's W8 as S. So S = 1 * u = 1 * 10 = 10.\nDefine each X3's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 10 + 10 = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 26, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y0 equals each Y2's X6. The number of each X8's W0 equals 14 more than each X8's W6. The number of each Y2's X6 equals 1 times each Z5's Y5. The number of each Z5's Y5 equals the difference of each X8's W6 and each Z8's YYY. The number of each X6's W0 equals 8. The number of each Z8's Y0 equals 22 times each X8's W0. The number of each X8's W6 equals each Y0's X8. The number of each Y0's X8 equals each X6's W0. How many Y0 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["X6's W0 = 8. Y0's X8 = X6's W0 = 8.\nDefine each X8's W6 as u. So u = Y0's X8 = 8.\nDefine each X8's W0 as S. So S = 14 * u = 14 * 8 = 20.\nDefine each Z8's Y0 as A. So A = 22 * S = 22 * 20 = 3.\nDefine each Z8's YYY as i. So i = A = 3.\nDefine each Z5's Y5 as Y. So Y = u - i = 8 - 3 = 5.\nDefine each Y2's X6 as F. So F = 1 * Y = 1 * 5 = 5.\nDefine each Z5's Y0 as r. So r = F = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 27, "question": "The number of each Y9's X5 equals the sum of each Y1's XXX and each Y1's X7. The number of each Y0's X7 equals the sum of each Y1's X7 and each Y9's XXX. The number of each Y1's X7 equals 7. How many XXX does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["Y1's X7 as u. So u = 7.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as S. So S = u = 7.\nDefine each Y9's X5 as A. So A = S + u = 7 + 7 = 14.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as i. So i = A = 14.\nDefine each Y0's X7 as Y. So Y = u + i = 7 + 14 = 21.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as F. So F = Y = 21.\nThus, the answer is 21."], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 28, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y7 equals 4. The number of each Y7's X4 equals 11 times each Z4's YYY. The number of each Z7's Y0 equals 5 times each Z7's Y7. The number of each Z4's Y0 equals the sum of each Z4's Y7, each Y0's X8 and each Z7's Y0. The number of each Z4's Y7 equals 19 times each Y0's XXX. The number of each Y0's X4 equals 17 times the difference of each X4's W7 and each Y0's X8. The number of each X4's W7 equals 12 times each Z7's Y0. The number of each Y0's X8 equals each X4's W7. How many X4 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 29, "question": "The number of each Y5's X7 equals 4. The number of each Y9's X8 equals 1 more than each Y5's X7. How many XXX does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Y5's X7 as u. So u = 4.\nDefine each Y9's X8 as S. So S = 1 * u = 1 * 4 = 4.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as A. So A = S = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 30, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y0 equals 18. How many YYY does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["Z5's Y0 = 18.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as u. So u = Z5's YYY = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 31, "question": "The number of each X8's W0 equals 3 more than each Y5's X5. The number of each Y5's X8 equals 3 more than each X8's W0. The number of each X5's W9 equals the difference of each X5's W4 and each X8's W9. The number of each X5's W4 equals 22 more than the sum of each Y5's X5 and each X8's W9. The number of each X8's W9 equals 19. The number of each X8's W4 equals 12 times each X8's W9. The number of each X5's W0 equals each X5's W9. The number of each Y5's X5 equals the difference of each X8's W4 and each X8's W9. How many WWW does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["X8's W9 as u. So u = 19.\nDefine each X8's W4 as S. So S = 12 * u = 12 * 19 = 21.\nDefine each Y5's X5 as A. So A = S - u = 21 - 19 = 2.\nDefine each X8's W0 as i. So i = 3 * A = 3 * 2 = 6.\nDefine each X5's W4 as Y. So Y = 22 * A + u = 22 * 2 + 19 = 17.\nDefine each X5's W9 as F. So F = Y - u = 17 - 19 = 21.\nDefine each X5's W0 as r. So r = F = 21.\nDefine each X5's WWW as l. So l = r + Y + F = 21 + 17 + 21 = 13.\nDefine each Y5's X8 as V. So V = 3 * i = 3 * 6 = 18.\nDefine each X8's WWW as q. So q = S + u + i = 21 + 19 + 6 = 0.\nDefine each Y5's WWW as z. So z = A * l + V * q = 2 * 13 + 18 * 0 = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 32, "question": "The number of each Y2's X0 equals 9. The number of each Y2's X7 equals 17 times each Y2's X0. How many X7 does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Y2's X0 as u. So u = 9.\nDefine each Y2's X7 as S. So S = 17 * u = 17 * 9 = 15.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 15 + 9 = 1.\nDefine each Y1's X0 as i. So i = 23.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as Y. So Y = i = 23.\nDefine each X3's WWW as F. So F = X3's WWW = 3.\nDefine each X5's WWW as r. So r = X5's WWW = 5.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as l. So l = i = 23.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 33, "question": "The number of each X8's W8 equals 3 times the sum of each Z2's YYY and each Z2's Y2. The number of each Z2's Y2 equals 11. How many W8 does each X8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Z2's Y2 as u. So u = 11.\nDefine each Z2's YYY as S. So S = u = 11.\nDefine each X8's W8 as A. So A = 3 * S + u = 3 * 11 + 11 = 21.\nThus, the answer is 21."], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 34, "question": "The number of each X4's W1 equals 17 more than each X6's W3. The number of each X6's W3 equals 19. How many W1 does each X4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["X6's W3 = 19. X4's W1 = 17 * X6's W3 = 17 * 19 = 1.\nDefine each X4's W1 as u. So u = 17 * X6's W3 = 17 * 19 = 1.\nDefine each X6's WWW as S. So S = X6's W3 = 19.\nDefine each X3's WWW as A. So A = X3's W2 = 2.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as i. So i = Y1's A = 2.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as Y. So Y = i = 2.\nDefine each X3's W2 as F. So F = 2.\nDefine each X3's WWW as r. So r = F = 2.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as l. So l = Y + i = 2 + 2 = 4.\nDefine each X6's WWW as V. So V = S = 19.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as q. So q = Y + i + l = 2 + 2 + 4 = 8.\nThus, the answer is 8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 35, "question": "The number of each Y3's X3 equals 5 times each Y3's X7. The number of each Y3's X7 equals each X3's W2. The number of each Y7's X7 equals 21 times the difference of each X3's W2 and each Y3's XXX. The number of each X3's W2 equals 21. How many X7 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["X3's W2 as u. So u = 21.\nDefine each Y3's X7 as S. So S = u = 21.\nDefine each Y3's X3 as A. So A = 5 * S = 5 * 21 = 13.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as i. So i = S + A + u = 21 + 13 + 21 = 9.\nDefine each Y7's X7 as Y. So Y = 21 * u - i = 21 * 21 - 9 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 36, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y9 equals 16. The number of each Z3's Y6 equals 16 more than each Z3's Y9. How many YYY does each Z3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Z3's Y9 = 16. Z3's Y6 = 16 + Z3's YYY = 16 + 3 = 19.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as u. So u = Z3's Y9 + Z3's Y6 = 16 + 19 = 12.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as S. So S = Z3's Y9 + Z3's Y6 = 16 + 19 = 12.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as A. So A = i. So i = 19.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as i. So i = A = 19.\nDefine each Z3's XXX as Y. So Y = Z3's Y9 * A + Z3's Y6 * i = 16 * 19 + 19 * 19 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 37, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y6 equals each Y4's XXX. The number of each Y4's X7 equals 10. The number of each Y4's X8 equals 17. How many Y6 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["Y4's X8 as u. So u = 17.\nDefine each Y4's X7 as S. So S = 10.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 10 + 17 = 4.\nDefine each Z5's Y6 as i. So i = A = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 38, "question": "The number of each Y4's X1 equals 16 times the difference of each X8's W5 and each Y9's X6. The number of each X8's W5 equals 4. The number of each X1's W9 equals 14 times each Y9's XXX. The number of each Y9's X6 equals 22 times each X8's W5. The number of each X8's W9 equals the sum of each Y4's WWW, each Y4's X1 and each X1's WWW. How many W9 does each X8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["X8's W5 as u. So u = 4.\nDefine each Y9's X6 as S. So S = 22 * u = 22 * 4 = 19.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as A. So A = S = 19.\nDefine each X1's W9 as i. So i = 14 * A = 14 * 19 = 13.\nDefine each X1's WWW as Y. So Y = i = 13.\nDefine each Y4's X1 as F. So F = 16 * u - S = 16 * 4 - 19 = 19.\nDefine each Y4's WWW as r. So r = F * Y = 19 * 13 = 17.\nDefine each X8's W9 as l. So l = (r + F + Y) = (17 + 19 + 13) = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 39, "question": "The number of each Z4's Y0 equals 1 times the difference of each Y6's X6 and each Y0's X1. The number of each Y0's X1 equals 18 more than each Y6's X6. The number of each Y6's X6 equals 10. The number of each Z0's Y0 equals 19 times the sum of each Y6's X6 and each Z4's Y0. How many XXX does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["Y6's X6 as u. So u = 10.\nDefine each Y0's X1 as S. So S = 18 * u = 18 * 10 = 19.\nDefine each Z4's Y0 as A. So A = 1 * u - S = 1 * 10 - 19 = 14.\nDefine each Z0's Y0 as i. So i = 19 * u + A = 19 * 10 + 14 = 15.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as Y. So Y = S = 19.\nDefine each Z0's XXX as F. So F = i * Y = 15 * 19 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 40, "question": "The number of each X7's W8 equals each Y3's X4. The number of each X5's W0 equals each Y6's XXX. The number of each X5's W4 equals the difference of each X7's WWW and each Y6's X5. The number of each Y6's X4 equals 18 times each X7's WWW. The number of each Y9's X5 equals 11 times each X5's WWW. The number of each X7's W0 equals 16 times the difference of each Y3's X4 and each X7's W8. The number of each X5's W8 equals 16 times each Y6's X5. The number of each Y8's X5 equals each X5's W0. The number of each Y6's X5 equals each X7's W8. The number of each Y8's X1 equals 7 more than each Y9's X5. The number of each Y3's X4 equals 13. How many XXX does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Y3's X4. X7's W8 as u. So u = the Y3's X4 = 13.\nDefine each X7's W0 as S. So S = 16 * Y3's X4 - u = 16 * 13 - 13 = 11.\nDefine each X7's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 11 + 13 = 1.\nDefine each Y6's X4 as i. So i = 18 * A = 18 * 1 = 18.\nDefine each Y6's X5 as Y. So Y = u = 13.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as F. So F = Y + i = 13 + 18 = 8.\nDefine each X5's W0 as r. So r = F = 8.\nDefine each X5's W8 as l. So l = 16 * Y = 16 * 13 = 1.\nDefine each X5's W4 as V. So V = A - Y = 1 - 13 = 11.\nDefine each X5's WWW as q. So q = V + l + r = 11 + 1 + 8 = 20.\nDefine each Y9's X5 as z. So z = 11 * q = 11 * 20 = 13.\nDefine each Y8's X1 as A. So A = 7 * S = 7 * 13 = 22.\nDefine each Y8's X5 as i. So i = r = 8.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as Y. So Y = i + A = 8 + 22 = 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 41, "question": "The number of each Y6's X6 equals 1. How many X6 does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Y6's X6 = 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 42, "question": "The number of each Y2's X0 equals each Z3's Y2. The number of each Z3's Y2 equals 16. The number of each Y1's X5 equals 7 times the sum of each Z3's Y2, each Y2's X0 and each Z3's XXX. How many X5 does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Z3's Y2 as u. So u = 16.\nDefine each Y2's X0 as S. So S = u = 16.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as A. So A = S = 16.\nDefine each Z3's XXX as i. So i = u * A = 16 * 16 = 3.\nDefine each Y1's X5 as Y. So Y = 7 * (u + S + i) = 7 * (16 + 16 + 3) = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 43, "question": "The number of each X5's W6 equals 12. The number of each X9's W6 equals each X5's W6. The number of each X9's W0 equals 2 times each X9's W6. The number of each X5's W9 equals the difference of each X9's W6 and each X9's W0. How many W9 does each X5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["X5's W6 = 12. X9's W6 = X5's W6. X9's W0 = 2 * X9's W6 = 2 * 12 = 1.\nDefine each X5's W9 as u. So u = A - S = 12 - 1 = 11.\nDefine each X9's W6 as S. So S = u = 11.\nDefine each X9's W0 as A. So A = 2 * S = 2 * 11 = 22.\nDefine each X5's WWW as i. So i = u + Y = 11 + 11 = 22.\nDefine each X9's WWW as Y. So Y = S + A = 11 + 22 = 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So Y = 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10. So 10.\nDefine each Y = 10"], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 44, "question": "The number of each Y8's X7 equals 16 times the difference of each Y9's XXX and each Y9's X5. The number of each Y9's X5 equals 16. The number of each Y8's X5 equals the sum of each Y8's X7, each Y9's XXX and each Y9's X5. The number of each Y7's X2 equals each Y8's XXX. The number of each Y3's X5 equals the difference of each Y9's X5 and each Y7's XXX. How many XXX does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["Y9's X5 as u. So u = 16.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as S. So S = u = 16.\nDefine each Y8's X7 as A. So A = 16 * S - u = 16 * 16 - 16 = 10.\nDefine each Y8's X5 as i. So i = (A + S + u) = (10 + 16 + 16) = 19.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as Y. So Y = i + A = 19 + 10 = 6.\nDefine each Y7's X2 as F. So F = Y = 6.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as r. So r = F = 6.\nDefine each Y3's X5 as l. So l = u - r = 16 - 6 = 10.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as V. So V = l = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 45, "question": "The number of each Y4's X8 equals 15 more than each Y4's X2. The number of each Y0's X2 equals 18. The number of each Z1's Y0 equals each Y4's XXX. The number of each Z1's Y4 equals 6 more than each Z1's Y0. The number of each Y4's X2 equals 13 more than each Y0's X2. How many YYY does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["Y0's X2 as u. So u = 18.\nDefine each Y4's X2 as S. So S = 13 * u = 13 * 18 = 4.\nDefine each Y4's X8 as A. So A = 15 * S = 15 * 4 = 14.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as i. So i = S + A = 4 + 14 = 18.\nDefine each Z1's Y0 as Y. So Y = i = 18.\nDefine each Z1's Y4 as F. So F = 6 * Y = 6 * 18 = 16.\nDefine each Z1's YYY as r. So r = F + Y = 16 + 18 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 46, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y0 equals 2 times each Z1's Y1. The number of each Z4's Y1 equals 13 times each Z4's Y0. The number of each Z1's Y1 equals each Z4's Y1. The number of each Z4's Y0 equals 15. How many YYY does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Z4's Y0 as u. So u = 15.\nDefine each Z4's Y1 as S. So S = 13 * u = 13 * 15 = 11.\nDefine each Z1's Y1 as A. So A = S = 11.\nDefine each Z1's Y0 as i. So i = 2 * A = 2 * 11 = 22.\nDefine each Z1's YYY as Y. So Y = i + A = 22 + 11 = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 47, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y8 equals the sum of each X4's W4, each Y8's X4, each Z8's Y4 and each Y3's X9. The number of each Y3's X9 equals 8 times each X4's W4. The number of each X5's W2 equals 10 times the difference of each Z7's YYY and each Z7's Y8. The number of each Y8's X4 equals 1 times the sum of each Y3's X9, each X4's W4 and each Z8's Y4. The number of each X4's W4 equals 16. The number of each Z8's Y4 equals 7 times the difference of each X4's W4 and each Y3's X9. How many WWW does each X5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["X4's W4 as u. So u = 16.\nDefine each Y3's X9 as S. So S = 8 * u = 8 * 16 = 13.\nDefine each Z8's Y4 as A. So A = 7 * u - S = 7 * 16 - 13 = 11.\nDefine each Y8's X4 as i. So i = 1 * (S + u + A) = 1 * (13 + 16 + 11) = 17.\nDefine each Z7's Y8 as Y. So Y = (u + i + A + S) = (16 + 17 + 11 + 13) = 11.\nDefine each Z7's YYY as F. So F = Y = 11.\nDefine each X5's W2 as r. So r = 10 * F - Y = 10 * 11 - 11 = 6.\nDefine each X5's WWW as l. So l = r = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 48, "question": "The number of each X0's W6 equals 6. The number of each X8's W6 equals each X0's W6. The number of each X0's W4 equals 5 times each X8's WWW. The number of each X8's W4 equals each X0's W6. How many W4 does each X0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["X0's W6 as u. So u = 6.\nDefine each X8's W4 as S. So S = u = 6.\nDefine each X8's W6 as A. So A = u = 6.\nDefine each X8's WWW as i. So i = S + A = 6 + 6 = 12.\nDefine each X0's W4 as Y. So Y = 5 * i = 5 * 12 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 49, "question": "The number of each X7's W3 equals 8 more than each X1's W1. The number of each Y5's X6 equals 13. The number of each X1's W1 equals each Y5's X6. The number of each Z4's Y8 equals 8 times each X7's WWW. The number of each X7's W1 equals 10 times each Z4's Y5. The number of each Z4's Y5 equals 13. The number of each Z4's Y1 equals each X7's W3. How many YYY does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y5's X6 = 13. X1's W1 = Y5's X6 = 13. X7's W3 as u. So u = 8 * X1's W1 = 8 * 13 = 12.\nDefine each Z4's Y1 as S. So S = u = 12.\nDefine each Z4's Y5 as A. So A = 13.\nDefine each X7's W1 as i. So i = 10 * A = 10 * 13 = 15.\nDefine each X7's WWW as Y. So Y = u + i = 12 + 15 = 4.\nDefine each Z4's Y8 as F. So F = 8 * Y = 8 * 4 = 9.\nDefine each Z4's YYY as r. So r = S + A + F = 12 + 13 + 9 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 50, "question": "The number of each Y4's X5 equals 0 times each Y0's X3. The number of each Y0's X3 equals 5 times the sum of each Y0's X5 and each Z2's Y4. The number of each Y4's X3 equals 4. The number of each Z2's Y0 equals 22 more than each Z2's Y4. The number of each Y0's X5 equals 14. The number of each Z2's Y4 equals 2. How many XXX does each Z2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Z2's Y4 as u. So u = 2.\nDefine each Y0's X5 as S. So S = 14.\nDefine each Y0's X3 as A. So A = 5 * S + u = 5 * 14 + 2 = 19.\nDefine each Y4's X5 as i. So i = 0 * A = 0 * 19 = 0.\nDefine each Y4's X3 as Y. So Y = 4.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as F. So F = Y + i = 4 + 0 = 4.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as r. So r = S + A = 14 + 19 = 10.\nDefine each Z2's Y0 as l. So l = 22 + u = 22 + 2 = 1.\nDefine each Z2's XXX as V. So V = l * r + u * F = 1 * 10 + 2 * 4 = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 51, "question": "The number of each Y6's X6 equals 18 more than each Y7's X4. The number of each X4's W6 equals 3 times the sum of each Y6's X6 and each Y7's X4. The number of each Y6's X1 equals 11 times the sum of each Y7's X4, each Y6's X6 and each X1's W8. The number of each X1's W8 equals 6 more than the sum of each Y5's X6, each X4's W6 and each Y7's X4. The number of each Y7's X4 equals 10. The number of each X6's W8 equals 21 more than the sum of each Y6's X6, each Y6's X1 and each X1's W8. The number of each Y5's X6 equals 0 times the sum of each Y7's X4, each X4's W6 and each Y6's X6. How many W8 does each X6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["Y7's X4. Y6's X6 = 18 * Y7's X4 = 18 * 10 = 19.\nDefine each X4's W6 as u. So u = 3 * Y6's X6 + Y7's X4 = 3 * 19 + 10 = 12.\nDefine each Y5's X6 as S. So S = 0 * (Y7's X4 + u + Y = 0 * (10 + 12 + 19) = 0.\nDefine each X1's W8 as A. So A = 6 * (S + u + Y) = 6 * (0 + 12 + 19) = 19.\nDefine each Y6's X1 as i. So i = 11 + (Y7's X4 + u + A) = 11 + (10 + 12 + 19) = 6.\nDefine each X6's W8 as Y. So Y = 21 * (i + i + A) = 21 * (6 + 6 + 19) = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 52, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y3 equals 11. The number of each Y9's X0 equals 16 times each Z9's Y3. How many XXX does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Z9's Y3 as u. So u = 11.\nDefine each Y9's X0 as S. So S = 16 * u = 16 * 11 = 15.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as A. So A = S = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 53, "question": "The number of each Z2's Y8 equals 9 more than each Z4's YYY. The number of each Z4's Y8 equals 2. The number of each Z2's Y4 equals 6 more than each Z4's YYY. The number of each Y4's X2 equals each Z2's YYY. The number of each Z4's Y4 equals 10. How many X2 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Z4's Y4 as u. So u = 10.\nDefine each Z4's Y8 as S. So S = 2.\nDefine each Z4's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 2 + 10 = 12.\nDefine each Z2's Y4 as i. So i = 6 * A = 6 * 12 = 3.\nDefine each Z2's Y8 as Y. So Y = 9 * A = 9 * 12 = 16.\nDefine each Z2's YYY as F. So F = Y + i = 16 + 3 = 19.\nDefine each Y4's X2 as r. So r = F = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 54, "question": "The number of each X6's W9 equals each Y8's XXX. The number of each Y8's X1 equals 17. The number of each X2's W4 equals each X1's WWW. The number of each X1's W9 equals 9. The number of each Y8's X2 equals the sum of each X2's WWW and each X2's W4. How many W9 does each X6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["X1's W9 as u. So u = 9.\nDefine each X1's WWW as S. So S = u = 9.\nDefine each X2's W4 as A. So A = S = 9.\nDefine each X2's WWW as i. So i = A = 9.\nDefine each Y8's X2 as Y. So Y = i + A = 9 + 9 = 18.\nDefine each Y8's X1 as F. So F = 17.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as r. So r = Y + F = 18 + 17 = 12.\nDefine each X6's W9 as l. So l = r = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 55, "question": "The number of each Y4's X9 equals 4. The number of each Y0's X3 equals 10 more than each Y4's X9. How many X3 does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Y4's X9 as u. So u = 4.\nDefine each Y0's X3 as S. So S = 10 * u = 10 * 4 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 56, "question": "The number of each Z4's Y0 equals 18 more than each Z0's YYY. The number of each X3's W6 equals 5. The number of each X9's W4 equals 22 times each Z8's Y5. The number of each Z8's Y5 equals 15 more than each X3's W6. The number of each Z0's Y6 equals 11 more than each X1's W4. The number of each X1's W4 equals 3 times each Y0's X9. The number of each Z1's Y6 equals 7 times the sum of each Z0's Y6 and each Y6's WWW. The number of each Y3's X9 equals 22 more than each Z1's WWW. The number of each X6's W8 equals 0 more than each Z4's Y0. The number of each Y0's X9 equals 7 times the sum of each Z8's Y5 and each X9's W4. The number of each Y6's X6 equals the sum of each X9's W4 and each X6's WWW. The number of each Y5's X3 equals 8 more than each Y3's X9. How many X3 does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 57, "question": "The number of each X4's W1 equals 22. The number of each Y2's X1 equals each X4's W1. How many XXX does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["X4's W1 = 22. Y2's X1 = X4's W1. Y2's XXX = Y2's X2. Y2's XXX = Y2's X2. Y2's XXX = Y2's X1. Y2's XXX = Y2's X2. Y2's XXX = Y2's X1. Y2's XXX = Y2's X2. Y2's XXX = Y2's X2. Y2's XXX = Y2's X2. Y2's XXX = Y2's X2. Y2's XXX = Y2's X2. Y2's XXX = Y2's X2. Y2's XXX = Y2's X2. Y2's XXX = Y2's X2. Y2's XXX = Y2's X2. Y2's XXX = Y2's X2. Y2's XXX = Y2's X2. Y2's XXX = Y2's X2. Y2's X1 = X4's W1. Y2's XXX = Y2's X2. Y2's XXX = Y2's X2. Y2's XXX = Y2's X2. Y2's XXX = Y2's X2. Y2's X1 as u. So u = X4's W1. Y2's XXX as S. So S = Y2's X2 + Y2's X1 + Y2's X1 + u = 22 + 21 + 21 + 21 = 17.\nDefine each X4's W1 as A. So A = 22.\nDefine each Y2's X1 as i. So i = A = 22.\nDefine each Y2's X2 as Y. So Y = A = 22.\nDefine each Y2's X XXX as F. So F = Y + i + u = 22 + 22 + 22 = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 58, "question": "The number of each Y0's X8 equals 4. How many X8 does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["Y0's X8 = 4. So 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 59, "question": "The number of each X9's W0 equals 9 times each Z4's YYY. The number of each Y6's X9 equals 0 times each X9's W0. The number of each Z4's Y0 equals 20 more than each Z1's Y0. The number of each Z1's Y0 equals 13. How many XXX does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Z1's Y0 as u. So u = 13.\nDefine each Z4's Y0 as S. So S = 20 * u = 20 * 13 = 7.\nDefine each Z4's YYY as A. So A = S = 7.\nDefine each X9's W0 as i. So i = 9 * A = 9 * 7 = 17.\nDefine each Y6's X9 as Y. So Y = 0 * i = 0 * 17 = 0.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as F. So F = Y = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 60, "question": "The number of each Y9's X8 equals each Z3's YYY. The number of each Z6's Y5 equals each Y6's XXX. The number of each Z3's Y5 equals the sum of each Y6's X8 and each Z6's Y5. The number of each Y6's X8 equals 10. The number of each Z3's Y6 equals each Z3's Y5. How many XXX does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["Y6's X8 = 10. Y6's XXX = 10. Y9's X8 = Z3's YYY. Y9's XXX as u. So u = Y6's XXX = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 61, "question": "The number of each X3's W1 equals 18 more than each X0's W8. The number of each X1's W2 equals 17 more than each Y3's X0. The number of each X0's W8 equals 21 times each Y1's XXX. The number of each Y2's X3 equals the difference of each Y1's WWW and each X1's WWW. The number of each Y1's X1 equals 14. The number of each Y1's X3 equals each Y3's XXX. The number of each Y3's X0 equals 20 more than each Y1's X1. How many WWW does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["Y1's X1 as u. So u = 14.\nDefine each Y3's X0 as S. So S = 20 * u = 20 * 14 = 4.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as A. So A = S = 4.\nDefine each Y1's X3 as i. So i = A = 4.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as Y. So Y = u + i = 14 + 4 = 18.\nDefine each X0's W8 as F. So F = 21 * Y = 21 * 18 = 10.\nDefine each X3's W1 as r. So r = 18 * F = 18 * 10 = 19.\nDefine each X3's WWW as l. So l = r = 19.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as V. So V = u * Y + i * l = 14 * 18 + 4 * 19 = 19.\nDefine each X1's W2 as q. So q = 17 * S = 17 * 4 = 22.\nDefine each X1's WWW as z. So z = q = 22.\nDefine each Y2's X3 as A. So A = V - S = 19 - 4 = 15.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as i. So i = A * l = 15 * 19 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 62, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y8 equals 3. The number of each X4's W4 equals each Z6's Y8. How many W4 does each X4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["Z6's Y8 = 3. X4's W4 = Z6's Y8.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 63, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y9 equals 6. The number of each Z9's Y9 equals 9 more than the difference of each Z1's Y4 and each Z1's Y9. The number of each Z9's Y4 equals 9 times the sum of each Z9's Y1 and each Z1's Y4. The number of each Z1's Y4 equals each Z1's Y9. The number of each Z9's Y1 equals each Z9's Y9. The number of each Z7's Y4 equals each Z9's YYY. How many Y4 does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Z1's Y9 as u. So u = 6.\nDefine each Z1's Y4 as S. So S = u = 6.\nDefine each Z9's Y9 as A. So A = 9 * S - u = 9 * 6 - 6 = 14.\nDefine each Z9's Y1 as i. So i = A = 14.\nDefine each Z9's Y4 as Y. So Y = 9 * i + S = 9 * 14 + 6 = 15.\nDefine each Z9's YYY as F. So F = Y + A + i = 15 + 14 + 14 = 20.\nDefine each Z7's Y4 as r. So r = F = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 64, "question": "The number of each Y7's X8 equals 9. The number of each Z3's Y7 equals 13 times each Y7's XXX. How many Y7 does each Z3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Y7's X8 = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's X8 = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's X8 = 9. Y7's XXX as u. So u = Y7's X8 + Y7's XXX = 9 + 9 = 18. Y7's XXX as S. So S = Y7's X8 + u = 9 + 18 = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 65, "question": "The number of each X7's W5 equals 5 more than each X2's W5. The number of each X2's W8 equals 9 times each X7's W5. The number of each X2's W5 equals 10. How many W8 does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["X2's W5 as u. So u = 10.\nDefine each X7's W5 as S. So S = 5 * u = 5 * 10 = 4.\nDefine each X2's W8 as A. So A = 9 * S = 9 * 4 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 66, "question": "The number of each Y9's X7 equals 14. The number of each Y2's X7 equals 11 times each Y9's XXX. The number of each Y9's X8 equals 16 more than each Y9's X7. How many XXX does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Y9's X7 as u. So u = 14.\nDefine each Y9's X8 as S. So S = 16 * u = 16 * 14 = 17.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 17 + 14 = 8.\nDefine each Y2's X7 as i. So i = 11 * A = 11 * 8 = 19.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as Y. So Y = i = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 67, "question": "The number of each X2's W8 equals 12 more than the sum of each Y1's XXX, each Y0's X7 and each X0's W0. The number of each Z9's Y0 equals 20. The number of each Z8's Y0 equals each Z9's Y0. The number of each Y1's X2 equals 8 times the sum of each Y1's X7, each Z8's Y0 and each Z9's Y0. The number of each X0's W0 equals the sum of each Y0's X7, each Y1's X7 and each Z9's Y0. The number of each Y0's X7 equals 8 times each Y1's XXX. The number of each X7's W8 equals 19 times the sum of each Y1's X7, each X2's W8 and each Y1's XXX. The number of each Y1's X7 equals 5 times the sum of each Z9's Y0 and each Z8's Y0. How many W8 does each X7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["Z9's Y0. Z8's Y0 = Z9's Y0. Y1's X7 as u. So u = 5 * Z9's Y0 + Z8's Y0 = 5 * 9 + 8 = 17.\nDefine each Y1's X2 as S. So S = 8 + (u + Z8's Y0 + Z9's Y0) = 8 + (17 + 8 + 9) = 19.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 19 + 17 = 13.\nDefine each Y0's X7 as i. So i = 8 * A = 8 * 13 = 12.\nDefine each X0's W0 as Y. So Y = (i + u + Z9's Y0) = (12 + 17 + 9) = 15.\nDefine each X2's W8 as F. So F = 12 * (A + i + Y) = 12 * (13 + 12 + 15) = 19.\nDefine each X7's W8 as r. So r = 19 * (u + F + A) = 19 * (17 + 19 + 13) = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 68, "question": "The number of each Y6's X4 equals 6 times each Z2's Y1. The number of each Z2's Y1 equals 15. How many XXX does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["Z2's Y1 as u. So u = 15.\nDefine each Y6's X4 as S. So S = 6 * u = 6 * 15 = 21.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as A. So A = S = 21.\nThus, the answer is 21."], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 69, "question": "The number of each X0's W6 equals 19 times each Y5's X0. The number of each X7's W0 equals 0. The number of each Y5's X0 equals 17 more than each X7's W0. The number of each X3's W0 equals each X0's W6. How many W0 does each X3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["X7's W0 = 0. Y5's X0 = 17 * X7 = 17 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X0's W6 as u. So u = 19 * Y5's X0 = 19 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X3's W0 as S. So S = u = 0.\nDefine each X3's WWW as A. So A = S = 0.\nDefine each X7's WWW as i. So i = 0.\nDefine each Y5's X0 as Y. So Y = 17 * X7 = 17 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X0's WWW as F. So F = u = 0.\nDefine each Y5's WWW as r. So r = Y * F = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X7's W0 as l. So l = 0.\nDefine each Y5's WWW as V. So V = Y * F = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X7's WWW as q. So q = l = 0.\nDefine each Y5's WWW as z. So z = Y * V = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X3's W0 as A. So A = S = 0.\nDefine each X3's WWW as i. So i = A = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 70, "question": "The number of each Y2's X7 equals 17. The number of each Y2's X4 equals 14 times the sum of each Y2's X7, each Y6's X4 and each Y6's XXX. The number of each Y6's X4 equals 1 more than each Y2's X7. How many X4 does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Y2's X7 as u. So u = 17.\nDefine each Y6's X4 as S. So S = 1 * u = 1 * 17 = 17.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as A. So A = S = 17.\nDefine each Y2's X4 as i. So i = 14 * (u + S + A) = 14 * (17 + 17 + 17) = 19.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as Y. So Y = u + i = 17 + 19 = 13.\nDefine each X3's WWW as F. So F = Y = 13.\nDefine each X3's WWW as r. So r = F = 13.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as l. So l = S * r = 17 * 13 = 14.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as V. So V = u * Y + i * l = 17 * 13 + 19 * 14 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 71, "question": "The number of each Z4's Y6 equals 10. How many Y6 does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Z4's Y6 = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 72, "question": "The number of each Z4's Y4 equals 13. How many Y4 does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["Z4's Y4 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 73, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y9 equals 21 times each Y1's X4. The number of each Z6's Y1 equals 20 times the sum of each Y9's X4 and each Z6's Y9. The number of each Y9's X4 equals each Z6's Y9. The number of each Y1's X4 equals 3. The number of each Y0's X4 equals 0 more than each Z6's Y1. How many X4 does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["Y1's X4 as u. So u = 3.\nDefine each Z6's Y9 as S. So S = 21 * u = 21 * 3 = 17.\nDefine each Y9's X4 as A. So A = S = 17.\nDefine each Z6's Y1 as i. So i = 20 * A + S = 20 * 17 + 17 = 12.\nDefine each Y0's X4 as Y. So Y = 0 * i = 0 * 12 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 74, "question": "The number of each Y9's X1 equals 22. The number of each Y1's X0 equals each Z1's XXX. The number of each Y1's X1 equals each Y9's X1. The number of each Z1's Y9 equals the difference of each Y9's X1 and each Y9's XXX. How many XXX does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["Y9's X1 as u. So u = 22.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as S. So S = u = 22.\nDefine each Z1's Y9 as A. So A = u - S = 22 - 22 = 0.\nDefine each Z1's XXX as i. So i = A * S = 0 * 22 = 0.\nDefine each Y1's X0 as Y. So Y = i = 0.\nDefine each Y1's X1 as F. So F = u = 22.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as r. So r = Y + F = 0 + 22 = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 75, "question": "The number of each X0's W0 equals 16 times the difference of each X1's W0 and each X1's WWW. The number of each X1's W0 equals 0 more than the difference of each X1's W5 and each X2's W5. The number of each X2's W5 equals 15. The number of each X1's W5 equals each X2's W5. How many W0 does each X0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["X2's W5 = 15. X1's W5 as u. So u = S = 15.\nDefine each X1's W0 as S. So S = 0 * u - u = 0 * 15 - 15 = 8.\nDefine each X1's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 8 + 15 = 0.\nDefine each X0's W0 as i. So i = 16 * S - A = 16 * 8 - 0 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 76, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y5 equals 4. The number of each Z9's Y5 equals 17 times each Z5's Y7. The number of each Z5's Y7 equals 22 times each Z0's Y5. How many Y5 does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Z0's Y5 = 4. Z5's Y7 = 22 * Z0's Y5 = 22 * 4 = 19.\nDefine each Z9's Y5 as u. So u = 17 * Z5's Y7 = 17 * 19 = 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 77, "question": "The number of each Y9's X4 equals 9. The number of each X8's W1 equals 2 more than each Y9's X4. The number of each X4's W9 equals 3 more than the sum of each X8's W1, each Y9's X8 and each X4's W1. The number of each Y9's X8 equals 14 times each Y9's X4. The number of each Y5's X4 equals 8 times each Z0's WWW. The number of each X4's W1 equals 15 more than each Y9's X8. The number of each Z0's Y9 equals 13 times each Y9's X4. How many X4 does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Y9's X4 as u. So u = 9.\nDefine each Y9's X8 as S. So S = 14 * u = 14 * 9 = 11.\nDefine each X4's W1 as A. So A = 15 * S = 15 * 11 = 4.\nDefine each X8's W1 as i. So i = 2 * u = 2 * 9 = 18.\nDefine each X4's W9 as Y. So Y = 3 * (i + S + A) = 3 * (18 + 11 + 4) = 19.\nDefine each X4's WWW as F. So F = Y + A = 19 + 4 = 0.\nDefine each Y9's WWW as r. So r = S * F + u * F = 11 * 0 + 9 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z0's Y9 as l. So l = 13 + u = 13 + 9 = 22.\nDefine each Z0's WWW as V. So V = l * r = 22 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y5's X4 as q. So q = 8 * V = 8 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 78, "question": "The number of each Y8's X8 equals each Y6's X9. The number of each Y6's X3 equals 4 times the difference of each Y6's X8 and each Y6's X0. The number of each Y6's X8 equals 0. The number of each Y8's X0 equals 6 more than each Y8's X3. The number of each Y6's X9 equals 5 more than the sum of each Y6's X8 and each Y6's X0. The number of each Y6's X0 equals 2. The number of each Y8's X3 equals 10 more than each Y6's X8. The number of each Y8's X9 equals the difference of each Y6's XXX and each Y6's X0. How many XXX does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["Y6's X0 = 2.\nDefine each Y6's X8 as u. So u = 0.\nDefine each Y6's X3 as S. So S = 4 * u - u = 4 * 0 - 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y6's X9 as A. So A = 5 * u + u = 5 * 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as i. So i = S + A + u = 0 + 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y8's X9 as Y. So Y = i - u = 0 - 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y8's X3 as F. So F = 10 * u = 10 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y8's X8 as r. So r = A = 0.\nDefine each Y8's X0 as l. So l = 6 + F = 6 + 0 = 6.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as V. So V = l + r + Y + F = 6 + 0 + 0 + 0 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 79, "question": "The number of each X2's W7 equals 16 times each Y3's X5. The number of each Y3's X5 equals 8. The number of each Z0's Y3 equals 0. The number of each Z4's Y6 equals 7 times each Z0's WWW. The number of each Y6's X2 equals each Y3's X5. The number of each X5's W7 equals 8 more than each Y3's X5. The number of each Y6's X7 equals 18 more than each Y6's X2. The number of each X7's W1 equals the sum of each Y3's WWW and each X5's W7. How many WWW does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y3's X5 as u. So u = 8.\nDefine each X5's W7 as S. So S = 8 * u = 8 * 8 = 18.\nDefine each X5's WWW as A. So A = S = 18.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as i. So i = u * A = 8 * 18 = 6.\nDefine each X7's W1 as Y. So Y = i + S = 6 + 18 = 1.\nDefine each X2's W7 as F. So F = 16 * u = 16 * 8 = 13.\nDefine each X2's WWW as r. So r = F = 13.\nDefine each Y6's X2 as l. So l = u = 8.\nDefine each Y6's X7 as V. So V = 18 * l = 18 * 8 = 6.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as q. So q = V * A + l * r = 6 * 18 + 8 * 13 = 19.\nDefine each Z0's Y3 as z. So z = 0.\nDefine each Z0's WWW as A. So A = z * i = 0 * 6 = 0.\nDefine each Z4's Y6 as i. So i = 7 * A = 7 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z4's WWW as Y. So Y = i * q = 0 * 19 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 80, "question": "The number of each Y1's X7 equals 5 times the sum of each Y5's XXX, each Y5's X7 and each Y3's X7. The number of each Y3's X7 equals 22 more than each Y5's X2. The number of each Y5's X7 equals 0 times the sum of each Y3's X7 and each Y5's X2. The number of each Y5's X2 equals 15. How many X7 does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["Y5's X2 as u. So u = 15.\nDefine each Y3's X7 as S. So S = 22 * u = 22 * 15 = 8.\nDefine each Y5's X7 as A. So A = 0 * S + u = 0 * 8 + 15 = 15.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as i. So i = u + A = 15 + 15 = 7.\nDefine each Y1's X7 as Y. So Y = 5 * (i + A + S) = 5 * (7 + 15 + 8) = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 81, "question": "The number of each X6's W8 equals 5 more than each X8's W5. The number of each X8's W5 equals each Z5's Y9. The number of each Z5's Y9 equals 3. The number of each Y5's X6 equals 19 times the difference of each X8's W5 and each X6's W8. The number of each Z9's Y9 equals 17 times each Z4's Y6. The number of each Z7's Y5 equals the difference of each X6's WWW and each X8's W5. The number of each Z4's Y6 equals the sum of each X8's W5, each X9's WWW and each Z5's Y9. The number of each X9's W8 equals the difference of each Z7's WWW and each X6's WWW. The number of each X2's W0 equals 18 times each Z9's Y9. How many W0 does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Z4's Y6 = (i + WWW + Z5's Y9) = (17 + 17 + 3) = 14.\nDefine each Z9's Y9 as u. So u = 17 * Z4's Y6 = 17 * 14 = 8.\nDefine each X2's W0 as S. So S = 18 * u = 18 * 8 = 6.\nDefine each X8's W5 as A. So A = Z5's Y9 = 3.\nDefine each X6's W8 as i. So i = 5 * A = 5 * 3 = 15.\nDefine each X6's WWW as Y. So Y = i = 15.\nDefine each Y5's X6 as F. So F = 19 * A - i = 19 * 3 - 15 = 19.\nDefine each Y5's WWW as r. So r = F * Y = 19 * 15 = 9.\nDefine each Z7's Y5 as l. So l = Y - A = 15 - 3 = 12.\nDefine each Z7's WWW as V. So V = l * r = 12 * 9 = 16.\nDefine each X9's W8 as q. So q = V - Y = 16 - 15 = 1.\nDefine each X9's WWW as z. So z = q = 1.\nDefine each Z4's Y6 as A. So A = (A + S + Z5's Y9) = (3 + 6 + 3) = 12.\nDefine each Z9's Y9 as i. So i = 17 * A = 17 * 12 = 20.\nDefine each X2's W0 as Y. So Y = 18 * i = 18 * 20 = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 82, "question": "The number of each Y6's X2 equals 2. How many X2 does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Y6's X2 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 83, "question": "The number of each Y0's X5 equals 10 more than each X9's WWW. The number of each X9's W1 equals 7 more than each Z8's Y0. The number of each Z5's Y7 equals 0 more than each Y7's X9. The number of each X9's W8 equals 22 times the sum of each Z8's Y0 and each X9's W1. The number of each Z8's Y0 equals 16. The number of each Y7's X9 equals each Y0's X5. How many Y7 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["Z8's Y0 = 16. X9's W1 as u. So u = 7 * Z8's Y0 = 7 * 16 = 20.\nDefine each X9's W8 as S. So S = 22 * Z8's Y0 + u = 22 * 16 + 20 = 14.\nDefine each X9's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 14 + 20 = 11.\nDefine each Y0's X5 as i. So i = 10 * A = 10 * 11 = 18.\nDefine each Y7's X9 as Y. So Y = i = 18.\nDefine each Z5's Y7 as F. So F = 0 * Y = 0 * 18 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 84, "question": "The number of each Y5's X2 equals 19. How many XXX does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Y5's X2 = 19. Y5's XXX = 19. Y6's X2 = 21. Y6's XXX as i. So i = Y6's X2 = 21.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as Y. So Y = i = 21.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as A. So A = Y = 19.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as i. So i = Y = 21.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as Y. So Y = Y = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 85, "question": "The number of each Y5's X4 equals 1. The number of each Z6's Y4 equals 19 more than each Y4's XXX. The number of each Y4's X0 equals 21 more than each Y4's X4. The number of each Z0's Y4 equals each Y5's XXX. The number of each Y5's X0 equals each Z6's Y5. The number of each Z6's Y5 equals 15 more than each Y5's X4. The number of each Y4's X4 equals the difference of each Z0's Y4 and each Y5's X0. How many Y4 does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Y5's X4 = 1. Y5's X0 = 15 + Z6's Y5 = 15 + 15 = 7.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as u. So u = Y5's X4 + Y5's X0 = 1 + 7 = 8.\nDefine each Z0's Y4 as S. So S = u = 8.\nDefine each Y4's X4 as A. So A = S - u = 8 - 8 = 0.\nDefine each Y4's X0 as i. So i = 21 * A = 21 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as Y. So Y = i + A = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z6's Y4 as F. So F = 19 * Y = 19 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 86, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y3 equals 11 times each Y7's X2. The number of each Z4's Y7 equals 3. The number of each Z6's Y7 equals the sum of each Y7's X2 and each Y7's XXX. The number of each Y7's X2 equals 9 times each Z4's Y7. The number of each Y7's X7 equals 6. How many YYY does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["Y7's X7 as u. So u = 6.\nDefine each Z4's Y7 as S. So S = 3.\nDefine each Y7's X2 as A. So A = 9 * S = 9 * 3 = 4.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as i. So i = A + u = 4 + 6 = 10.\nDefine each Z6's Y7 as Y. So Y = A + i = 4 + 10 = 14.\nDefine each Z6's Y3 as F. So F = 11 * A = 11 * 4 = 21.\nDefine each Z6's YYY as r. So r = F + Y = 21 + 14 = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 87, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y4 equals 13 times each Z4's Y7. The number of each Z4's Y7 equals 9. How many Y4 does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Z4's Y7 as u. So u = 9.\nDefine each Z6's Y4 as S. So S = 13 + u = 13 + 9 = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 88, "question": "The number of each X7's W9 equals 20. The number of each X7's W7 equals 20 times each X9's W7. The number of each X9's W7 equals each X5's W9. The number of each Y4's X5 equals 3 times each Y7's WWW. The number of each X5's W9 equals each X5's W7. The number of each Y7's X7 equals 0 more than the difference of each X5's W9 and each X7's W9. The number of each Y4's X4 equals each Y7's WWW. The number of each Y8's X7 equals each Y4's XXX. The number of each X5's W7 equals 17. How many WWW does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["X5's W7 as u. So u = 17.\nDefine each X5's W9 as S. So S = u = 17.\nDefine each X9's W7 as A. So A = S = 17.\nDefine each X7's W7 as i. So i = 20 * A = 20 * 17 = 18.\nDefine each X7's W9 as Y. So Y = 20.\nDefine each X7's WWW as F. So F = Y + i = 20 + 18 = 15.\nDefine each Y7's X7 as r. So r = 0 * S - Y = 0 * 17 - 20 = 3.\nDefine each Y7's WWW as l. So l = r * F = 3 * 15 = 22.\nDefine each Y4's X4 as V. So V = l = 22.\nDefine each Y4's X5 as q. So q = 3 + l = 3 + 22 = 2.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as z. So z = q + V = 2 + 22 = 1.\nDefine each Y8's X7 as A. So A = z = 1.\nDefine each Y8's WWW as i. So i = A * F = 1 * 15 = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 89, "question": "The number of each X4's W8 equals 19 times each Z4's Y0. The number of each Z8's Y0 equals 10. The number of each Z4's Y0 equals 10 more than each Z8's YYY. The number of each Y0's X3 equals 7 more than each Y8's WWW. The number of each Y8's X4 equals each X4's WWW. How many X3 does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["Z8's Y0 = 10. Z8's YYY = 10. Z4's Y0 = 10 * Z8's Y0 = 10 * 10 = 8.\nDefine each X4's W8 as u. So u = 19 * Z4's Y0 = 19 * 8 = 14.\nDefine each X4's WWW as S. So S = u = 14.\nDefine each Y8's X4 as A. So A = S = 14.\nDefine each Y8's WWW as i. So i = A * S = 14 * 14 = 12.\nDefine each Y0's X3 as Y. So Y = 7 * i = 7 * 12 = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 90, "question": "The number of each X3's W6 equals each X6's W6. The number of each X1's W6 equals each X6's WWW. The number of each X6's W8 equals each X6's W6. The number of each X3's W4 equals the difference of each X6's W8 and each X4's W0. The number of each X1's W0 equals 10 more than each X1's W8. The number of each X6's W6 equals 12 more than each X4's W0. The number of each X1's W8 equals the difference of each X6's W0 and each X1's W4. The number of each X3's W8 equals 18 more than each X3's W6. The number of each X3's W0 equals each X6's WWW. The number of each X1's W4 equals 1 times each X3's WWW. The number of each X6's W0 equals 8 times each X4's W0. The number of each X4's W0 equals 3. How many WWW does each X1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 91, "question": "The number of each X0's W1 equals 19. The number of each X1's W1 equals 16 more than each X0's W1. The number of each X1's W3 equals 0 more than each X0's W1. How many WWW does each X1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["X0's W1 = 19. X1's W1 as u. So u = 16 * X0's W1 = 16 * 19 = 5.\nDefine each X1's W3 as S. So S = 0 * X0's W1 = 0 * 19 = 0.\nDefine each X1's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 0 + 5 = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 92, "question": "The number of each Y6's X7 equals each Y7's X1. The number of each Y7's X1 equals 3. The number of each X4's W6 equals each Y6's X7. How many W6 does each X4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["Y7's X1 as u. So u = 3.\nDefine each Y6's X7 as S. So S = u = 3.\nDefine each X4's W6 as A. So A = S = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 93, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y3 equals the sum of each Z4's XXX and each Z4's Y2. The number of each Z4's Y2 equals 19 more than each Y2's X2. The number of each Y3's X7 equals the difference of each Z1's Y3 and each Z8's Y3. The number of each Y7's X7 equals 0 more than each Z1's XXX. The number of each Y3's X2 equals 4 times each Z8's Y3. The number of each Z8's Y3 equals 1 more than each Y2's XXX. The number of each Y2's X2 equals 19. How many X7 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Y2's X2 as u. So u = 19.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as S. So S = u = 19.\nDefine each Z8's Y3 as A. So A = 1 * S = 1 * 19 = 19.\nDefine each Y3's X2 as i. So i = 4 * A = 4 * 19 = 7.\nDefine each Z4's Y2 as Y. So Y = 19 * u = 19 * 19 = 16.\nDefine each Z4's XXX as F. So F = Y * S = 16 * 19 = 5.\nDefine each Z1's Y3 as r. So r = F + Y = 5 + 16 = 21.\nDefine each Y3's X7 as l. So l = r - A = 21 - 19 = 2.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as V. So V = l + i = 2 + 7 = 9.\nDefine each Z1's XXX as q. So q = r * V = 21 * 9 = 5.\nDefine each Y7's X7 as z. So z = 0 * q = 0 * 5 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 94, "question": "The number of each X5's W6 equals the difference of each X0's W6 and each X6's W9. The number of each X6's W6 equals 18 times the sum of each X0's W6, each X6's W8 and each X6's W9. The number of each X5's W4 equals 21. The number of each X0's W6 equals 0. The number of each X6's W9 equals 5. The number of each X5's W8 equals each X6's WWW. The number of each X6's W8 equals 8. The number of each X6's W4 equals 22 times each X6's W9. How many WWW does each X5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["X6's W9 as u. So u = 5.\nDefine each X6's W4 as S. So S = 22 * u = 22 * 5 = 18.\nDefine each X0's W6 as A. So A = 0.\nDefine each X6's W8 as i. So i = 8.\nDefine each X6's W6 as Y. So Y = 18 * (A + i + u) = 18 * (0 + 8 + 5) = 19.\nDefine each X6's WWW as F. So F = Y + S + i + u = 19 + 18 + 8 + 5 = 4.\nDefine each X5's W8 as r. So r = F = 4.\nDefine each X5's W4 as l. So l = 21.\nDefine each X5's W6 as V. So V = A - u = 0 - 5 = 18.\nDefine each X5's WWW as q. So q = V + l + r = 18 + 21 + 4 = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 95, "question": "The number of each Y5's X9 equals 13. The number of each Y7's X2 equals each X2's W9. The number of each Y2's X9 equals 18 times the difference of each X5's W9 and each X9's W9. The number of each Y7's X5 equals 10 times the difference of each X5's W9 and each Y5's X9. The number of each X9's W9 equals 19 more than each Y7's X5. The number of each X5's W9 equals 3 times each Y5's X9. The number of each X2's W9 equals the sum of each X5's W9, each Y5's X9, each Y2's WWW and each X9's W9. How many X2 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["Y5's X9 = 13. X5's W9 = 3 * Y5's X9 = 3 * 13 = 16.\nDefine each Y7's X5 as u. So u = 10 * A - Y5's X9 = 10 * 13 - 13 = 2.\nDefine each X9's W9 as S. So S = 19 * u = 19 * 2 = 15.\nDefine each Y2's X9 as A. So A = 18 * X5's W9 - S = 18 * 16 - 15 = 17.\nDefine each X9's WWW as i. So i = S = 15.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as Y. So Y = A * i = 17 * 15 = 2.\nDefine each X2's W9 as F. So F = (i + Y + u + S) = (15 + 2 + 2 + 15) = 11.\nDefine each Y7's X2 as r. So r = F = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 96, "question": "The number of each Y2's X0 equals 21. The number of each Y5's X1 equals 10 more than each Y2's X0. How many XXX does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["Y2's X0 = 21. Y5's X1 = 10 * Y2's X0 = 10 * 21 = 3.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as u. So u = Y5's X1 = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 97, "question": "The number of each Z2's Y7 equals 2. How many Y7 does each Z2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Z2's Y7 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 98, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y3 equals 22. How many Y3 does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["Z9's Y3 = 22. So 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 99, "question": "The number of each Z2's Y9 equals 12. The number of each Y7's X1 equals each Z2's YYY. The number of each Z2's Y7 equals 2 more than each Y7's X6. The number of each Y7's X6 equals 16 more than each Y9's X6. The number of each Y9's X6 equals 4. How many X1 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["Y9's X6 as u. So u = 4.\nDefine each Y7's X6 as S. So S = 16 * u = 16 * 4 = 18.\nDefine each Z2's Y7 as A. So A = 2 * S = 2 * 18 = 13.\nDefine each Z2's Y9 as i. So i = 12.\nDefine each Z2's YYY as Y. So Y = i + A + u = 12 + 13 + 4 = 6.\nDefine each Y7's X1 as F. So F = Y = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 100, "question": "The number of each X7's W9 equals 11 more than the sum of each X7's W3 and each X7's W1. The number of each X1's W3 equals 9 times the sum of each X7's W9, each X7's W1 and each X7's WWW. The number of each X7's W3 equals 2. The number of each X7's W1 equals 9. How many W3 does each X1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["X7's W1 as u. So u = 9.\nDefine each X7's W3 as S. So S = 2.\nDefine each X7's W9 as A. So A = 11 * S + u = 11 * 2 + 9 = 8.\nDefine each X7's WWW as i. So i = S + A + u = 2 + 8 + 9 = 19.\nDefine each X1's W3 as Y. So Y = 9 * (A + u + i) = 9 * (8 + 9 + 19) = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 101, "question": "The number of each Y9's X5 equals each X5's W4. The number of each X6's W1 equals 12 more than each X5's W4. The number of each X5's W4 equals 15. The number of each X5's W1 equals each X6's W1. The number of each Y9's X6 equals each X5's W1. The number of each X6's W4 equals 10 more than the sum of each X5's W1, each X5's W4 and each Y9's X5. How many WWW does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["X5's W4 as u. So u = 15.\nDefine each X6's W1 as S. So S = 12 * u = 12 * 15 = 19.\nDefine each X5's W1 as A. So A = S = 19.\nDefine each Y9's X6 as i. So i = A = 19.\nDefine each Y9's X5 as Y. So Y = u = 15.\nDefine each X6's W4 as F. So F = 10 * (A + u + Y) = 10 * (19 + 15 + 15) = 19.\nDefine each X6's WWW as r. So r = S + F = 19 + 19 = 15.\nDefine each X5's WWW as l. So l = A + u = 19 + 15 = 11.\nDefine each Y9's WWW as V. So V = Y * l + i * r = 15 * 11 + 19 * 15 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 102, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y6 equals 6. How many Y6 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Z5's Y6 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 103, "question": "The number of each X0's W2 equals 14. The number of each X1's W2 equals 14 times the sum of each X3's WWW, each X0's W2 and each X0's WWW. The number of each X3's W2 equals 15 more than the sum of each X0's WWW and each X0's W2. The number of each X2's W0 equals 6 times the sum of each X1's WWW, each X3's W2 and each X1's W2. How many WWW does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["X0's W2 as u. So u = 14.\nDefine each X0's WWW as S. So S = u = 14.\nDefine each X3's W2 as A. So A = 15 * S + u = 15 * 14 + 14 = 17.\nDefine each X3's WWW as i. So i = A = 17.\nDefine each X1's W2 as Y. So Y = 14 + (i + u + S) = 14 + (17 + 14 + 14) = 13.\nDefine each X1's WWW as F. So F = Y = 13.\nDefine each X2's W0 as r. So r = 6 * (F + A + Y) = 6 * (13 + 17 + 13) = 19.\nDefine each X2's WWW as l. So l = r = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 104, "question": "The number of each X0's W9 equals 17. The number of each X7's W1 equals 18 more than each X0's W9. The number of each X9's W9 equals 21. The number of each X9's W1 equals 15 times each X7's WWW. The number of each X9's W6 equals 21. How many WWW does each X9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["X0's W9 = 17. X7's W1 = 18 * X0's W9 = 18 * 17 = 7.\nDefine each X7's WWW as u. So u = 7.\nDefine each X9's W1 as S. So S = 15 * u = 15 * 7 = 13.\nDefine each X9's W6 as A. So A = 21.\nDefine each X9's W9 as i. So i = 21.\nDefine each X9's WWW as Y. So Y = S + A + i = 13 + 21 + 21 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 105, "question": "The number of each Y8's X4 equals 10. The number of each X5's W6 equals the sum of each Y8's X4 and each X5's W5. The number of each X0's W6 equals 12 times each X5's WWW. The number of each X5's W5 equals 4. The number of each X4's W6 equals 4 times each Y4's WWW. The number of each Y5's X0 equals each X4's WWW. The number of each Y4's X5 equals 17 times each X5's WWW. How many WWW does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["X5's W5 as u. So u = 4.\nDefine each X5's W6 as S. So S = Y8's X4 + u = 8 + 4 = 12.\nDefine each X5's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 12 + 4 = 16.\nDefine each Y4's X5 as i. So i = 17 * A = 17 * 16 = 19.\nDefine each Y4's WWW as Y. So Y = i * A = 19 * 16 = 5.\nDefine each X4's W6 as F. So F = 4 * Y = 4 * 5 = 20.\nDefine each X4's WWW as r. So r = F = 20.\nDefine each Y5's X0 as l. So l = r = 20.\nDefine each X0's W6 as V. So V = 12 * A = 12 * 16 = 8.\nDefine each X0's WWW as q. So q = V = 8.\nDefine each Y5's WWW as z. So z = l * q = 20 * 8 = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 106, "question": "The number of each Y8's X5 equals 16. The number of each Y8's X9 equals 15 more than each Y8's X5. How many XXX does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Y8's X5 as u. So u = 16.\nDefine each Y8's X9 as S. So S = 15 * u = 15 * 16 = 10.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 10 + 16 = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 107, "question": "The number of each X7's W6 equals 17 more than the difference of each X0's WWW and each X0's W7. The number of each X7's W7 equals the sum of each X0's W6, each X0's WWW and each X0's W1. The number of each X0's W8 equals 19. The number of each X7's W8 equals 11 more than the sum of each X7's W6 and each X0's W8. The number of each X0's W1 equals 17 more than each X0's W6. The number of each X0's W7 equals 8 more than the difference of each X0's W1 and each X0's W6. The number of each X0's W6 equals 12. How many WWW does each X7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["X0's W6 as u. So u = 12.\nDefine each X0's W1 as S. So S = 17 * u = 17 * 12 = 20.\nDefine each X0's W7 as A. So A = 8 * S - u = 8 * 20 - 12 = 1.\nDefine each X0's W8 as i. So i = 19.\nDefine each X0's WWW as Y. So Y = S + A + i + u = 20 + 1 + 19 + 12 = 6.\nDefine each X7's W6 as F. So F = 17 * Y - A = 17 * 6 - 1 = 10.\nDefine each X7's W8 as r. So r = 11 * F + i = 11 * 10 + 19 = 17.\nDefine each X7's W7 as l. So l = (u + Y + S) = (12 + 6 + 20) = 15.\nDefine each X7's WWW as V. So V = l + r + F = 15 + 17 + 10 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 108, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y0 equals 13 more than the difference of each Z0's Y5 and each Z9's Y2. The number of each Z0's Y5 equals 20. The number of each Z9's Y2 equals each Z0's Y5. The number of each Z9's Y8 equals 5 times the sum of each Z0's YYY and each Z9's Y0. How many YYY does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Z0's Y5 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each Z9's Y2 as S. So S = u = 20.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as A. So A = u = 20.\nDefine each Z9's Y0 as i. So i = 13 + u - S = 13 + 20 - 20 = 13.\nDefine each Z9's Y8 as Y. So Y = 5 * A + i = 5 * 20 + 13 = 18.\nDefine each Z9's YYY as F. So F = Y + S + i = 18 + 20 + 13 = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 109, "question": "The number of each Y7's X2 equals 0. The number of each Y0's X2 equals 18 more than each Y7's X2. How many X2 does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["Y7's X2 = 0. Y0's X2 = 18 * Y7's X2 = 18 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 110, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y8 equals 1 more than each Z7's Y0. The number of each Z3's Y8 equals each Z7's Y0. The number of each Z2's Y8 equals the difference of each Z6's YYY and each Z3's Y8. The number of each Z2's Y5 equals 13. The number of each Z3's Y0 equals 4 more than each Z7's YYY. The number of each Y5's X8 equals the difference of each Z3's YYY and each Z3's Y8. The number of each Z2's Y0 equals the sum of each Z7's Y0, each Z3's Y0 and each Y5's X8. The number of each Z6's Y8 equals the difference of each Z2's Y0 and each Z3's YYY. The number of each Z7's Y0 equals each Z2's Y5. The number of each Z3's Y7 equals 17 more than each Z7's YYY. The number of each Y8's X2 equals 11. The number of each Y8's X9 equals the sum of each Z6's Y8 and each Z2's Y8. How many XXX does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Z2's Y5 as u. So u = 13.\nDefine each Z7's Y0 as S. So S = u = 13.\nDefine each Z7's Y8 as A. So A = 1 * S = 1 * 13 = 13.\nDefine each Z7's YYY as i. So i = S + A = 13 + 13 = 3.\nDefine each Z3's Y7 as Y. So Y = 17 * i = 17 * 3 = 5.\nDefine each Z3's Y0 as F. So F = 4 * i = 4 * 3 = 12.\nDefine each Z2's Y8 as r. So r = Y - F = 5 - 12 = 16.\nDefine each Z6's Y8 as l. So l = r - i = 16 - 3 = 13.\nDefine each Z6's YYY as V. So V = l = 13.\nDefine each Y5's X8 as q. So q = V - F = 13 - 12 = 1.\nDefine each Z2's Y0 as z. So z = (S + F + q) = (13 + 12 + 1) = 3.\nDefine each Y8's X2 as A. So A = 11.\nDefine each Y8's X9 as i. So i = l + r = 13 + 16 = 6.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as Y. So Y = i + A = 6 + 11 = 17.\nDefine each Z6's XXX as F. So F = l * Y = 13 * 17 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 111, "question": "The number of each Y2's X7 equals 6 more than each Y2's X1. The number of each Y2's X1 equals 21 times each Y4's X1. The number of each Y4's X1 equals 17. How many X7 does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["Y4's X1 as u. So u = 17.\nDefine each Y2's X1 as S. So S = 21 * u = 21 * 17 = 12.\nDefine each Y2's X7 as A. So A = 6 * S = 6 * 12 = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 112, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y5 equals 3. The number of each Z3's Y3 equals 5 times each Z3's Y5. The number of each Z9's Y5 equals 10 times the difference of each Z3's YYY and each Z3's Y3. How many Y5 does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["Z3's Y5 = 3. Z3's Y3 = 5 * Z3's Y5 = 5.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as u. So u = Z3's Y5 + Z3's Y3 = 3 + 5 = 8.\nDefine each Z9's Y5 as S. So S = 10 * u - u = 10 * 8 - 8 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 113, "question": "The number of each Y6's X9 equals each Z6's Y6. The number of each X2's W5 equals 19. The number of each Y6's X2 equals each X2's W5. The number of each Z6's Y6 equals 7. How many XXX does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["Z6's Y6 as u. So u = 7.\nDefine each Y6's X9 as S. So S = u = 7.\nDefine each X2's W5 as A. So A = 19.\nDefine each Y6's X2 as i. So i = A = 19.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as Y. So Y = S + i = 7 + 19 = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 114, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y6 equals 14. How many Y6 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Z5's Y6 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 115, "question": "The number of each Y5's X0 equals 4. How many X0 does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["Y5's X0 = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 116, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y1 equals 11. The number of each Z6's Y8 equals each Z6's Y1. How many YYY does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["Z6's Y1 as u. So u = 11.\nDefine each Z6's Y8 as S. So S = u = 11.\nDefine each Z6's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 11 + 11 = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 117, "question": "The number of each X2's W9 equals 20. The number of each Y0's X2 equals each X7's WWW. The number of each X7's W9 equals 0 more than each X2's W9. The number of each X2's W0 equals 21 more than each X7's W9. The number of each Y0's X7 equals the sum of each X2's W0 and each X2's W9. The number of each X7's W0 equals 9 times each X2's W9. The number of each Y8's X7 equals each Y0's WWW. The number of each Y8's X2 equals the sum of each Y8's X7 and each X7's WWW. How many WWW does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["Y0's X7 as u. So u = X2's W9 + X2's W0 = 20.\nDefine each X7's W0 as S. So S = 9 * X2's W9 = 9 * 20 = 19.\nDefine each X7's W9 as A. So A = 0 * X2's W9 = 0 * 20 = 0.\nDefine each X7's WWW as i. So i = S + A = 19 + 0 = 19.\nDefine each X2's W0 as Y. So Y = 21 * A = 21 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X2's W9 as F. So F = 20.\nDefine each Y0's X2 as r. So r = i = 19.\nDefine each Y0's X7 as l. So l = Y + F = 0 + 20 = 20.\nDefine each Y0's WWW as V. So V = l * i + r * A = 20 * 19 + 19 * 0 = 12.\nDefine each Y8's X7 as q. So q = V = 12.\nDefine each Y8's X2 as z. So z = q + i = 12 + 19 = 8.\nDefine each Y8's WWW as A. So A = q * i + z * A = 12 * 19 + 8 * 0 = 21.\nThus, the answer is 21."], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 118, "question": "The number of each X8's W1 equals each Y1's X8. The number of each Y8's X5 equals 22 times each Z6's WWW. The number of each X5's W0 equals 4 more than each Y1's WWW. The number of each Y1's X8 equals 7. The number of each Z7's Y8 equals 21 more than each Y1's X8. The number of each X5's W9 equals each Z6's WWW. The number of each Z6's Y1 equals 4 times each Y1's WWW. How many WWW does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["Y1's X8 = 7. Z6's Y1 as u. So u = 4 * Y1's X8 = 4 * 7 = 5.\nDefine each X8's W1 as S. So S = u = 5.\nDefine each X8's WWW as A. So A = S = 5.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as i. So i = Y1's X8 * A = 7 * 5 = 12.\nDefine each Z6's WWW as Y. So Y = u * i = 5 * 12 = 14.\nDefine each X5's W9 as F. So F = Y = 14.\nDefine each X5's W0 as r. So r = 4 * i = 4 * 12 = 2.\nDefine each X5's WWW as l. So l = r + F = 2 + 14 = 16.\nDefine each Y8's X5 as V. So V = 22 * Y = 22 * 14 = 9.\nDefine each Y8's WWW as q. So q = V * l = 9 * 16 = 6.\nDefine each Z7's Y8 as z. So z = 21 * u = 21 * 5 = 13.\nDefine each Z7's WWW as A. So A = z * q = 13 * 6 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 119, "question": "The number of each Y8's X3 equals the difference of each X4's W4 and each Y8's X5. The number of each X5's W4 equals 8 times the sum of each X4's W4 and each X4's W2. The number of each X4's W2 equals 10. The number of each X4's W4 equals 17 times each X4's W2. The number of each Y8's X5 equals 6 more than each X5's WWW. The number of each Y8's X4 equals 3. How many XXX does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["Y8's X4 as u. So u = 3.\nDefine each X4's W2 as S. So S = 10.\nDefine each X4's W4 as A. So A = 17 * S = 17 * 10 = 9.\nDefine each X5's W4 as i. So i = 8 * A + S = 8 * 9 + 10 = 17.\nDefine each X5's WWW as Y. So Y = i = 17.\nDefine each Y8's X5 as F. So F = 6 * Y = 6 * 17 = 10.\nDefine each Y8's X3 as r. So r = A - F = 9 - 10 = 22.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as l. So l = r + F + u = 22 + 10 + 3 = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 120, "question": "The number of each Y6's X5 equals 8 more than each Y8's XXX. The number of each Y6's X0 equals 7 times each Y6's X5. The number of each Y8's X0 equals 13. The number of each Z9's Y6 equals 10 times the sum of each Y8's X0, each Y8's XXX and each Y6's X5. How many XXX does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Y8's X0 = 13. Y8's XXX as u. So u = Y8's XXX = 13.\nDefine each Y6's X5 as S. So S = 8 * u = 8 * 13 = 12.\nDefine each Y6's X0 as A. So A = 7 * S = 7 * 12 = 15.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as i. So i = S + A = 12 + 15 = 4.\nDefine each Z9's Y6 as Y. So Y = 10 * (Y + u + S) = 10 * (10 + 13 + 12) = 19.\nDefine each Z9's XXX as F. So F = Y * i = 19 * 4 = 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 121, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y1 equals each Z9's Y8. The number of each Z9's Y8 equals 19 times each Z1's Y6. The number of each Z1's Y6 equals 10. The number of each Z9's Y6 equals the difference of each Z9's Y1 and each Z1's Y6. How many YYY does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["Z1's Y6 as u. So u = 10.\nDefine each Z9's Y8 as S. So S = 19 * u = 19 * 10 = 6.\nDefine each Z9's Y1 as A. So A = S = 6.\nDefine each Z9's Y6 as i. So i = A - u = 6 - 10 = 19.\nDefine each Z9's YYY as Y. So Y = S + A + i = 6 + 6 + 19 = 8.\nThus, the answer is 8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 122, "question": "The number of each Y2's X1 equals 18 more than each Y5's X1. The number of each Y7's X1 equals the difference of each Y6's XXX and each Y7's X9. The number of each Y6's X1 equals the difference of each Y5's X1 and each Y2's X1. The number of each Y6's X4 equals each Y2's XXX. The number of each Y7's X9 equals the sum of each Y6's XXX, each Y6's X4 and each Y2's XXX. The number of each Y5's X1 equals 20. How many XXX does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Y5's X1 = 20. Y2's X1 as u. So u = 18 * Y5's X1 = 18 * 20 = 15.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as S. So S = u = 15.\nDefine each Y6's X4 as A. So A = S = 15.\nDefine each Y6's X1 as i. So i = Y5's X1 - u = 20 - 15 = 5.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as Y. So Y = A + i = 15 + 5 = 20.\nDefine each Y7's X9 as F. So F = (Y + A + S) = (20 + 15 + 15) = 4.\nDefine each Y7's X1 as r. So r = Y - F = 20 - 4 = 16.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as l. So l = r + F = 16 + 4 = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 123, "question": "The number of each X9's W8 equals 1 more than the sum of each Y9's X9 and each X2's W9. The number of each Y7's X2 equals the sum of each X9's W8 and each X3's W8. The number of each X5's W9 equals each X9's W8. The number of each X3's W8 equals 0 more than each Y9's WWW. The number of each X5's W8 equals 20 more than each X9's W8. The number of each X9's W9 equals the sum of each X2's W9 and each X9's W8. The number of each X5's W1 equals 10. The number of each Y9's X9 equals 22 more than each X2's W9. The number of each Y9's X5 equals 7 more than each X9's WWW. The number of each X2's W9 equals 12. How many X2 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["X2's W9 as u. So u = 12.\nDefine each Y9's X9 as S. So S = 22 * u = 22 * 12 = 11.\nDefine each X9's W8 as A. So A = 1 * S + u = 1 * 11 + 12 = 0.\nDefine each X9's W9 as i. So i = u + A = 12 + 0 = 12.\nDefine each X9's WWW as Y. So Y = A + i = 0 + 12 = 12.\nDefine each Y9's X5 as F. So F = 7 + Y = 7 + 12 = 19.\nDefine each X5's W1 as r. So r = 10.\nDefine each X5's W8 as l. So l = 20 * A = 20 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X3's W8 as V. So V = 0 * Y = 0 * 12 = 0.\nDefine each Y7's X2 as q. So q = A + V = 0 + 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 124, "question": "The number of each Y6's X6 equals the sum of each Y1's X8 and each Y8's X6. The number of each Y6's X7 equals 2. The number of each Y1's X8 equals 6 more than each Y8's X6. The number of each Y8's X7 equals each Y6's X7. The number of each Y9's X6 equals the difference of each Y8's X8 and each Y8's X7. The number of each Y8's X8 equals each Y1's X7. The number of each Y8's X6 equals 19 times each Y6's X7. The number of each Y9's X8 equals 20 times each Y8's X8. The number of each Y1's X7 equals 3 times each Y6's X6. The number of each Y9's X3 equals the sum of each Y8's X6 and each Y8's X7. How many XXX does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Y6's X7 as u. So u = 2.\nDefine each Y8's X6 as S. So S = 19 * u = 19 * 2 = 15.\nDefine each Y1's X8 as A. So A = 6 * S = 6 * 15 = 21.\nDefine each Y6's X6 as i. So i = A + S = 21 + 15 = 13.\nDefine each Y1's X7 as Y. So Y = 3 * i = 3 * 13 = 16.\nDefine each Y8's X8 as F. So F = Y = 16.\nDefine each Y9's X8 as r. So r = 20 * F = 20 * 16 = 21.\nDefine each Y8's X7 as l. So l = u = 2.\nDefine each Y9's X3 as V. So V = S + l = 15 + 2 = 17.\nDefine each Y9's X6 as q. So q = F - l = 16 - 2 = 14.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as z. So z = V + q + r = 17 + 14 + 21 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 125, "question": "The number of each Y5's X5 equals 1 more than each X5's WWW. The number of each X5's W7 equals 19 more than each Y7's XXX. The number of each Y7's X4 equals 17. How many WWW does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["Y7's X4 as u. So u = 17.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as S. So S = u = 17.\nDefine each X5's W7 as A. So A = 19 * S = 19 * 17 = 1.\nDefine each X5's WWW as i. So i = A = 1.\nDefine each Y5's X5 as Y. So Y = 1 * i = 1 * 1 = 1.\nDefine each Y5's WWW as F. So F = Y * i = 1 * 1 = 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 126, "question": "The number of each Y6's X1 equals 14 more than the sum of each X1's W6 and each Y3's X1. The number of each Z8's Y4 equals 12 times the difference of each Z4's WWW and each Z9's Y3. The number of each Y4's X5 equals 6 more than the sum of each X5's WWW, each X1's W6 and each Z4's Y4. The number of each X5's W6 equals 15 more than each X1's W6. The number of each Y3's X1 equals 9 times the sum of each Z9's Y3, each Z8's WWW and each Z8's Y4. The number of each Z4's Y4 equals 14 times the difference of each X1's W6 and each X5's W6. The number of each Z9's Y3 equals the sum of each Z4's WWW, each Y4's X5 and each X5's W6. The number of each X1's W6 equals 17. How many X1 does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["17. X1's W6 = 17. X5's W6 = 15 * u = 15 * 17 = 2.\nDefine each X5's WWW as u. So u = 2.\nDefine each Z4's Y4 as S. So S = 14 * u - u = 14 * 2 - 2 = 3.\nDefine each Y4's X5 as A. So A = 6 * (u + u + S) = 6 * (2 + 2 + 3) = 1.\nDefine each Y4's WWW as i. So i = A * u = 1 * 2 = 2.\nDefine each Z4's WWW as Y. So Y = S * i = 3 * 2 = 6.\nDefine each Z9's Y3 as F. So F = (Y + A + u) = (6 + 1 + 2) = 9.\nDefine each Z8's Y4 as r. So r = 12 * Y - F = 12 * 6 - 9 = 19.\nDefine each Z8's WWW as l. So l = r * i = 19 * 2 = 15.\nDefine each Y3's X1 as V. So V = 9 * (F + l + u) = 9 * (9 + 15 + 2) = 1.\nDefine each X1's W6 as q. So q = 17.\nDefine each X5's W6 as z. So z = 15 + q = 15 + 17 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 127, "question": "The number of each X5's W7 equals each X6's W6. The number of each X6's W6 equals 14 times the sum of each X7's W0 and each X7's W3. The number of each X7's W0 equals 12. The number of each X7's W3 equals 8 times each X7's W0. How many W7 does each X5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["X7's W0 + X7's W3 = 12.\nDefine each X7's W0 as u. So u = 12.\nDefine each X7's W3 as S. So S = 8 * u = 8 * 12 = 4.\nDefine each X6's W6 as A. So A = 14 * u + S = 14 * 12 + 4 = 21.\nDefine each X5's W7 as i. So i = A = 21.\nThus, the answer is 21."], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 128, "question": "The number of each Z4's Y9 equals 2. The number of each Z8's Y9 equals 10 times each Z4's YYY. How many YYY does each Z8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Z4's Y9 = 2.\nDefine each Z4's YYY as u. So u = Y9 + 2 = 11.\nDefine each Z8's Y9 as S. So S = 10 * u = 10 * 11 = 18.\nDefine each Z8's YYY as A. So A = S = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 129, "question": "The number of each Z2's Y3 equals the sum of each Z7's Y3, each Y0's X4 and each Y0's X2. The number of each Z7's Y3 equals 8. The number of each X2's W0 equals each Y7's X4. The number of each Z7's Y0 equals each X2's W0. The number of each Y0's X2 equals each Y0's X4. The number of each Y7's X4 equals 1 more than each Z2's YYY. The number of each Y0's X4 equals 18 more than each Z7's Y3. How many Y0 does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Z7's Y3 as u. So u = 8.\nDefine each Y0's X4 as S. So S = 18 * u = 18 * 8 = 6.\nDefine each Y0's X2 as A. So A = S = 6.\nDefine each Z2's Y3 as i. So i = (u + S + A) = (8 + 6 + 6) = 20.\nDefine each Z2's YYY as Y. So Y = i = 20.\nDefine each Y7's X4 as F. So F = 1 * Y = 1 * 20 = 20.\nDefine each X2's W0 as r. So r = F = 20.\nDefine each Z7's Y0 as l. So l = r = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 130, "question": "The number of each Y3's X5 equals 1. The number of each Y0's X8 equals 12 times each Y3's X5. The number of each Y0's X2 equals 19. The number of each Z7's Y3 equals each Z1's XXX. The number of each Z1's Y0 equals the sum of each Y0's X8 and each Y0's XXX. How many Y3 does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["Y3's X5 as u. So u = 1.\nDefine each Y0's X8 as S. So S = 12 * u = 12 * 1 = 12.\nDefine each Y0's X2 as A. So A = 19.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as i. So i = S + A = 12 + 19 = 8.\nDefine each Z1's Y0 as Y. So Y = S + i = 12 + 8 = 20.\nDefine each Z1's XXX as F. So F = Y * i = 20 * 8 = 22.\nDefine each Z7's Y3 as r. So r = F = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 131, "question": "The number of each Y4's X4 equals 12. How many X4 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["Y4's X4 = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 132, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y0 equals 18 more than each Z4's Y7. The number of each Z4's Y7 equals 10. How many Y0 does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Z4's Y7 as u. So u = 10.\nDefine each Z1's Y0 as S. So S = 18 * u = 18 * 10 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 133, "question": "The number of each X8's W4 equals each X6's W1. The number of each X6's W1 equals 4. The number of each Y9's X9 equals each X8's W4. The number of each Y1's X8 equals 5 more than each Y9's X9. How many X8 does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["X6's W1 = 4. X8's W4 = 4. X6's W1 = 4. X8's WWW = X6's W1. X6's W1 = 4. X8's WWW = X6's W1. X8's WWW = X6's W1. X6's W1 = 4. X8's WWW = X6's W1. X8's WWW = X6's W1. X6's W1 = 4. X8's W4 as u. So u = X6's W1. X8's WWW as S. So S = u = 4.\nDefine each X6's W1 as A. So A = 4.\nDefine each X8's W4 as i. So i = A = 4.\nDefine each X8's WWW as Y. So Y = i + S + u = 4 + 4 + 4 = 12.\nDefine each Y9's X9 as F. So F = u = 4.\nDefine each Y1's X8 as r. So r = 5 * F = 5 * 4 = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 134, "question": "The number of each Y9's X2 equals 16 more than each X3's W3. The number of each Y9's X5 equals each Y2's XXX. The number of each Y2's X2 equals each X3's W3. The number of each X3's W3 equals 21. The number of each Y2's X4 equals each X3's W3. How many XXX does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["X3's W3 = 21. Y2's X2 as u. So u = X3's W3 = 21.\nDefine each Y2's X4 as S. So S = X3's W3 = 21.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 21 + 21 = 19.\nDefine each Y9's X5 as i. So i = A = 19.\nDefine each Y9's X2 as Y. So Y = 16 * X3's W3 = 16 * 21 = 14.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as F. So F = Y + i = 14 + 19 = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 135, "question": "The number of each Z4's Y8 equals 14. How many Y8 does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Z4's Y8 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 136, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y8 equals 7 times each Z4's Y8. The number of each Z4's Y8 equals 8. How many YYY does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Z4's Y8 as u. So u = 8.\nDefine each Z9's Y8 as S. So S = 7 * u = 7 * 8 = 10.\nDefine each Z9's YYY as A. So A = S = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 137, "question": "The number of each Z4's Y2 equals 19. The number of each Z1's Y2 equals each Z4's Y2. How many YYY does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Z4's Y2 as u. So u = 19.\nDefine each Z1's Y2 as S. So S = u = 19.\nDefine each Z1's YYY as A. So A = S = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 138, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y1 equals 11. How many Y1 does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["Z9's Y1 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 139, "question": "The number of each X8's W5 equals 4. The number of each X5's W5 equals the difference of each X8's W5 and each X8's WWW. How many WWW does each X5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["X8's W5 as u. So u = 4.\nDefine each X8's WWW as S. So S = u = 4.\nDefine each X5's W5 as A. So A = u - S = 4 - 4 = 0.\nDefine each X5's WWW as i. So i = A = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 140, "question": "The number of each Y3's X6 equals the sum of each Z8's YYY and each Z3's YYY. The number of each Y9's X6 equals 9. The number of each Y8's X6 equals each Y9's X4. The number of each Z8's Y3 equals each Y3's X4. The number of each Y3's X4 equals each Y9's X4. The number of each Z3's Y9 equals each Z8's YYY. The number of each Z3's Y8 equals 22 more than each Z3's Y3. The number of each Z8's Y8 equals each Z8's Y3. The number of each Y9's X4 equals 15 more than each Y9's X6. The number of each Y8's X4 equals 14 more than each Y9's X6. The number of each Z3's Y3 equals the difference of each Y8's XXX and each Y8's X6. The number of each Z8's Y9 equals each Z3's Y8. How many X6 does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Y9's X6 as u. So u = 9.\nDefine each Y9's X4 as S. So S = 15 * u = 15 * 9 = 20.\nDefine each Y8's X6 as A. So A = S = 20.\nDefine each Y8's X4 as i. So i = 14 * u = 14 * 9 = 11.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as Y. So Y = A + i = 20 + 11 = 8.\nDefine each Z3's Y3 as F. So F = Y - A = 8 - 20 = 11.\nDefine each Z3's Y8 as r. So r = 22 * F = 22 * 11 = 12.\nDefine each Z8's Y9 as l. So l = r = 12.\nDefine each Y3's X4 as V. So V = S = 20.\nDefine each Z8's Y3 as q. So q = V = 20.\nDefine each Z8's Y8 as z. So z = q = 20.\nDefine each Z8's YYY as A. So A = l + q + Z = 12 + 20 + 20 = 6.\nDefine each Z3's Y9 as i. So i = A = 6.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as Y. So Y = F + i + r = 11 + 6 + 12 = 6.\nDefine each Y3's X6 as F. So F = A + Y = 20 + 6 = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 141, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y9 equals 18. The number of each Y3's X9 equals the difference of each Z9's WWW and each Z1's Y9. The number of each Z9's Y9 equals 7 more than each X9's W5. The number of each X9's W5 equals 0 more than each Z1's Y9. The number of each Y9's X9 equals 2 more than each X9's W5. How many X9 does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["Z1's Y9 = 18. X9's W5 = 0 * Z1's Y9 = 0 * 18 = 0.\nDefine each X9's WWW as u. So u = X9's W5 = 0.\nDefine each Y9's X9 as S. So S = 2 * u = 2 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y9's WWW as A. So A = S * u = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z9's Y9 as i. So i = 7 * u = 7 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z9's WWW as Y. So Y = i * A = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y3's X9 as F. So F = Y - Z1's Y9 = 0 - 18 = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 142, "question": "The number of each Y5's X6 equals 7. How many XXX does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["Y5's X6 = 7. Y5's XXX = 7. Y6's X6 = 13. Y6's XXX as i. So i = Y6's X6 = 13.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as Y. So Y = Y = 13.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as F. So F = Y = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 143, "question": "The number of each Y4's X1 equals 2 more than the difference of each Y4's X4 and each Y4's X6. The number of each Y4's X7 equals 9. The number of each Y8's X4 equals each Y4's XXX. The number of each Y4's X6 equals 8. The number of each Y8's X7 equals the difference of each Y4's X1 and each Y4's X7. The number of each Y5's X4 equals the sum of each Y8's X4 and each Y8's XXX. The number of each Y4's X4 equals 16. How many X4 does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["Y4's X4 as u. So u = 16.\nDefine each Y4's X6 as S. So S = 8.\nDefine each Y4's X1 as A. So A = 2 * u - S = 2 * 16 - 8 = 1.\nDefine each Y4's X7 as i. So i = 9.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as Y. So Y = S + A + i + u = 8 + 1 + 9 + 16 = 11.\nDefine each Y8's X4 as F. So F = Y = 11.\nDefine each Y8's X7 as r. So r = A - i = 1 - 9 = 15.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as l. So l = r + F = 15 + 11 = 3.\nDefine each Y5's X4 as V. So V = F + l = 11 + 3 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 144, "question": "The number of each Y2's X9 equals 12. The number of each X9's W0 equals 8 more than each X3's W1. The number of each X3's W1 equals 12. The number of each X3's W0 equals 8 times each X3's W1. The number of each Y8's X9 equals each Y2's WWW. The number of each Y2's X3 equals each X3's WWW. The number of each X9's W1 equals 5 more than the difference of each X3's W0 and each X3's W1. How many XXX does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["X3's W1 as u. So u = 12.\nDefine each X3's W0 as S. So S = 8 * u = 8 * 12 = 4.\nDefine each X3's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 4 + 12 = 16.\nDefine each Y2's X3 as i. So i = A = 16.\nDefine each X9's W1 as Y. So Y = 5 * S - u = 5 * 4 - 12 = 14.\nDefine each X9's W0 as F. So F = 8 * u = 8 * 12 = 4.\nDefine each X9's WWW as r. So r = Y + F = 14 + 4 = 18.\nDefine each Y2's X9 as l. So l = 12.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as V. So V = l * r + i * A = 12 * 18 + 16 * 16 = 19.\nDefine each Y8's X9 as q. So q = V = 19.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as z. So z = q = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 145, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y0 equals 9 more than each Z6's Y7. The number of each Z6's Y7 equals 13. How many Y0 does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["Z6's Y7 as u. So u = 13.\nDefine each Z9's Y0 as S. So S = 9 * u = 9 * 13 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 146, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y7 equals each Z7's Y1. The number of each Z7's Y7 equals 15. The number of each Z1's Y1 equals the sum of each Z7's Y7 and each Z7's YYY. The number of each Z7's Y1 equals 4 more than each Z7's Y7. How many YYY does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["Z7's Y7 as u. So u = 15.\nDefine each Z7's Y1 as S. So S = 4 * u = 4 * 15 = 14.\nDefine each Z7's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 14 + 15 = 6.\nDefine each Z1's Y1 as i. So i = u + A = 15 + 6 = 21.\nDefine each Z1's Y7 as Y. So Y = S = 14.\nDefine each Z1's YYY as F. So F = Y + i = 14 + 21 = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 147, "question": "The number of each Y1's X4 equals 1. The number of each Y8's X4 equals each Y1's X4. How many XXX does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Y1's X4 as u. So u = 1.\nDefine each Y8's X4 as S. So S = u = 1.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as A. So A = S = 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 148, "question": "The number of each Y3's X5 equals 10. The number of each X8's W9 equals 10 times each Y3's XXX. The number of each X5's W9 equals 14 more than each X8's WWW. How many WWW does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["Y3's X5 = 10. Y3's XXX = 10. X8's W9 = 10 * Y3's XXX = 10 * 10 = 8.\nDefine each X8's WWW as u. So u = 8.\nDefine each X5's W9 as S. So S = 14 * u = 14 * 8 = 20.\nDefine each X5's WWW as A. So A = S = 20.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as i. So i = Y3's A = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 149, "question": "The number of each Y7's X8 equals 2. The number of each Z5's Y6 equals each Y7's X8. How many Y6 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Y7's X8 = 2.\nDefine each Z5's Y6 as u. So u = Y7's X8 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 150, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y1 equals 5. How many Y1 does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Z7's Y1 as u. So u = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 151, "question": "The number of each X6's W1 equals 21 more than each X0's W7. The number of each X0's W7 equals 14. How many WWW does each X6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["X0's W7 as u. So u = 14.\nDefine each X6's W1 as S. So S = 21 * u = 21 * 14 = 18.\nDefine each X6's WWW as A. So A = S = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 152, "question": "The number of each X1's W3 equals 12. How many W3 does each X1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["X1's W3 = 12.\nDefine each X1's WWW as u. So u = X1's W3 = 12.\nDefine each Y1's l0 as S. So S = 20.\nDefine each Y1's l0 as A. So A = 20.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as i. So i = S + A = 20 + 20 = 17.\nDefine each Z9's Y1 as Y. So Y = 9.\nDefine each Z9's YYY as F. So F = Y = 9.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as r. So r = S + A = 20 + 20 = 17.\nDefine each Z9's XXX as l. So l = Y * i = 9 * 17 = 15.\nDefine each X3's W3 as V. So V = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 153, "question": "The number of each Y9's X1 equals 14. The number of each Y4's X2 equals 22 times each Y0's X5. The number of each X1's W3 equals each X2's WWW. The number of each X1's W9 equals 7. The number of each Y0's X5 equals 22 more than each X5's W1. The number of each Y6's X5 equals 22 more than each Y4's X2. The number of each X2's W9 equals the sum of each Y6's X5 and each X5's W1. The number of each X5's W1 equals 21 times each Y9's XXX. How many WWW does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Y9's X1 as u. So u = 14.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as S. So S = u = 14.\nDefine each X5's W1 as A. So A = 21 * S = 21 * 14 = 18.\nDefine each Y0's X5 as i. So i = 22 * A = 22 * 18 = 5.\nDefine each Y4's X2 as Y. So Y = 22 * i = 22 * 5 = 18.\nDefine each Y6's X5 as F. So F = 22 * Y = 22 * 18 = 5.\nDefine each X2's W9 as r. So r = F + A = 5 + 18 = 0.\nDefine each X2's WWW as l. So l = r = 0.\nDefine each X1's W3 as V. So V = l = 0.\nDefine each X1's W9 as q. So q = 7.\nDefine each X1's WWW as z. So z = q + V = 7 + 0 = 7.\nDefine each Y9's WWW as A. So A = u * Z = 14 * 7 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 154, "question": "The number of each X2's W1 equals 19. How many W1 does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["X2's W1 = 19. So 19.\nDefine each X2's WWW as u. So u = X2's W1 = 19.\nDefine each Y1's l0 as S. So S = 21.\nDefine each Y1's l0 as A. So A = 21.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as i. So i = S + A = 21 + 21 = 19.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as l. So l = S + A = 21 + 21 = 19.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as V. So V = S + A = 21 + 21 = 19.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as q. So q = S + V = 21 + 19 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 155, "question": "The number of each X1's W6 equals 19. The number of each Y1's X8 equals each X8's WWW. The number of each X3's W9 equals 19 more than each Z2's Y4. The number of each Z2's Y4 equals 0 times each Y1's X8. The number of each Z7's Y1 equals 4 times each X1's W6. The number of each X8's W4 equals 3 times each Z7's Y1. How many W9 does each X3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["X1's W6 = 19. Z7's Y1 = 4 * X1's W6 = 4 * 19 = 7.\nDefine each X8's W4 as u. So u = 3 * Z7's Y1 = 3 * 7 = 21.\nDefine each X8's WWW as S. So S = u = 21.\nDefine each Y1's X8 as A. So A = S = 21.\nDefine each Z2's Y4 as i. So i = 0 * A = 0 * 21 = 0.\nDefine each X3's W9 as Y. So Y = 19 * i = 19 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 156, "question": "The number of each Y0's X9 equals 17. How many X9 does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["Y0's X9 = 17. So 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 157, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y1 equals each Y9's X5. The number of each Z5's Y9 equals the sum of each Y9's X5, each Y1's X4 and each Z5's Y1. The number of each X5's W3 equals 18 more than the difference of each Z5's YYY and each Y1's X4. The number of each Y9's X5 equals 7. The number of each Y1's X4 equals each Y9's X5. How many W3 does each X5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Y9's X5 as u. So u = 7.\nDefine each Y1's X4 as S. So S = u = 7.\nDefine each Z5's Y1 as A. So A = u = 7.\nDefine each Z5's Y9 as i. So i = (u + S + A) = (7 + 7 + 7) = 21.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as Y. So Y = i + A = 21 + 7 = 5.\nDefine each X5's W3 as F. So F = 18 * Y - S = 18 * 5 - 7 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 158, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y3 equals 16 more than the difference of each Z0's Y3 and each Z7's Y1. The number of each Z7's Y1 equals each Z0's Y1. The number of each Z8's Y9 equals 15. The number of each Z0's Y1 equals 2 times each Z0's Y3. The number of each Z0's Y3 equals the difference of each Z8's YYY and each Z8's Y9. The number of each Z0's Y9 equals 21 times each Z7's Y3. How many Y9 does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Z8's Y9 = 15. Z8's YYY = 15.\nDefine each Z0's Y3 as u. So u = Y8 - Z8's Y9 = 13 - 15 = 21.\nDefine each Z0's Y1 as S. So S = 2 * u = 2 * 21 = 19.\nDefine each Z7's Y1 as A. So A = S = 19.\nDefine each Z7's Y3 as i. So i = 16 * u - A = 16 * 21 - 19 = 18.\nDefine each Z0's Y9 as Y. So Y = 21 * i = 21 * 18 = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 159, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y9 equals 19. How many Y9 does each Z3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Z3's Y9 = 19. So 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 160, "question": "The number of each X1's W3 equals 4. The number of each Y6's X3 equals 0 more than each X1's W3. How many X3 does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["X1's W3 = 4. Y6's X3 = 0 * X1's W3 = 0 * 4 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 161, "question": "The number of each Y3's X7 equals 14. The number of each X9's W2 equals 6 times each Y3's XXX. How many W2 does each X9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Y3's X7 = 14. Y3's XXX = 14. Y3's XXX = 14. Y3's XXX = 14. Y3's XXX = 14. Y3's XXX = 14. Y3's XXX = 14. Y3's XXX = 14. Y3's XXX = 14. Y3's XXX = 14. Y3's XXX = 14. Y3's XXX = 14. Y3's XXX = 14. Y3's XXX = 14. Y3's XXX = 14. Y3's XXX = 14. Y3's XXX = 14. Y3's XXX = 14. Y3's XXX = 14. Y3's XXX = 14. Y3's XXX = 14. Y3's XXX = 14. Y3's XXX = 14. Y3's XXX = 14. Y3's XXX = 14. Y3's X7 as u. So u = 14.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as S. So S = u = 14.\nDefine each X9's W2 as A. So A = 6 * S = 6 * 14 = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 162, "question": "The number of each Y4's X3 equals 5. The number of each Y0's X0 equals 18 times each Y4's X4. The number of each Y4's X4 equals 7 more than each Y4's X3. The number of each Y0's X3 equals 16 more than each Y0's X0. How many X3 does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Y4's X3 as u. So u = 5.\nDefine each Y4's X4 as S. So S = 7 * u = 7 * 5 = 12.\nDefine each Y0's X0 as A. So A = 18 * S = 18 * 12 = 9.\nDefine each Y0's X3 as i. So i = 16 * A = 16 * 9 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 163, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y3 equals 8. How many Y3 does each Z3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["Z3's Y3 as u. So u = 8.\nThus, the answer is 8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 164, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y4 equals 20. The number of each Y7's X2 equals 9 more than each Z9's Y7. The number of each Z1's Y4 equals each Z9's XXX. The number of each Z9's Y7 equals 9 times each Z0's Y4. The number of each Z7's Y7 equals 8 times each Z1's Y4. How many XXX does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Z0's Y4 = 20. Z9's Y7 as u. So u = 9 * Z0's Y4 = 9 * 20 = 19.\nDefine each Y7's X2 as S. So S = 9 * u = 9 * 19 = 10.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as A. So A = S = 10.\nDefine each Z9's XXX as i. So i = u * A = 19 * 10 = 6.\nDefine each Z1's Y4 as Y. So Y = i = 6.\nDefine each Z7's Y7 as F. So F = 8 * Y = 8 * 6 = 2.\nDefine each Z7's XXX as r. So r = F * A = 2 * 10 = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 165, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y3 equals the difference of each Z1's YYY and each Z1's Y3. The number of each Z1's Y3 equals 20. The number of each Z1's Y4 equals 8 more than each Z1's Y3. How many Y3 does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Z1's Y3 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each Z1's Y4 as S. So S = 8 * u = 8 * 20 = 22.\nDefine each Z1's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 22 + 20 = 19.\nDefine each Z0's Y3 as i. So i = A - u = 19 - 20 = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 166, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y9 equals 20 times each Z8's Y1. The number of each Z8's Y3 equals 20 times each Z5's Y3. The number of each Z9's Y6 equals 15. The number of each Z9's Y9 equals 20 more than each Z7's Y3. The number of each Z7's Y3 equals 4. The number of each Z9's Y3 equals 7. The number of each Z8's Y6 equals 12 more than each Z8's Y9. The number of each Z5's Y3 equals 12 times each Z8's Y1. The number of each Z8's Y1 equals 21 more than each Z9's YYY. How many YYY does each Z8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Z9's Y3 as u. So u = 7.\nDefine each Z7's Y3 as S. So S = 4.\nDefine each Z9's Y9 as A. So A = 20 * S = 20 * 4 = 11.\nDefine each Z9's Y6 as i. So i = 15.\nDefine each Z9's YYY as Y. So Y = u + A + i = 7 + 11 + 15 = 10.\nDefine each Z8's Y1 as F. So F = 21 * Y = 21 * 10 = 3.\nDefine each Z5's Y3 as r. So r = 12 * F = 12 * 3 = 13.\nDefine each Z8's Y3 as l. So l = 20 * r = 20 * 13 = 7.\nDefine each Z8's Y9 as V. So V = 20 * F = 20 * 3 = 14.\nDefine each Z8's Y6 as q. So q = 12 * V = 12 * 14 = 7.\nDefine each Z8's YYY as z. So z = q + l + V + F = 7 + 7 + 14 + 3 = 8.\nThus, the answer is 8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 167, "question": "The number of each Z2's Y3 equals 1. How many YYY does each Z2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Z2's Y3 = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's YYY = 1. Z2's"], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 168, "question": "The number of each X2's W8 equals 11 times each Y1's X7. The number of each Y1's X0 equals 12 times each X2's W8. The number of each X7's W1 equals 8. The number of each X7's W5 equals each Y1's XXX. The number of each X0's W5 equals the sum of each X7's WWW and each Z7's Y1. The number of each Y1's X7 equals 3 times each Z7's Y1. The number of each Z7's Y1 equals 15. How many WWW does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["Z7's Y1 as u. So u = 15.\nDefine each Y1's X7 as S. So S = 3 * u = 3 * 15 = 22.\nDefine each X2's W8 as A. So A = 11 * S = 11 * 22 = 12.\nDefine each Y1's X0 as i. So i = 12 * A = 12 * 12 = 6.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as Y. So Y = S + i = 22 + 6 = 5.\nDefine each X7's W5 as F. So F = Y = 5.\nDefine each X7's W1 as r. So r = 8.\nDefine each X7's WWW as l. So l = r + F = 8 + 5 = 13.\nDefine each X0's W5 as V. So V = l + u = 13 + 15 = 5.\nDefine each X0's WWW as q. So q = V = 5.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as z. So z = S * l + i * q = 22 * 13 + 6 * 5 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 169, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y1 equals 4. The number of each Z9's Y0 equals each Z8's Y1. The number of each Z8's Y1 equals 12 more than each Z9's Y1. How many Y0 does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Z9's Y1 as u. So u = 4.\nDefine each Z8's Y1 as S. So S = 12 * u = 12 * 4 = 2.\nDefine each Z9's Y0 as A. So A = S = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 170, "question": "The number of each X6's W5 equals 15. The number of each X9's W5 equals 19 times each Y3's X9. The number of each Y5's X9 equals 0 times each Y8's X2. The number of each Z7's Y3 equals 1 more than each Z9's WWW. The number of each X8's W5 equals each Y8's X2. The number of each Z9's Y5 equals 14 more than each X8's W5. The number of each Y8's X2 equals 18 times each X6's W5. The number of each Y3's X9 equals 5 more than each Z9's YYY. How many Y3 does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["X6's W5 = 15.\nDefine each Y8's X2 as u. So u = 18 * X6's W5 = 18 * 15 = 17.\nDefine each X8's W5 as S. So S = u = 17.\nDefine each Z9's Y5 as A. So A = 14 * S = 14 * 17 = 8.\nDefine each Z9's YYY as i. So i = A = 8.\nDefine each Y3's X9 as Y. So Y = 5 * i = 5 * 8 = 17.\nDefine each X9's W5 as F. So F = 19 * Y = 19 * 17 = 1.\nDefine each X9's WWW as r. So r = F = 1.\nDefine each Y5's X9 as l. So l = 0 * u = 0 * 17 = 0.\nDefine each Y5's WWW as V. So V = l * r = 0 * 1 = 0.\nDefine each Z9's WWW as q. So q = A * V = 8 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z7's Y3 as z. So z = 1 * q = 1 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 171, "question": "The number of each X2's W6 equals 22. How many W6 does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["X2's W6 = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 172, "question": "The number of each X5's W6 equals 9 times the sum of each X5's W0, each X4's W0 and each X4's W2. The number of each X0's W6 equals the sum of each X5's W0, each X5's W6, each X5's WWW and each X4's W2. The number of each X5's W0 equals 7 more than the sum of each X4's W0 and each X4's W2. The number of each X4's W0 equals 3 more than each X4's W2. The number of each X4's W2 equals 21. The number of each X4's W6 equals 19 more than each X0's W6. The number of each X5's W2 equals the sum of each X4's W2 and each X5's W6. The number of each X0's W0 equals each X4's W6. The number of each X0's W2 equals 10 more than the difference of each X0's W0 and each X5's W6. How many W2 does each X0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["10 + X4's W2 + u = 10 + 21 + 3 = 11.\nDefine each X4's W0 as S. So S = 3 * u = 3 * 11 = 10.\nDefine each X5's W0 as A. So A = 7 * S + u = 7 * 10 + 11 = 18.\nDefine each X5's W6 as i. So i = 9 * (A + S + u) = 9 * (18 + 10 + 11) = 19.\nDefine each X5's W2 as Y. So Y = u + i = 11 + 19 = 7.\nDefine each X5's WWW as F. So F = Y + A + i = 7 + 18 + 19 = 21.\nDefine each X0's W6 as r. So r = (A + i + F + u) = (18 + 19 + 21 + 11) = 0.\nDefine each X4's W6 as l. So l = 19 * r = 19 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X0's W0 as V. So V = l = 0.\nDefine each X0's W2 as q. So q = 10 * V - i = 10 * 0 - 19 = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 173, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y1 equals 12. The number of each Z1's Y3 equals 20 times the sum of each Z9's Y1 and each Z9's Y2. The number of each Z9's Y2 equals 6 more than each Z9's Y1. The number of each Z0's Y1 equals each Z1's Y3. How many Y1 does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Z9's Y1 as u. So u = 12.\nDefine each Z9's Y2 as S. So S = 6 * u = 6 * 12 = 3.\nDefine each Z1's Y3 as A. So A = 20 * u + S = 20 * 12 + 3 = 11.\nDefine each Z0's Y1 as i. So i = A = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 174, "question": "The number of each X9's W5 equals 11 times each X9's W1. The number of each X9's W1 equals 5. How many WWW does each X9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["X9's W1 as u. So u = 5.\nDefine each X9's W5 as S. So S = 11 * u = 11 * 5 = 9.\nDefine each X9's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 9 + 5 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 175, "question": "The number of each X2's W3 equals 3 times each X0's WWW. The number of each X0's W3 equals 12. How many W3 does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["X0's W3 as u. So u = 12.\nDefine each X0's WWW as S. So S = u = 12.\nDefine each X2's W3 as A. So A = 3 * S = 3 * 12 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 176, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y3 equals 13 times each Y3's XXX. The number of each Y3's X6 equals 15. The number of each Y3's X8 equals each Y3's X6. How many Y3 does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["Y3's X6 as u. So u = 15.\nDefine each Y3's X8 as S. So S = u = 15.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 15 + 15 = 7.\nDefine each Z0's Y3 as i. So i = 13 * A = 13 * 7 = 22.\nDefine each X3's WWW as Y. So Y = u = 15.\nDefine each X3's WWW as F. So F = Y = 15.\nDefine each X8's WWW as r. So r = Y + F = 15 + 15 = 7.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as l. So l = S * r + u * Y = 15 * 7 + 15 * 15 = 19.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as V. So V = i = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 177, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y2 equals 2 times each Z0's Y3. The number of each Z6's Y3 equals 18 times each Z5's Y3. The number of each Z0's Y5 equals each Z0's Y2. The number of each Z5's Y5 equals 20 times the sum of each Z0's Y3 and each Z5's Y2. The number of each Z0's Y2 equals the sum of each Z6's YYY, each Z0's Y3 and each Z5's YYY. The number of each Z6's Y5 equals the sum of each Z5's YYY, each Z5's Y3 and each Z6's Y3. The number of each Z6's Y2 equals the sum of each Z5's Y2, each Z5's Y5 and each Z5's YYY. The number of each Z0's Y3 equals 17. The number of each Z5's Y3 equals 5 more than the sum of each Z5's Y2 and each Z0's Y3. How many Y5 does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["17. So 17.\nDefine each Z0's Y3 as u. So u = 17.\nDefine each Z5's Y2 as S. So S = 2 * u = 2 * 17 = 11.\nDefine each Z5's Y3 as A. So A = 5 * S + u = 5 * 11 + 17 = 1.\nDefine each Z5's Y5 as i. So i = 20 * u + S = 20 * 17 + 11 = 19.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as Y. So Y = S + A + i = 11 + 1 + 19 = 8.\nDefine each Z6's Y3 as F. So F = 18 + A = 18 + 1 = 19.\nDefine each Z6's Y5 as r. So r = (Y + A + F) = (8 + 1 + 19) = 5.\nDefine each Z6's Y2 as l. So l = (S + i + Y) = (11 + 19 + 8) = 15.\nDefine each Z6's YYY as V. So V = l + r + F = 15 + 5 + 19 = 16.\nDefine each Z0's Y2 as q. So q = (V + u + Y) = (16 + 17 + 8) = 18.\nDefine each Z0's Y5 as z. So z = q = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 178, "question": "The number of each Y2's X3 equals 20 times each Y5's XXX. The number of each Z9's Y5 equals 3 times each Y3's X3. The number of each Y0's X0 equals 12 times each Y3's X0. The number of each Y5's X0 equals 10. The number of each Y3's X3 equals 12 times each Y2's X3. The number of each Y3's X0 equals the sum of each Z0's Y5 and each Y3's X3. The number of each Y3's X1 equals 21 times the difference of each Y0's XXX and each Z9's Y5. The number of each Z9's Y3 equals 11 times the difference of each Z9's Y5 and each Y5's X0. The number of each Z0's Y5 equals the difference of each Z9's Y3 and each Z9's YYY. How many X1 does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["21."], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 179, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y3 equals 13. The number of each X8's W7 equals 19. The number of each Y3's X3 equals the difference of each X3's WWW and each X8's W7. The number of each Z7's Y2 equals the difference of each X2's W0 and each X3's WWW. The number of each Z8's Y2 equals 16 more than each Z3's Y3. The number of each Y2's X3 equals 14 times the difference of each Z3's WWW and each X3's W7. The number of each X3's W7 equals 8 times each X8's W7. The number of each X2's W0 equals 16 times each Z8's WWW. The number of each Y8's X8 equals 14 times each Z7's Y2. How many X8 does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["14. Z3's Y3 = 13. Z8's Y2 as u. So u = 16 * Z3's Y3 = 16 * 13 = 1.\nDefine each X8's W7 as S. So S = 19.\nDefine each X3's W7 as A. So A = 8 * S = 8 * 19 = 14.\nDefine each X3's WWW as i. So i = A = 14.\nDefine each Y3's X3 as Y. So Y = i - S = 14 - 19 = 18.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as F. So F = Y * i = 18 * 14 = 22.\nDefine each Z3's WWW as r. So r = Z3's WWW as l. So l = r * F = 13 * 22 = 10.\nDefine each Y2's X3 as V. So V = 14 * l - A = 14 * 10 - 14 = 11.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as q. So q = V * i = 11 * 14 = 16.\nDefine each Z8's Y2 as z. So z = 16 * l = 16 * 10 = 22.\nDefine each Z8's WWW as A. So A = z * q = 22 * 16 = 7.\nDefine each X2's W0 as i. So i = 16 * A = 16 * 7 = 20.\nDefine each Z7's Y2 as Y. So Y = i - i = 20 - 20 = 0.\nDefine each Y8's X8 as F. So F = 14 * Y = 14 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 180, "question": "The number of each X4's W8 equals 15 times the difference of each X4's W3 and each X1's W6. The number of each X5's W3 equals 16 times the sum of each X5's W8, each X4's WWW and each X4's W3. The number of each X1's W6 equals 17 times each X4's W3. The number of each X5's W8 equals 13 times the difference of each X1's W6 and each X1's WWW. The number of each X7's W1 equals 18 times the sum of each X4's WWW, each X5's W8 and each X5's W3. The number of each X4's W3 equals 19. The number of each X7's W8 equals 19 more than each X5's WWW. How many WWW does each X7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 181, "question": "The number of each Z2's Y0 equals 5. The number of each X5's W0 equals 20 more than each Z2's YYY. How many W0 does each X5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["X5's W0 = 20 * Z2's Y0 = 20 * 5 = 8.\nDefine each Z2's Y0 as u. So u = 5.\nDefine each Z2's YYY as S. So S = u = 5.\nDefine each X5's W0 as A. So A = 20 * S = 20 * 5 = 8.\nDefine each X5's WWW as i. So i = A = 8.\nDefine each Y0's lollip as Y. So Y = 20.\nDefine each Y0's WWW as F. So F = Y * i = 20 * 8 = 22.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as r. So r = Y * F = 20 * 22 = 3.\nDefine each Z2's WWW as l. So l = u * F = 5 * 22 = 18.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as V. So V = r = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 182, "question": "The number of each Y9's X3 equals 0 times the difference of each Z2's Y4 and each Y0's X8. The number of each Z2's Y4 equals each Y0's X8. The number of each Y4's X0 equals 3 times each Y9's X3. The number of each Y0's X8 equals 1. The number of each X8's W5 equals 10 more than each Y4's X0. How many WWW does each X8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Y0's X8 = 1.\nDefine each Z2's Y4 as u. So u = Y0's X8 = 1.\nDefine each Y9's X3 as S. So S = 0 * u - Y0's X8 = 0 * 1 - 1 = 22.\nDefine each Y4's X0 as A. So A = 3 * S = 3 * 22 = 20.\nDefine each X8's W5 as i. So i = 10 * A = 10 * 20 = 16.\nDefine each X8's WWW as Y. So Y = i = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 183, "question": "The number of each X8's W6 equals each X6's W1. The number of each X1's W6 equals each X8's W6. The number of each X6's W6 equals 3 more than each X6's W7. The number of each X6's W7 equals 18. The number of each X6's W1 equals 12 more than each X6's W6. How many W6 does each X1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["X6's W7 as u. So u = 18.\nDefine each X6's W6 as S. So S = 3 * u = 3 * 18 = 8.\nDefine each X6's W1 as A. So A = 12 * S = 12 * 8 = 4.\nDefine each X8's W6 as i. So i = A = 4.\nDefine each X1's W6 as Y. So Y = i = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 184, "question": "The number of each Y8's X5 equals each Y8's X2. The number of each Y8's X2 equals 8. How many XXX does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Y8's X2 as u. So u = 8.\nDefine each Y8's X5 as S. So S = u = 8.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as A. So A = S + u + Y = 8 + 8 + 8 = 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 185, "question": "The number of each Y8's X8 equals 19 more than each Y9's XXX. The number of each Y9's X5 equals 13. The number of each Y9's X8 equals each Y5's X8. The number of each Y8's X1 equals 6 more than the difference of each Y9's XXX and each Y8's X8. The number of each Y5's X8 equals 4. How many X1 does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Y5's X8 = 4. Y9's X8 as u. So u = Y5's X8 = 4.\nDefine each Y9's X5 as S. So S = 13.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 13 + 4 = 17.\nDefine each Y8's X8 as i. So i = 19 * A = 19 * 17 = 1.\nDefine each Y8's X1 as Y. So Y = 6 * A - i = 6 * 17 - 1 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 186, "question": "The number of each X7's W8 equals 0. The number of each Y7's X7 equals 11 times each Z0's WWW. The number of each Z0's Y6 equals 5. The number of each Y6's X7 equals each X7's WWW. How many X7 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["X7's W8 = 0. X7's WWW = 0. X7's WWW = 0. X7's WWW = 0. X7's WWW = 0. X7's WWW = 0. X7's WWW = 0. X7's WWW = 0. X7's WWW = 0. X7's WWW = 0. X7's W8 = 0. X7's WWW as u. So u = u = 0.\nDefine each Y6's X7 as S. So S = u = 0.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as A. So A = S * u = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z0's Y6 as i. So i = 5.\nDefine each Z0's WWW as Y. So Y = i * A = 5 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y7's X7 as F. So F = 11 * Y = 11 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 187, "question": "The number of each Z4's Y0 equals 14 times each X1's W3. The number of each Y6's X1 equals 13. The number of each X4's W3 equals 15 times each Y6's XXX. The number of each Y6's X4 equals 20 more than the difference of each Y0's XXX and each Y0's X1. The number of each X1's W3 equals each Y0's X1. The number of each Y0's X1 equals 3. The number of each X4's W8 equals 2 times the difference of each Y6's XXX and each Z4's XXX. The number of each Z4's Y6 equals each X4's W3. How many W8 does each X4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["Y0's X1 as u. So u = 3.\nDefine each X1's W3 as S. So S = u = 3.\nDefine each Z4's Y0 as A. So A = 14 * S = 14 * 3 = 19.\nDefine each Y6's X1 as i. So i = 13.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as Y. So Y = u = 3.\nDefine each Y6's X4 as F. So F = 20 * Y - u = 20 * 3 - 3 = 11.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as r. So r = F + i = 11 + 13 = 1.\nDefine each X4's W3 as l. So l = 15 * r = 15 * 1 = 15.\nDefine each Z4's Y6 as V. So V = l = 15.\nDefine each Z4's XXX as q. So q = A * Y + V * r = 19 * 3 + 15 * 1 = 19.\nDefine each X4's W8 as z. So z = 2 * r - q = 2 * 1 - 19 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 188, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y5 equals 10 times each Z0's Y0. The number of each Y0's X8 equals each Y0's X4. The number of each Z5's Y5 equals the sum of each Y0's X4 and each Z0's YYY. The number of each Z5's Y0 equals 8 times the sum of each Y0's XXX and each Z5's Y2. The number of each Z5's Y2 equals 22 times each Z0's YYY. The number of each Z0's Y2 equals the sum of each Y0's XXX and each Y0's X8. The number of each Y0's X4 equals 4. The number of each Z0's Y0 equals each Y0's X8. How many YYY does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["Y0's X4 as u. So u = 4.\nDefine each Y0's X8 as S. So S = u = 4.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 4 + 4 = 8.\nDefine each Z0's Y2 as i. So i = A + S = 8 + 4 = 12.\nDefine each Z0's Y0 as Y. So Y = S = 4.\nDefine each Z0's Y5 as F. So F = 10 * Y = 10 * 4 = 17.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as r. So r = Y + F + i = 4 + 17 + 12 = 10.\nDefine each Z5's Y2 as l. So l = 22 * r = 22 * 10 = 13.\nDefine each Z5's Y5 as V. So V = u + r = 4 + 10 = 14.\nDefine each Z5's Y0 as q. So q = 8 * A + l = 8 * 8 + 13 = 19.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as z. So z = q + V + l = 19 + 14 + 13 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 189, "question": "The number of each Y6's X1 equals 20 more than each X1's WWW. The number of each X1's W7 equals 12. How many WWW does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["X1's W7 as u. So u = 12.\nDefine each X1's WWW as S. So S = u = 12.\nDefine each Y6's X1 as A. So A = 20 * S = 20 * 12 = 10.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as i. So i = A * S = 10 * 12 = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 190, "question": "The number of each Y6's X3 equals 20 more than each X4's W7. The number of each X4's W7 equals each X6's WWW. The number of each X6's W4 equals 1. The number of each X3's W4 equals each X4's W7. The number of each Y6's X4 equals 7. The number of each X3's W8 equals 7 more than the sum of each X6's W4 and each X3's W4. How many WWW does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Y6's X4 as u. So u = 7.\nDefine each X6's W4 as S. So S = 1.\nDefine each X6's WWW as A. So A = S = 1.\nDefine each X4's W7 as i. So i = A = 1.\nDefine each X3's W4 as Y. So Y = i = 1.\nDefine each X3's W8 as F. So F = 7 * S + Y = 7 * 1 + 1 = 8.\nDefine each X3's WWW as r. So r = Y + F = 1 + 8 = 9.\nDefine each Y6's X3 as l. So l = 20 * i = 20 * 1 = 20.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as V. So V = l * r + u * A = 20 * 9 + 7 * 1 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 191, "question": "The number of each Y9's X6 equals each X6's W0. The number of each Z9's Y9 equals 22. The number of each X0's W0 equals the sum of each Y6's X3, each Y0's X0 and each Z3's Y7. The number of each Y0's X0 equals 6 more than each Z3's Y7. The number of each Y6's X3 equals 10 times each Y0's X0. The number of each Z3's Y7 equals 7 more than each Y7's X3. The number of each Y6's X0 equals 0 more than each X3's W1. The number of each Y7's X3 equals 1 more than the difference of each X6's W0 and each Y9's X6. The number of each X6's W0 equals each Y7's X8. The number of each Y7's X8 equals 0 more than each Z9's Y9. The number of each X3's W1 equals 3 more than each Y7's X8. How many WWW does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Z9's Y9 = 22. Y7's X8 = 0 * Z9's Y9 = 0 * 22 = 0.\nDefine each X6's W0 as u. So u = Y7's X8 = 0.\nDefine each Y9's X6 as S. So S = u = 0.\nDefine each Y7's X3 as A. So A = 1 * u - S = 1 * 0 - 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z3's Y7 as i. So i = 7 * A = 7 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y0's X0 as Y. So Y = 6 * i = 6 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y6's X3 as F. So F = 10 * Y = 10 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X3's W1 as r. So r = 3 * Y = 3 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y6's X0 as l. So l = 0 * r = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X0's W0 as V. So V = (F + Y + i) = (0 + 0 + 0) = 0.\nDefine each X0's WWW as q. So q = V = 0.\nDefine each Z9's Y9 as z. So z = 22.\nDefine each Y7's X8 as A. So A = 0 + Z9's Y9 = 0 + 22 = 22.\nDefine each X6's W0 as i. So i = A = 22.\nDefine each Y9's WWW as Y. So Y = S * q = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as F. So F = l * q + F * Y = 0 * 0 + 0 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 192, "question": "The number of each Y3's X2 equals the difference of each Y7's X8 and each X5's W3. The number of each X8's W2 equals each Y3's X2. The number of each Y7's X8 equals each X5's W3. The number of each X5's W3 equals 3. How many W2 does each X8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["X5's W3 = 3.\nDefine each Y7's X8 as u. So u = X5's W3 = 3.\nDefine each Y3's X2 as S. So S = u - X5's W3 = 3 - 3 = 0.\nDefine each X8's W2 as A. So A = S = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 193, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y0 equals the sum of each Z3's XXX, each Y3's XXX and each Z3's YYY. The number of each Y0's X9 equals 5. The number of each Y3's X2 equals 15 more than the sum of each Z3's YYY, each Y0's XXX and each Z6's Y3. The number of each Z6's Y3 equals the sum of each Y0's XXX, each Y0's X9 and each Z3's YYY. The number of each Z3's Y3 equals 4 more than the sum of each Y0's XXX and each Y0's X9. How many Y0 does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Y0's X9 as u. So u = 5.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as S. So S = u = 5.\nDefine each Z3's Y3 as A. So A = 4 * S + u = 4 * 5 + 5 = 7.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as i. So i = A = 7.\nDefine each Z6's Y3 as Y. So Y = (S + u + i) = (5 + 5 + 7) = 17.\nDefine each Y3's X2 as F. So F = 15 + (i + S + Y) = 15 + (7 + 5 + 17) = 21.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as r. So r = F = 21.\nDefine each Z3's XXX as l. So l = A * r = 7 * 21 = 9.\nDefine each Z6's Y0 as V. So V = (l + r + i) = (9 + 21 + 7) = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 194, "question": "The number of each Y8's X6 equals the sum of each X5's WWW, each X6's WWW and each X5's W4. The number of each X5's W4 equals the difference of each X6's W2 and each X6's WWW. The number of each X6's W4 equals 17 more than each Y2's X6. The number of each Z2's Y8 equals 6. The number of each X6's W2 equals the difference of each Y2's X6 and each Y8's X5. The number of each Y2's X6 equals each Y8's X5. The number of each X5's W2 equals 15 times each X5's W4. The number of each Y8's X5 equals each Z2's Y8. How many X6 does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Z2's Y8 = 6. Y8's X5 = Z2's Y8 = 6.\nDefine each Y2's X6 as u. So u = Y8's X5 = 6.\nDefine each X6's W4 as S. So S = 17 * u = 17 * 6 = 10.\nDefine each X6's W2 as A. So A = u - Y8's X5 = 6 - 6 = 0.\nDefine each X6's WWW as i. So i = S + A = 10 + 0 = 10.\nDefine each X5's W4 as Y. So Y = A - i = 0 - 10 = 13.\nDefine each X5's W2 as F. So F = 15 * Y = 15 * 13 = 11.\nDefine each X5's WWW as r. So r = Y + F = 13 + 11 = 1.\nDefine each Y8's X6 as l. So l = (r + i + Y) = (1 + 10 + 13) = 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 195, "question": "The number of each X6's W6 equals 10. The number of each Y3's X9 equals 14 more than each X6's W6. How many X9 does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["X6's W6 = 10. Y3's X9 = 14 * X6's W6 = 14 * 10 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 196, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y4 equals 15 times the difference of each Z7's YYY and each Z7's Y7. The number of each Z7's Y4 equals 4 times each Y7's X8. The number of each Y7's X8 equals 1. The number of each Y4's X7 equals 2 times the sum of each Z6's Y4, each Z7's Y4 and each Y7's X8. The number of each Z7's Y7 equals 20 more than the difference of each Y7's X8 and each Z7's Y4. The number of each Y4's X8 equals 22 times each Z6's Y4. How many XXX does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Y7's X8 as u. So u = 1.\nDefine each Z7's Y4 as S. So S = 4 * u = 4 * 1 = 4.\nDefine each Z7's Y7 as A. So A = 20 * u - S = 20 * 1 - 4 = 16.\nDefine each Z7's YYY as i. So i = S + A = 4 + 16 = 20.\nDefine each Z6's Y4 as Y. So Y = 15 * i - A = 15 * 20 - 16 = 17.\nDefine each Y4's X8 as F. So F = 22 * Y = 22 * 17 = 6.\nDefine each Y4's X7 as r. So r = 2 * (Y + S + u) = 2 * (17 + 4 + 1) = 19.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as l. So l = r + F = 19 + 6 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 197, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y2 equals 22 more than each Z8's Y1. The number of each Y2's X7 equals 3 more than each Z1's YYY. The number of each Z8's Y1 equals 4. The number of each Y2's X3 equals 9. The number of each Z1's Y1 equals 11 more than the difference of each Z8's Y1 and each Z8's YYY. The number of each Z1's Y2 equals 2 more than each Z1's Y1. How many XXX does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["Y2's X3 as u. So u = 9.\nDefine each Z8's Y1 as S. So S = 4.\nDefine each Z8's Y2 as A. So A = 22 * S = 22 * 4 = 19.\nDefine each Z8's YYY as i. So i = S + A = 4 + 19 = 0.\nDefine each Z1's Y1 as Y. So Y = 11 * S - i = 11 * 4 - 0 = 21.\nDefine each Z1's Y2 as F. So F = 2 * Y = 2 * 21 = 19.\nDefine each Z1's YYY as r. So r = Y + F = 21 + 19 = 17.\nDefine each Y2's X7 as l. So l = 3 * r = 3 * 17 = 5.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as V. So V = l + u = 5 + 9 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 198, "question": "The number of each X3's W8 equals 14. The number of each X3's W1 equals the difference of each X3's W8 and each X9's W8. The number of each X9's W8 equals 5 times each X3's W8. The number of each Y2's X3 equals each X3's WWW. The number of each Y2's X9 equals 10 more than the sum of each X3's W1 and each Y2's X3. The number of each X2's W1 equals the difference of each Y2's WWW and each X9's WWW. How many WWW does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["X3's W8 as u. So u = 14.\nDefine each X9's W8 as S. So S = 5 * u = 5 * 14 = 1.\nDefine each X9's WWW as A. So A = S = 1.\nDefine each X3's W1 as i. So i = u - S = 14 - 1 = 13.\nDefine each X3's WWW as Y. So Y = u + i = 14 + 13 = 4.\nDefine each Y2's X3 as F. So F = Y = 4.\nDefine each Y2's X9 as r. So r = 10 * i + F = 10 * 13 + 4 = 18.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as l. So l = r * A + F * Y = 18 * 1 + 4 * 4 = 14.\nDefine each X2's W1 as V. So V = l - A = 14 - 1 = 13.\nDefine each X2's WWW as q. So q = V = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 199, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y0 equals each Y0's X6. The number of each Y0's X3 equals 10 times each Y1's XXX. The number of each Y8's X5 equals each Y1's XXX. The number of each Z6's Y1 equals 13 more than each Y1's X6. The number of each Y1's X5 equals 7 more than each Z6's Y1. The number of each Y0's X6 equals the difference of each Z6's Y1 and each Z6's XXX. The number of each Z0's Y8 equals the sum of each Y0's X6 and each Z8's Y0. The number of each Z8's Y1 equals each Y0's X6. The number of each Y8's X3 equals 18 more than each Z8's XXX. The number of each Y1's X6 equals 13. How many XXX does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Y1's X6 = 13. Z6's Y1 as u. So u = 13 + Y1's X6 = 13 + 13 = 3.\nDefine each Y1's X5 as S. So S = 7 * u = 7 * 3 = 21.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as A. So A = S + Y1's X6 = 21 + 13 = 11.\nDefine each Z6's XXX as i. So i = u * A = 3 * 11 = 10.\nDefine each Y0's X6 as Y. So Y = u - i = 3 - 10 = 16.\nDefine each Z8's Y1 as F. So F = Y = 16.\nDefine each Z8's Y0 as r. So r = Y = 16.\nDefine each Y8's X5 as l. So l = A = 11.\nDefine each Y8's X3 as V. So V = 18 * Z8's XXX = 18 * 16 = 12.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as q. So q = V + l = 12 + 11 = 0.\nDefine each Z0's Y8 as z. So z = Y + r = 16 + 16 = 9.\nDefine each Z0's XXX as A. So A = z * q = 9 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 200, "question": "The number of each Y6's X3 equals 4 times each Y0's X1. The number of each Y0's X1 equals the sum of each Y5's X1, each Y5's X3 and each Y0's X3. The number of each Y5's X1 equals the difference of each Y0's X3 and each Y5's X3. The number of each Y0's X3 equals each Y5's X3. The number of each Y5's X3 equals 16. How many X3 does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["Y5's X3 = 16. Y0's X3 = 16. Y5's X1 = Y0's X3 - Y5's X3 = 11. Y0's X1 = (Y5's X1 + Y5's X3 + Y0's X3) = 18. Y6's X3 = 4 * Y0's X1 = 4 * 18 = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 201, "question": "The number of each Y2's X8 equals 20 more than the sum of each Y6's X8, each Y6's X0 and each Y2's X4. The number of each Y8's X8 equals each Y2's XXX. The number of each Y2's X4 equals 1 times the difference of each Y6's X0 and each Y6's X8. The number of each Y6's X8 equals each Y6's X0. The number of each Y5's X3 equals 18 times each Y8's XXX. The number of each Y6's X0 equals 5. The number of each Y8's X3 equals each Y2's XXX. The number of each Y5's X8 equals 6 times each Y6's X3. The number of each Y5's X4 equals the sum of each Y8's X8, each Y2's X8 and each Y8's X3. The number of each Y6's X3 equals 14. The number of each Y5's X0 equals 17 times the sum of each Y6's X8 and each Y8's XXX. How many XXX does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["Y6's X0 as u. So u = 5.\nDefine each Y6's X8 as S. So S = u = 5.\nDefine each Y2's X4 as A. So A = 1 * u - S = 1 * 5 - 5 = 0.\nDefine each Y2's X8 as i. So i = 20 * (S + u + A) = 20 * (5 + 5 + 0) = 19.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as Y. So Y = i + A = 19 + 0 = 19.\nDefine each Y8's X8 as F. So F = Y = 19.\nDefine each Y6's X3 as r. So r = 14.\nDefine each Y8's X3 as l. So l = Y = 19.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as V. So V = l + F = 19 + 19 = 15.\nDefine each Y5's X0 as q. So q = 17 * S + V = 17 * 5 + 15 = 16.\nDefine each Y5's X4 as z. So z = (F + i + l) = (19 + 19 + 19) = 11.\nDefine each Y5's X3 as A. So A = 18 + V = 18 + 15 = 10.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as i. So i = A + q + Z = 10 + 16 + 11 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 202, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y0 equals 16 more than the difference of each Y8's X3 and each X2's WWW. The number of each X3's W1 equals 14 more than each Z6's WWW. The number of each Z6's Y0 equals 17. The number of each X2's W1 equals 11 times each Z6's Y0. The number of each Y8's X3 equals 5 times the sum of each Y0's WWW and each X3's WWW. The number of each Y0's X2 equals 7 more than each Z6's Y0. How many WWW does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Z6's Y0 = 17. Y0's X2 as u. So u = 7 * Z6's Y0 = 7 * 17 = 4.\nDefine each Z6's WWW as S. So S = Z6's Y0 * Y0's X2 = 17 * 4 = 22.\nDefine each X3's W1 as A. So A = 14 * S = 14 * 22 = 9.\nDefine each X3's WWW as i. So i = A = 9.\nDefine each Y0's WWW as Y. So Y = u * i = 4 * 9 = 13.\nDefine each Y8's X3 as F. So F = 5 * Y + i = 5 * 13 + 9 = 15.\nDefine each X2's W1 as r. So r = 11 * Z6's Y0 = 11 * 17 = 3.\nDefine each X2's WWW as l. So l = r = 3.\nDefine each Z7's Y0 as V. So V = 16 + F - l = 16 + 15 - 3 = 5.\nDefine each Z7's WWW as q. So q = V * Y = 5 * 13 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 203, "question": "The number of each Y0's X0 equals 9 more than the sum of each Y3's XXX, each Y3's X3 and each Z7's XXX. The number of each Y3's X3 equals 0 times the difference of each Z8's Y0 and each Y3's X0. The number of each Z7's Y3 equals 10 more than the sum of each Y3's X3, each Z8's Y0 and each Y3's X0. The number of each Y3's X0 equals 16 times each Z8's Y0. The number of each Z8's Y0 equals 1. How many XXX does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Z8's Y0 = 1. Y3's X0 = 16 * Z8's Y0 = 16 * 1 = 16.\nDefine each Y3's X3 as u. So u = 0 * Z8's Y0 - u = 0 * 1 - 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z7's Y3 as S. So S = 10 * (u + Z8's Y0 + u) = 10 * (0 + 1 + 0) = 10.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as A. So A = u = 0.\nDefine each Z7's XXX as i. So i = S * A = 10 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y0's X0 as Y. So Y = 9 * (A + u + i) = 9 * (0 + 0 + 0) = 0.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as F. So F = Y = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 204, "question": "The number of each X5's W7 equals 4. The number of each Y9's X5 equals each Y8's X5. The number of each Y9's X1 equals 20 times each Y9's X5. The number of each Y8's X5 equals 13 more than each X5's W7. How many XXX does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["X5's W7 = 4.\nDefine each Y8's X5 as u. So u = 13 * X5's W7 = 13 * 4 = 6.\nDefine each Y9's X5 as S. So S = u = 6.\nDefine each Y9's X1 as A. So A = 20 * S = 20 * 6 = 5.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as i. So i = S + A = 6 + 5 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 205, "question": "The number of each Y4's X1 equals the sum of each Z6's Y9, each Y9's XXX and each Z0's Y7. The number of each Z8's Y7 equals 7. The number of each Y9's X1 equals each Z8's YYY. The number of each Z6's Y9 equals 9 more than each Y9's XXX. The number of each Z0's Y7 equals 17 times each Z6's XXX. How many X1 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["Z8's Y7 = 7. Z8's YYY = 7. Z6's Y9's XXX as u. So u = Z8's Y7 * Y7 = 7 * 7 = 3.\nDefine each Z0's Y7 as S. So S = 17 * u = 17 * 3 = 5.\nDefine each Y9's X1 as A. So A = u = 3.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as i. So i = A = 3.\nDefine each Z6's Y9 as Y. So Y = 9 * i = 9 * 3 = 4.\nDefine each Z6's XXX as F. So F = Y * i = 4 * 3 = 12.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as r. So r = S = 5.\nDefine each Y7's X1 as l. So l = (Y + i + S) = (4 + 3 + 5) = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 206, "question": "The number of each X0's W8 equals 10 times the sum of each X3's W6 and each X3's WWW. The number of each X3's W6 equals each X3's W8. The number of each Y8's X0 equals 20. The number of each X3's W8 equals 0. How many WWW does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["X3's W8 as u. So u = 0.\nDefine each X3's W6 as S. So S = u = 0.\nDefine each X3's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each X0's W8 as i. So i = 10 * S + A = 10 * 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each X0's WWW as Y. So Y = i = 0.\nDefine each Y8's X0 as F. So F = 20.\nDefine each Y8's WWW as r. So r = F * Y = 20 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 207, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y4 equals 4 more than each Z5's YYY. The number of each Z5's Y4 equals 10 more than each Z5's Y0. The number of each Z8's Y0 equals each Z5's YYY. The number of each Z9's Y0 equals the sum of each Z8's Y0 and each Z8's YYY. The number of each Z5's Y0 equals 5. The number of each Z8's Y4 equals each Z5's YYY. How many YYY does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Z5's Y0 as u. So u = 5.\nDefine each Z5's Y4 as S. So S = 10 * u = 10 * 5 = 4.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 4 + 5 = 9.\nDefine each Z8's Y4 as i. So i = A = 9.\nDefine each Z8's Y0 as Y. So Y = A = 9.\nDefine each Z8's YYY as F. So F = Y + i = 9 + 9 = 18.\nDefine each Z9's Y0 as r. So r = Y + F = 9 + 18 = 4.\nDefine each Z9's Y4 as l. So l = 4 * A = 4 * 9 = 13.\nDefine each Z9's YYY as V. So V = l + r = 13 + 4 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 208, "question": "The number of each X1's W0 equals the difference of each Y4's X1 and each Y4's XXX. The number of each Y4's X1 equals 0. The number of each X1's W9 equals 15 more than each Y4's X1. The number of each Y4's X5 equals 8 times each Y4's X1. How many WWW does each X1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["X1's W9 as u. So u = 15 * Y4's X1 = 15 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y4's X1 as S. So S = 0.\nDefine each Y4's X5 as A. So A = 8 * S = 8 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as i. So i = S + A = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each X1's W0 as Y. So Y = S - i = 0 - 0 = 0.\nDefine each X1's WWW as F. So F = Y + u = 0 + 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 209, "question": "The number of each Y6's X6 equals 6. How many X6 does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Y6's X6 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 210, "question": "The number of each Y7's X8 equals 3 times each Y7's X3. The number of each Y7's X3 equals 14. The number of each Z6's Y7 equals 18 more than the difference of each Y7's X3 and each Y7's X8. The number of each Z1's Y7 equals the sum of each Z6's XXX, each Y7's X3 and each Z6's Y7. How many Y7 does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Y7's X3 as u. So u = 14.\nDefine each Y7's X8 as S. So S = 3 * u = 3 * 14 = 19.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 19 + 14 = 10.\nDefine each Z6's Y7 as i. So i = 18 * u - S = 18 * 14 - 19 = 19.\nDefine each Z6's XXX as Y. So Y = i * A = 19 * 10 = 6.\nDefine each Z1's Y7 as F. So F = (Y + u + i) = (6 + 14 + 19) = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 211, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y0 equals 17 more than each Z0's Y3. The number of each Z9's Y9 equals the sum of each Z9's Y0 and each Z0's Y3. The number of each Z9's Y3 equals 11. The number of each Z0's Y3 equals 9. How many YYY does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["Z0's Y3 as u. So u = 9.\nDefine each Z9's Y0 as S. So S = 17 * u = 17 * 9 = 15.\nDefine each Z9's Y9 as A. So A = S + u = 15 + 9 = 1.\nDefine each Z9's Y3 as i. So i = 11.\nDefine each Z9's YYY as Y. So Y = S + A + i = 15 + 1 + 11 = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 212, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y0 equals 8. The number of each Z9's Y7 equals 14 times each Z9's Y0. How many Y7 does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Z9's Y0 as u. So u = 8.\nDefine each Z9's Y7 as S. So S = 14 * u = 14 * 8 = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 213, "question": "The number of each Y3's X0 equals 14 times the sum of each Y9's XXX, each Y9's X6 and each Y9's X4. The number of each Y3's X6 equals 4 times each Y9's X4. The number of each Y7's X4 equals 0 more than the difference of each Y9's X6 and each Y3's XXX. The number of each Y9's X6 equals 12 more than each Y9's X4. The number of each Y9's X4 equals 10. How many XXX does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Y9's X4 as u. So u = 10.\nDefine each Y9's X6 as S. So S = 12 * u = 12 * 10 = 5.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 5 + 10 = 15.\nDefine each Y3's X0 as i. So i = 14 * (A + S + u) = 14 * (15 + 5 + 10) = 19.\nDefine each Y3's X6 as Y. So Y = 4 * u = 4 * 10 = 17.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as F. So F = Y + i = 17 + 19 = 13.\nDefine each Y7's X4 as r. So r = 0 * S - F = 0 * 5 - 13 = 10.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as l. So l = r = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 214, "question": "The number of each X3's W3 equals 20 more than each X3's W8. The number of each X2's W3 equals 19. The number of each X6's W4 equals 21 more than the sum of each X2's W3 and each X3's W3. The number of each X3's W8 equals 1 more than each X2's W3. How many W4 does each X6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["X2's W3 as u. So u = 19.\nDefine each X3's W8 as S. So S = 1 * u = 1 * 19 = 19.\nDefine each X3's W3 as A. So A = 20 * S = 20 * 19 = 12.\nDefine each X6's W4 as i. So i = 21 * u + A = 21 * 19 + 12 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 215, "question": "The number of each Z2's Y0 equals 12. The number of each Z1's Y1 equals 15 times the difference of each Z2's YYY and each Z2's Y0. How many YYY does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Z2's Y0 = 12. Z2's YYY as u. So u = Z2's YYY = 12.\nDefine each Z1's Y1 as S. So S = 15 * u - u = 15 * 12 - 12 = 8.\nDefine each Z1's YYY as A. So A = S = 8.\nThus, the answer is 8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 216, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y7 equals 4. The number of each Z4's Y8 equals each Z3's Y7. The number of each Z4's Y9 equals 11 more than the sum of each Z3's Y7 and each Z4's Y8. How many Y9 does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Z3's Y7 as u. So u = 4.\nDefine each Z4's Y8 as S. So S = u = 4.\nDefine each Z4's Y9 as A. So A = 11 * u + S = 11 * 4 + 4 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 217, "question": "The number of each X8's W5 equals 18. The number of each Y0's X6 equals each Z9's Y0. The number of each Y9's X6 equals the sum of each X8's W5 and each Y0's X8. The number of each Y0's X8 equals 8 times the sum of each Z9's Y0, each Z9's YYY and each Z9's Y9. The number of each Z9's Y9 equals 12 times each Y0's X6. The number of each Y9's X8 equals the sum of each Y0's X8 and each Z9's Y9. The number of each Z9's Y0 equals 11 more than each X8's W5. How many XXX does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["X8's W5 = 18.\nDefine each Z9's Y0 as u. So u = 11 * X8's W5 = 11 * 18 = 14.\nDefine each Z9's Y9 as S. So S = 12 * u = 12 * 14 = 7.\nDefine each Z9's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 7 + 14 = 21.\nDefine each Y0's X8 as i. So i = 8 * (u + A + S) = 8 * (14 + 21 + 7) = 11.\nDefine each Y9's X6 as Y. So Y = X8's W5 + i = 18 + 11 = 6.\nDefine each Y9's X8 as F. So F = i + S = 11 + 7 = 18.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as r. So r = Y + F = 6 + 18 = 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 218, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y6 equals 10 times each X5's W4. The number of each Y4's X4 equals 7 times each Z6's Y6. The number of each X5's W4 equals 2. The number of each Z5's Y4 equals 10 times the sum of each X5's W4 and each Y4's X4. How many Y4 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["X5's W4 = 2.\nDefine each Z6's Y6 as u. So u = 10 * X5's W4 = 10 * 2 = 20.\nDefine each Y4's X4 as S. So S = 7 * u = 7 * 20 = 2.\nDefine each Z5's Y4 as A. So A = 10 * X5's W4 + S = 10 * 2 + 2 = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 219, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y1 equals 4. The number of each Z5's Y1 equals 7 times each Z0's Y1. How many Y1 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Z0's Y1 as u. So u = 4.\nDefine each Z5's Y1 as S. So S = 7 * u = 7 * 4 = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 220, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y6 equals 4. How many Y6 does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["Z6's Y6 = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 221, "question": "The number of each X7's W3 equals each Y6's WWW. The number of each Y6's X2 equals each X1's WWW. The number of each Y6's X1 equals 6. The number of each X1's W1 equals 8 more than the difference of each Y3's X2 and each X2's W9. The number of each X1's W3 equals 19 more than the difference of each X2's W9 and each Y3's X2. The number of each Y3's X2 equals 22. The number of each X7's W9 equals 20 more than each X7's W3. The number of each X2's W1 equals each Y3's X2. The number of each X2's W9 equals 8 times each Y3's X2. How many W9 does each X7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["Y3's X2. X2's W9 as u. So u = 8 * Y3's X2 = 8 * 22 = 15.\nDefine each X1's W3 as S. So S = 19 * u - Y = 19 * 15 - 2 = 14.\nDefine each X1's W1 as A. So A = 8 * Y - u = 8 * 22 - 15 = 19.\nDefine each X1's WWW as i. So i = S + A = 14 + 19 = 10.\nDefine each Y6's X2 as Y. So Y = i = 10.\nDefine each Y6's X1 as F. So F = 6.\nDefine each X2's W1 as r. So r = Y = 10.\nDefine each X2's WWW as l. So l = r + u = 10 + 15 = 2.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as V. So V = Y * l + F * i = 10 * 2 + 6 * 10 = 19.\nDefine each X7's W3 as q. So q = V = 19.\nDefine each X7's W9 as z. So z = 20 * q = 20 * 19 = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 222, "question": "The number of each Y0's X7 equals 11 more than the sum of each Y1's X6 and each Y1's XXX. The number of each Y1's X6 equals 4. The number of each X7's W1 equals 18 times each Y0's XXX. The number of each X6's W0 equals the difference of each Y0's WWW and each X7's WWW. How many WWW does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Y1's X6 as u. So u = 4.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as S. So S = u = 4.\nDefine each Y0's X7 as A. So A = 11 * u + S = 11 * 4 + 4 = 2.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as i. So i = A = 2.\nDefine each X7's W1 as Y. So Y = 18 * i = 18 * 2 = 13.\nDefine each X7's WWW as F. So F = Y = 13.\nDefine each Y0's WWW as r. So r = A * F = 2 * 13 = 3.\nDefine each X6's W0 as l. So l = r - F = 3 - 13 = 13.\nDefine each X6's WWW as V. So V = l = 13.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as q. So q = u * V = 4 * 13 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 223, "question": "The number of each Z2's Y0 equals the difference of each Y0's XXX and each Z5's XXX. The number of each Z2's Y3 equals 19 more than each Z2's Y0. The number of each Y0's X8 equals 16. The number of each Z5's Y0 equals the sum of each Y0's X2, each Y0's XXX and each Y0's X8. The number of each Y0's X2 equals 8 more than each Y0's X8. How many Y3 does each Z2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Y0's X8 as u. So u = 16.\nDefine each Y0's X2 as S. So S = 8 * u = 8 * 16 = 13.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 13 + 16 = 6.\nDefine each Z5's Y0 as i. So i = (S + A + u) = (13 + 6 + 16) = 12.\nDefine each Z5's XXX as Y. So Y = i * A = 12 * 6 = 3.\nDefine each Z2's Y0 as F. So F = A - Y = 6 - 3 = 3.\nDefine each Z2's Y3 as r. So r = 19 * F = 19 * 3 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 224, "question": "The number of each Y0's X0 equals each Y2's X0. The number of each Y2's X0 equals 12. The number of each Z5's Y2 equals each Z7's XXX. The number of each Z4's Y2 equals the sum of each Y2's XXX, each Y2's X0 and each Y2's X8. The number of each Z7's Y0 equals 15 more than each Z4's XXX. The number of each Y3's X8 equals 22 more than the difference of each Z5's XXX and each Z7's Y0. The number of each Y2's X8 equals 15 more than each Y2's X0. The number of each Y0's X8 equals the sum of each Z7's Y0 and each Y0's X0. How many X8 does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Y2's X0 as u. So u = 12.\nDefine each Y2's X8 as S. So S = 15 * u = 15 * 12 = 19.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 19 + 12 = 8.\nDefine each Z4's Y2 as i. So i = (A + u + S) = (8 + 12 + 19) = 16.\nDefine each Z4's XXX as Y. So Y = i * A = 16 * 8 = 13.\nDefine each Z7's Y0 as F. So F = 15 * Y = 15 * 13 = 11.\nDefine each Y0's X0 as r. So r = u = 12.\nDefine each Y0's X8 as l. So l = F + r = 11 + 12 = 0.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as V. So V = l + r = 0 + 12 = 12.\nDefine each Z7's XXX as q. So q = F * V = 11 * 12 = 17.\nDefine each Z5's Y2 as z. So z = q = 17.\nDefine each Z5's XXX as A. So A = z * A = 17 * 8 = 21.\nDefine each Y3's X8 as i. So i = 22 * A - F = 22 * 21 - 11 = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 225, "question": "The number of each Y3's X8 equals 17. The number of each Z1's Y1 equals 13 times each Y3's X8. How many Y1 does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Y3's X8 = 17. Z1's Y1 = 13 + Y3's X8 = 13 + 17 = 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 226, "question": "The number of each Y4's X1 equals 14 more than the sum of each Y9's XXX, each Y9's X4 and each Y4's X4. The number of each Y4's X4 equals 7 times the sum of each X1's WWW and each Y9's XXX. The number of each X1's W7 equals 3. The number of each Y9's X4 equals each X1's WWW. How many XXX does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["Y9's X4 as u. So u = X1's W7 = 3.\nDefine each X1's W7 as S. So S = 3.\nDefine each X1's WWW as A. So A = S = 3.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as i. So i = u = 3.\nDefine each Y4's X4 as Y. So Y = 7 * A + i = 7 * 3 + 3 = 1.\nDefine each Y4's X1 as F. So F = 14 * (i + u + Y) = 14 * (3 + 3 + 1) = 19.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as r. So r = F + Y = 19 + 1 = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 227, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y3 equals 3 times each Z5's Y7. The number of each Y7's X4 equals 0 times each Z5's Y3. The number of each Z5's Y7 equals 0 more than each X1's W1. The number of each Z2's Y7 equals 4 more than each Y7's XXX. The number of each X1's W1 equals 21 times each X4's W0. The number of each X4's W0 equals 5. How many Y7 does each Z2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["X4's W0 = 5. X1's W1 = 21 * X4 = 21 * 5 = 13.\nDefine each Z5's Y7 as u. So u = 0 * X1's W1 = 0 * 13 = 0.\nDefine each Z5's Y3 as S. So S = 3 + u = 3 + 0 = 3.\nDefine each Y7's X4 as A. So A = 0 * S = 0 * 3 = 0.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as i. So i = A = 0.\nDefine each Z2's Y7 as Y. So Y = 4 * i = 4 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 228, "question": "The number of each Y6's X3 equals 17 more than the difference of each Y6's X6 and each Y7's X2. The number of each Y4's X6 equals 12 more than the sum of each Y6's X6 and each Y7's X6. The number of each Y6's X2 equals 20 more than the difference of each Y4's XXX and each Y7's X6. The number of each Y4's X2 equals 7 times the sum of each Y7's X6 and each Y7's X2. The number of each Y6's X6 equals 1 times each Y7's X2. The number of each Y7's X3 equals 19 more than each Y6's X3. The number of each Y4's X3 equals 16 times each Y4's X6. The number of each Y7's X6 equals 12 times each Y7's X3. The number of each Y7's X2 equals 14. How many X2 does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["14. So 14.\nDefine each Y7's X2 as u. So u = 14.\nDefine each Y6's X6 as S. So S = 1 * u = 1 * 14 = 14.\nDefine each Y6's X3 as A. So A = 17 * S - u = 17 * 14 - 14 = 7.\nDefine each Y7's X3 as i. So i = 19 * A = 19 * 7 = 18.\nDefine each Y7's X6 as Y. So Y = 12 * i = 12 * 18 = 9.\nDefine each Y4's X6 as F. So F = 12 * S + Y = 12 * 14 + 9 = 16.\nDefine each Y4's X3 as r. So r = 16 * F = 16 * 16 = 3.\nDefine each Y4's X2 as l. So l = 7 * Y + u = 7 * 9 + 14 = 15.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as V. So V = l + r + F = 15 + 3 + 16 = 11.\nDefine each Y6's X2 as q. So q = 20 * V - Y = 20 * 11 - 9 = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 229, "question": "The number of each Y0's X7 equals 21. How many X7 does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["Y0's X7 = 21.\nThus, the answer is 21."], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 230, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y6 equals 16 more than each Y6's X7. The number of each Z5's Y9 equals 3 more than each Z0's Y6. The number of each Y6's X7 equals 7. How many YYY does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["Y6's X7 as u. So u = 7.\nDefine each Z0's Y6 as S. So S = 16 * u = 16 * 7 = 20.\nDefine each Z5's Y9 as A. So A = 3 * S = 3 * 20 = 14.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as i. So i = A = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 231, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y4 equals 8 more than the sum of each Z8's WWW, each Y2's WWW and each Y2's X6. The number of each Z8's Y2 equals the sum of each X3's W6, each X6's W1 and each Z3's Y4. The number of each Z3's Y3 equals 3. The number of each X6's W3 equals 3 more than each Z3's Y4. The number of each Y2's X6 equals 17. The number of each X3's W6 equals the sum of each X1's W1 and each Z3's Y4. The number of each X3's W1 equals 20 more than each X1's W1. The number of each X1's W1 equals each Z3's Y3. The number of each Z3's Y4 equals 4 more than each X3's W1. The number of each X6's W1 equals each X1's W1. The number of each Y4's X3 equals 11 times each Y2's X6. How many XXX does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Z3's Y3 = 3. X1's W1 = Z3's Y3 = 3.\nDefine each X3's W1 as u. So u = 20 * X1's W1 = 20 * 3 = 14.\nDefine each Z3's Y4 as S. So S = 4 * u = 4 * 14 = 10.\nDefine each X6's W3 as A. So A = 3 * S = 3 * 10 = 7.\nDefine each X6's W1 as i. So i = X1's W1 = 3.\nDefine each X6's WWW as Y. So Y = A + i = 7 + 3 = 10.\nDefine each Y2's X6 as F. So F = 17.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as r. So r = F * Y = 17 * 10 = 9.\nDefine each Z8's Y2 as l. So l = (F + i + S) = (17 + 3 + 10) = 7.\nDefine each Z8's WWW as V. So V = l * r = 7 * 9 = 17.\nDefine each Z0's Y4 as q. So q = 8 * (V + r + F) = 8 * (17 + 9 + 17) = 19.\nDefine each Z0's XXX as z. So z = q * Y = 19 * 10 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 232, "question": "The number of each Y6's X2 equals 20 times each Y2's X1. The number of each Z4's Y6 equals 20 times each Z5's Y2. The number of each Z5's Y2 equals each Y6's X2. The number of each Z8's Y6 equals 22. The number of each Y2's X0 equals the sum of each Z8's Y6 and each Z4's Y6. The number of each Y2's X1 equals each Z8's Y6. The number of each Y7's X0 equals the sum of each Y2's X1, each Z8's Y6, each Y2's X0 and each Z5's Y2. How many X0 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Z8's Y6. Y2's X1 = u = 22.\nDefine each Y6's X2 as S. So S = 20 * u = 20 * 22 = 3.\nDefine each Z5's Y2 as A. So A = S = 3.\nDefine each Z4's Y6 as i. So i = 20 * A = 20 * 3 = 14.\nDefine each Z8's Y6 as Y. So Y = 22.\nDefine each Y2's X0 as F. So F = Y + i = 22 + 14 = 13.\nDefine each Y7's X0 as r. So r = (u + Y + F + A) = (22 + 22 + 13 + 3) = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 233, "question": "The number of each Y8's X1 equals the sum of each Y8's X7 and each Y4's X9. The number of each Y4's X1 equals 21 more than the sum of each Y8's XXX and each Y8's X9. The number of each Y8's X9 equals 11 times the sum of each Y8's X1, each Y4's X9 and each Y8's X7. The number of each Y4's X9 equals 16. The number of each Y8's X7 equals each Y4's X9. How many X1 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Y4's X9 as u. So u = 16.\nDefine each Y8's X7 as S. So S = u = 16.\nDefine each Y8's X1 as A. So A = S + u = 16 + 16 = 9.\nDefine each Y8's X9 as i. So i = 11 * (A + u + S) = 11 * (9 + 16 + 16) = 19.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as Y. So Y = S + A + i = 16 + 9 + 19 = 21.\nDefine each Y4's X1 as F. So F = 21 * Y + i = 21 * 21 + 19 = 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 234, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y9 equals 19. The number of each X3's W6 equals 14 times each Z7's YYY. How many W6 does each X3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["X3's W6 = 14 * Z7's Y9 = 14 * 19 = 13.\nDefine each Z7's Y9 as u. So u = 19.\nDefine each Z7's YYY as S. So S = u = 19.\nDefine each X3's W6 as A. So A = 14 * S = 14 * 19 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 235, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y6 equals 3 times each Z0's Y4. The number of each X9's W0 equals 15 more than the sum of each Z0's Y6, each X4's W0 and each Z0's Y4. The number of each Y4's X9 equals the sum of each Y4's X8, each X8's W0 and each Z0's Y6. The number of each X8's W0 equals 2 more than the sum of each X4's W0 and each X9's W0. The number of each X4's W0 equals each Z0's YYY. The number of each Z0's Y4 equals 13. The number of each Y4's X8 equals 12 more than the difference of each X8's W0 and each X9's W0. How many X9 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Z0's Y4 as u. So u = 13.\nDefine each Z0's Y6 as S. So S = 3 * u = 3 * 13 = 16.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 16 + 13 = 6.\nDefine each X4's W0 as i. So i = A = 6.\nDefine each X9's W0 as Y. So Y = 15 * (S + i + u) = 15 * (16 + 6 + 13) = 19.\nDefine each X8's W0 as F. So F = 2 * i + Y = 2 * 6 + 19 = 8.\nDefine each Y4's X8 as r. So r = 12 * F - Y = 12 * 8 - 19 = 19.\nDefine each Y4's X9 as l. So l = (r + F + S) = (19 + 8 + 16) = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 236, "question": "The number of each Y1's X9 equals 11 times the difference of each Y7's X3 and each Y1's X8. The number of each Y7's X3 equals 20. The number of each Y6's X3 equals 12 times the sum of each Y6's X7 and each Y1's X8. The number of each Y1's X8 equals 15 more than each Y7's X3. The number of each Y6's X7 equals 10 more than each Y1's X9. How many X3 does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["Y7's X3 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each Y1's X8 as S. So S = 15 * u = 15 * 20 = 1.\nDefine each Y1's X9 as A. So A = 11 * u - S = 11 * 20 - 1 = 1.\nDefine each Y6's X7 as i. So i = 10 * A = 10 * 1 = 10.\nDefine each Y6's X3 as Y. So Y = 12 * i + S = 12 * 10 + 1 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 237, "question": "The number of each Y1's X9 equals 15 times each Y0's X8. The number of each Y0's X8 equals 19. The number of each Y1's X1 equals each Y0's X8. The number of each Y3's X8 equals 21 times each Y1's XXX. How many X8 does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["Y0's X8 = 19. Y1's X9 as u. So u = 15 * Y0's X8 = 15 * 19 = 9.\nDefine each Y1's X1 as S. So S = Y0's X8 = 19.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 19 + 9 = 5.\nDefine each Y3's X8 as i. So i = 21 * A = 21 * 5 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 238, "question": "The number of each Y6's X5 equals the difference of each Y9's X0 and each Y9's XXX. The number of each Z7's Y9 equals 16 times each Z3's YYY. The number of each Z3's Y9 equals 6 times each Y6's XXX. The number of each Y9's X5 equals 20 times each Z7's Y6. The number of each Z7's Y6 equals 4. The number of each Y6's X0 equals 14 more than the difference of each Y9's X0 and each Y9's XXX. The number of each Z3's Y6 equals the sum of each Z3's Y9, each Y6's X5 and each Y9's XXX. The number of each Y9's X0 equals 13 more than each Z7's Y6. How many Y9 does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 239, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y5 equals each Z4's Y7. The number of each Z4's Y7 equals 17 more than each Z4's Y5. The number of each Z4's Y5 equals 19 more than each Z4's Y6. The number of each Z4's Y6 equals 5. How many Y5 does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["Z4's Y6 as u. So u = 5.\nDefine each Z4's Y5 as S. So S = 19 * u = 19 * 5 = 3.\nDefine each Z4's Y7 as A. So A = 17 * S = 17 * 3 = 5.\nDefine each Z7's Y5 as i. So i = A = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 240, "question": "The number of each X0's W4 equals 7 times each X2's WWW. The number of each Y6's X3 equals 6. The number of each X2's W7 equals the sum of each Y6's WWW and each X2's W4. The number of each X3's W7 equals 1 more than each Y6's X3. The number of each X2's W4 equals 19 times the sum of each Y6's WWW and each X3's W7. How many W4 does each X0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["Y6's X3 = 6. X3's W7 = 1 * Y6's = 1 * 6 = 6.\nDefine each X3's WWW as u. So u = 6.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as S. So S = Y6's X3 * u = 6 * 6 = 13.\nDefine each X2's W4 as A. So A = 19 * S + u = 19 * 13 + 6 = 17.\nDefine each X2's W7 as i. So i = S + A = 13 + 17 = 7.\nDefine each X2's WWW as Y. So Y = i + A = 7 + 17 = 1.\nDefine each X0's W4 as F. So F = 7 * Y = 7 * 1 = 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 241, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y2 equals 17. The number of each Z8's Y2 equals each Z8's Y8. The number of each Z8's Y5 equals 11 more than the difference of each Z2's YYY and each Z8's Y7. The number of each Z6's Y7 equals each Z6's Y2. The number of each Z2's Y5 equals 8. The number of each Z2's Y7 equals 7 times each Z9's Y2. The number of each Z9's Y8 equals each Z6's YYY. The number of each Z8's Y7 equals each Z2's Y7. The number of each Z8's Y8 equals 1 times each Z2's YYY. The number of each Z2's Y8 equals 9 more than each Z9's Y2. The number of each Z6's Y2 equals 1 times the sum of each Z2's Y7, each Z8's YYY and each Z8's Y8. How many Y8 does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["Z9's Y2. Z2's Y8 as u. So u = 9 * S9 = 12.\nDefine each Z2's Y7 as S. So S = 7 * u = 7 * 12 = 15.\nDefine each Z2's Y5 as A. So A = 8.\nDefine each Z2's YYY as i. So i = S + A + u = 15 + 8 + 12 = 12.\nDefine each Z8's Y8 as Y. So Y = 1 * i = 1 * 12 = 12.\nDefine each Z8's Y5 as F. So F = 11 * i - Y = 11 * 12 - 12 = 5.\nDefine each Z8's Y2 as r. So r = Y = 12.\nDefine each Z8's YYY as l. So l = r + Y + F = 12 + 12 + 5 = 6.\nDefine each Z6's Y2 as V. So V = 1 * (S + l + Y) = 1 * (15 + 6 + 12) = 10.\nDefine each Z6's Y7 as q. So q = V = 10.\nDefine each Z6's YYY as z. So z = q + V = 10 + 10 = 20.\nDefine each Z9's Y8 as A. So A = S = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 242, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y2 equals 20 more than the difference of each Z2's Y0 and each Z2's YYY. The number of each Z8's Y2 equals each Z1's Y2. The number of each Z5's Y0 equals the difference of each Z2's Y0 and each Z8's Y2. The number of each Z2's Y0 equals 4. How many Y0 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["Z2's Y0 as u. So u = 4.\nDefine each Z2's YYY as S. So S = u = 4.\nDefine each Z1's Y2 as A. So A = 20 * u - S = 20 * 4 - 4 = 13.\nDefine each Z8's Y2 as i. So i = A = 13.\nDefine each Z5's Y0 as Y. So Y = u - i = 4 - 13 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 243, "question": "The number of each Z4's Y6 equals 5. How many Y6 does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Z4's Y6 = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 244, "question": "The number of each X2's W5 equals 16 times each X0's W6. The number of each X0's W6 equals 3. How many W5 does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["X0's W6 = 3. X2's W5 = 16 * X0's W6 = 16 * 3 = 2.\nDefine each X2's WWW as u. So u = X2's W5 = 2.\nDefine each Y1's l0 as S. So S = 2.\nDefine each Y1's l0 as A. So A = 2.\nDefine each Y1's lWW as i. So i = S * u + A * u = 2 * 2 + 2 * 2 = 8.\nDefine each X3's WWW as Y. So Y = X3's WWW = 3.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as F. So F = S * i + A * u = 2 * 8 + 2 * 2 = 20.\nDefine each X0's W6 as r. So r = 3.\nDefine each X2's W5 as l. So l = 16 * r = 16 * 3 = 2.\nDefine each X2's WWW as V. So V = l = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 245, "question": "The number of each X5's W1 equals 9. The number of each Y2's X5 equals each X5's W1. The number of each X8's W6 equals the difference of each Y2's WWW and each Y2's X5. The number of each X5's W6 equals 4 more than each X5's W1. How many W6 does each X8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["X5's W1 = 9. X5's W6 = 4 * X5 = 4 * 9 = 13.\nDefine each X5's WWW as u. So u = u = 9.\nDefine each Y2's X5 as S. So S = u = 9.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as A. So A = S * u = 9 * 9 = 12.\nDefine each X8's W6 as i. So i = A - S = 12 - 9 = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 246, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y8 equals the difference of each Z6's Y3 and each Y9's X4. The number of each Y8's X9 equals 18. The number of each Y3's X9 equals 5. The number of each Z6's Y3 equals 9. The number of each Y3's X4 equals 2 more than each Y9's XXX. The number of each Z6's Y9 equals each Z6's Y8. The number of each Y9's X4 equals the difference of each Z3's Y9 and each Y8's X9. The number of each Y3's X1 equals 15 more than each Z3's Y9. The number of each Z3's Y9 equals each Z6's Y3. The number of each Y9's X1 equals 10 times each Y8's XXX. How many XXX does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["Z6's Y3 as u. So u = 9.\nDefine each Z3's Y9 as S. So S = u = 9.\nDefine each Y3's X1 as A. So A = 15 * S = 15 * 9 = 20.\nDefine each Y8's X9 as i. So i = 18.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as Y. So Y = i = 18.\nDefine each Y9's X1 as F. So F = 10 * Y = 10 * 18 = 19.\nDefine each Y9's X4 as r. So r = S - i = 9 - 18 = 14.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as l. So l = r + F = 14 + 19 = 10.\nDefine each Z6's Y8 as V. So V = u - r = 9 - 14 = 18.\nDefine each Z6's Y9 as q. So q = V = 18.\nDefine each Z6's Y3 as z. So z = 9.\nDefine each Z6's XXX as A. So A = q * l + u * Y = 18 * 10 + 9 * 18 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 247, "question": "The number of each Y8's X5 equals 22 times each Z8's Y1. The number of each Y8's X6 equals each Y8's X5. The number of each Z8's Y1 equals 18. How many X6 does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Z8's Y1 as u. So u = 18.\nDefine each Y8's X5 as S. So S = 22 * u = 22 * 18 = 5.\nDefine each Y8's X6 as A. So A = S = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 248, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y4 equals 10 times each Z1's XXX. The number of each Z1's Y4 equals 19 times the difference of each Z5's XXX and each Y6's X5. The number of each Y6's X5 equals 3 more than each Z5's Y6. The number of each Y9's X2 equals 20 times the sum of each Y4's XXX, each Z5's Y6 and each Z6's Y4. The number of each Z5's Y6 equals 0. The number of each Z6's Y9 equals each Y9's X2. The number of each Z3's Y4 equals the sum of each Z1's XXX, each Z6's Y9 and each Z5's Y6. The number of each Y4's X5 equals 4 times each Z5's XXX. How many Y4 does each Z3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Z5's Y6 = 0. Y6's X5 = 3 * Z5's = 3 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as u. So u = Y0.\nDefine each Z5's XXX as S. So S = Y6's XXX = 0.\nDefine each Y4's X5 as A. So A = 4 * S = 4 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as i. So i = A = 0.\nDefine each Z1's Y4 as Y. So Y = 19 * S - u = 19 * 0 - 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z1's XXX as F. So F = Y * i = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z6's Y4 as r. So r = 10 * F = 10 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y9's X2 as l. So l = 20 * (i + S + r) = 20 * (0 + 0 + 0) = 0.\nDefine each Z6's Y9 as V. So V = l = 0.\nDefine each Z3's Y4 as q. So q = (F + V + S) = (0 + 0 + 0) = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 249, "question": "The number of each Y7's X2 equals each Z5's WWW. The number of each Y1's X7 equals 11. The number of each Z3's Y7 equals 0. The number of each X7's W1 equals 18 more than each Z5's XXX. The number of each Z5's Y1 equals 21 times each Y1's X7. The number of each Z3's Y1 equals each Y1's XXX. The number of each X2's W1 equals 13 more than each Z3's XXX. How many WWW does each Z3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["Y1's X7 = 11. Z5's Y1 as u. So u = 21 * u = 21 * 11 = 1.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as S. So S = u = 1.\nDefine each Z5's XXX as A. So A = u * S = 1 * 1 = 1.\nDefine each X7's W1 as i. So i = 18 * A = 18 * 1 = 18.\nDefine each X7's WWW as Y. So Y = i = 18.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as F. So F = S * Y = 1 * 18 = 18.\nDefine each Z3's Y1 as r. So r = S = 1.\nDefine each Z3's Y7 as l. So l = 0.\nDefine each Z3's XXX as V. So V = l * A + r * S = 0 * 1 + 1 * 1 = 1.\nDefine each X2's W1 as q. So q = 13 * V = 13 * 1 = 13.\nDefine each X2's WWW as z. So z = q = 13.\nDefine each Z5's WWW as A. So A = u * F = 1 * 18 = 18.\nDefine each Y7's X2 as i. So i = A = 18.\nDefine each Y7's WWW as Y. So Y = i * Z = 18 * 13 = 4.\nDefine each Z3's WWW as F. So F = l * Y + r * F = 0 * 4 + 1 * 18 = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 250, "question": "The number of each Y7's X2 equals 9. How many XXX does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["Y7's X2 = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's X2 as u. So u = 9. Y7's XXX as S. So S = u = 9. Y7's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 9 + 9 = 18. Y7's XXX as i. So i = S + u = 18 + 9 = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 251, "question": "The number of each Y2's X3 equals the difference of each X5's W3 and each Z1's Y6. The number of each Z9's Y6 equals 11. The number of each X5's W3 equals 5 times each Z1's XXX. The number of each Y6's X5 equals each Z9's Y6. The number of each Z1's Y6 equals 17. The number of each Y6's X3 equals 21 times each Y6's X5. How many XXX does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Z9's Y6 = 11. Y6's X5 = Z9's Y6 = 11. Y6's X3 = 21 * Y6's X5 = 21. Y6's XXX as i. So i = Y6's X5 + Y6's X3 = 11 + 21 = 9.\nDefine each Z1's Y6 as Y. So Y = 17.\nDefine each Z1's XXX as F. So F = Y * i = 17 * 9 = 15.\nDefine each X5's W3 as r. So r = 5 * F = 5 * 15 = 6.\nDefine each Y2's X3 as l. So l = r - Y = 6 - 17 = 12.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as V. So V = l = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 252, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y4 equals 18. The number of each Y7's X5 equals 22 more than the sum of each Y7's X4, each Y4's XXX and each Y4's X5. The number of each Z7's Y7 equals 4 times each Y7's X5. The number of each Y4's X4 equals 18 more than each Y4's X5. The number of each Y4's X5 equals 2 times each Y7's X4. The number of each Y7's X4 equals 22. How many YYY does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["Y7's X4 as u. So u = 22.\nDefine each Y4's X5 as S. So S = 2 * u = 2 * 22 = 21.\nDefine each Y4's X4 as A. So A = 18 * S = 18 * 21 = 10.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as i. So i = S + A = 21 + 10 = 8.\nDefine each Y7's X5 as Y. So Y = 22 * (u + i + S) = 22 * (22 + 8 + 21) = 19.\nDefine each Z7's Y7 as F. So F = 4 + Y = 4 + 19 = 0.\nDefine each Z7's Y4 as r. So r = 18.\nDefine each Z7's YYY as l. So l = r + F = 18 + 0 = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 253, "question": "The number of each Y9's X6 equals 16 times each Y4's XXX. The number of each Y9's X3 equals 9 more than each Y9's X6. The number of each Y7's X3 equals 18. The number of each Y4's X6 equals 21 more than each Y7's X3. How many XXX does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Y7's X3 = 18. Y4's X6 as u. So u = 21 * Y7's X3 = 21 * 18 = 10.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as S. So S = u = 10.\nDefine each Y9's X6 as A. So A = 16 * S = 16 * 10 = 22.\nDefine each Y9's X3 as i. So i = 9 * A = 9 * 22 = 14.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as Y. So Y = i + A = 14 + 22 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 254, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y8 equals the sum of each Z3's YYY and each Z8's Y9. The number of each Z7's Y9 equals 22 times each Z4's Y9. The number of each Z3's Y4 equals 21. The number of each Z8's Y4 equals the sum of each Z3's Y9 and each Z3's YYY. The number of each Z3's Y1 equals 17 times each Z4's Y4. The number of each Z8's Y9 equals the difference of each Z8's Y4 and each Z3's Y4. The number of each Z4's Y4 equals each Z3's Y4. The number of each Z8's Y1 equals 10 times each Z3's YYY. The number of each Z3's Y9 equals 18 more than each Z4's Y4. The number of each Z4's Y9 equals 16 times each Z8's YYY. How many Y9 does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["22 + Z4's Y9 = 16 + 16 = 9.\nDefine each Z3's Y4 as u. So u = 21.\nDefine each Z4's Y4 as S. So S = u = 21.\nDefine each Z3's Y9 as A. So A = 18 * S = 18 * 21 = 10.\nDefine each Z3's Y1 as i. So i = 17 * S = 17 * 21 = 12.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as Y. So Y = u + A + i = 21 + 10 + 12 = 20.\nDefine each Z8's Y1 as F. So F = 10 * Y = 10 * 20 = 16.\nDefine each Z8's Y4 as r. So r = A + Y = 10 + 20 = 7.\nDefine each Z8's Y9 as l. So l = r - u = 7 - 21 = 9.\nDefine each Z8's Y8 as V. So V = Y + l = 20 + 9 = 6.\nDefine each Z8's YYY as q. So q = l + r + F + V = 9 + 7 + 16 + 6 = 15.\nDefine each Z4's Y9 as z. So z = 16 * q = 16 * 15 = 10.\nDefine each Z7's Y9 as A. So A = 22 * S = 22 * 21 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 255, "question": "The number of each Y6's X8 equals the sum of each Z5's Y6 and each Y2's XXX. The number of each Z5's Y6 equals 19. The number of each Z5's Y2 equals 17. The number of each Y2's X0 equals 12 times the difference of each Z5's Y6 and each Z5's YYY. The number of each Z3's Y6 equals 7. How many XXX does each Z3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Z5's Y2 as u. So u = 17.\nDefine each Z5's Y6 as S. So S = 19.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 19 + 17 = 13.\nDefine each Y2's X0 as i. So i = 12 * S - A = 12 * 19 - 13 = 18.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as Y. So Y = i = 18.\nDefine each Y6's X8 as F. So F = S + Y = 19 + 18 = 14.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as r. So r = F = 14.\nDefine each Z3's Y6 as l. So l = 7.\nDefine each Z3's XXX as V. So V = l * r = 7 * 14 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 256, "question": "The number of each Y1's X4 equals 16. The number of each X8's W3 equals 22 times each Y1's X9. The number of each Z1's Y1 equals 9 more than each Y1's X4. The number of each Y1's X9 equals 7. The number of each Y1's X8 equals 17 more than each X8's W3. How many XXX does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Y1's X9 as u. So u = 7.\nDefine each X8's W3 as S. So S = 22 * u = 22 * 7 = 16.\nDefine each Y1's X8 as A. So A = 17 * S = 17 * 16 = 19.\nDefine each Y1's X4 as i. So i = 16.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as Y. So Y = u + A + i = 7 + 19 + 16 = 19.\nDefine each Z1's Y1 as F. So F = 9 * i = 9 * 16 = 6.\nDefine each Z1's XXX as r. So r = F * Y = 6 * 19 = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 257, "question": "The number of each X4's W2 equals 19. How many W2 does each X4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["X4's W2 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 258, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y1 equals 16 more than each Z5's YYY. The number of each Z5's Y2 equals 1 times each Z5's Y3. The number of each Z5's Y3 equals 4. The number of each Z3's Y2 equals 20. How many YYY does each Z3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["Z5's Y3 as u. So u = 4.\nDefine each Z5's Y2 as S. So S = 1 * u = 1 * 4 = 4.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 4 + 4 = 8.\nDefine each Z3's Y1 as i. So i = 16 * A = 16 * 8 = 13.\nDefine each Z3's Y2 as Y. So Y = 20.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as F. So F = Y + i = 20 + 13 = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 259, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y2 equals 9 times each Z0's XXX. The number of each Z0's Y2 equals 4 times each Y2's X1. The number of each Y2's X1 equals 22. How many YYY does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["Y2's X1 as u. So u = 22.\nDefine each Z0's Y2 as S. So S = 4 * u = 4 * 22 = 19.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as A. So A = u = 22.\nDefine each Z0's XXX as i. So i = S * A = 19 * 22 = 4.\nDefine each Z1's Y2 as Y. So Y = 9 * i = 9 * 4 = 13.\nDefine each Z1's YYY as F. So F = Y = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 260, "question": "The number of each Y7's X6 equals 6 more than the difference of each Y7's X1 and each X6's WWW. The number of each Y7's X1 equals 0 times the sum of each X6's W5, each X6's W4 and each X6's WWW. The number of each X6's W2 equals 21. The number of each X1's W4 equals each X6's W4. The number of each X6's W5 equals 12 times each X6's W2. The number of each X1's W2 equals each Y3's XXX. The number of each X6's W4 equals 1 times the sum of each X6's W2 and each X6's W5. The number of each Y3's X1 equals each Y7's X6. The number of each Y3's X6 equals 4 more than the difference of each X1's W4 and each Y3's X1. How many W2 does each X1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 261, "question": "The number of each Y9's X0 equals 19. How many XXX does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Y9's X0 = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9's XXX = 19. Y9'"], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 262, "question": "The number of each Y7's X0 equals 13. How many X0 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["Y7's X0 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 263, "question": "The number of each Y8's X9 equals 21. The number of each Y8's X8 equals the sum of each Z9's Y4 and each Z3's Y3. The number of each Z3's Y3 equals 20 more than each Y8's X9. The number of each Z9's Y4 equals 8 times each Z3's Y3. How many XXX does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["Y8's X9 as u. So u = 21.\nDefine each Z3's Y3 as S. So S = 20 * u = 20 * 21 = 6.\nDefine each Z9's Y4 as A. So A = 8 * S = 8 * 6 = 2.\nDefine each Y8's X8 as i. So i = A + S = 2 + 6 = 8.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as Y. So Y = u + i = 21 + 8 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 264, "question": "The number of each Y1's X0 equals 21 times each X8's WWW. The number of each X8's W4 equals 22. How many X0 does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["X8's W4 as u. So u = 22.\nDefine each X8's WWW as S. So S = u = 22.\nDefine each Y1's X0 as A. So A = 21 * S = 21 * 22 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 265, "question": "The number of each X6's W1 equals 18. How many W1 does each X6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["X6's W1 = 18.\nDefine each X6's WWW as u. So u = X6's W1 = 18.\nDefine each Y1's l0 as S. So S = 20.\nDefine each Y1's l0 as A. So A = 20.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as i. So i = S + A = 20 + 20 = 17.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as l. So l = S + A = 20 + 20 = 17.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as V. So V = S + A = 20 + 20 = 17.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as q. So q = S + A + V = 20 + 20 + 17 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 266, "question": "The number of each X6's W4 equals 7. The number of each X1's W4 equals 0 more than the sum of each Y0's WWW, each Y0's X6 and each X6's WWW. The number of each Z0's Y1 equals each Y0's X6. The number of each Y0's X6 equals 5 more than the difference of each X6's WWW and each X6's W4. The number of each Y1's X1 equals 14 times the sum of each Y0's WWW, each X1's W4 and each X6's W4. How many WWW does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Y0's X6 as u. So u = 5 * X6's W4 - u = 5 * 7 - 5 = 12.\nDefine each X6's W4 as S. So S = 7.\nDefine each X6's WWW as A. So A = S = 7.\nDefine each Y0's WWW as i. So i = u * A = 12 * 7 = 15.\nDefine each X1's W4 as Y. So Y = 0 * (i + u + A) = 0 * (15 + 12 + 7) = 0.\nDefine each Y1's X1 as F. So F = 14 * (i + Y + S) = 14 * (15 + 0 + 7) = 11.\nDefine each X1's WWW as r. So r = Y = 0.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as l. So l = F * r = 11 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z0's Y1 as V. So V = u = 12.\nDefine each Z0's WWW as q. So q = V * l = 12 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 267, "question": "The number of each Y7's X3 equals 14. The number of each Y7's X1 equals 14 times each Y6's X1. The number of each Y6's X1 equals each Y7's X3. The number of each Y2's X0 equals 2 times the sum of each Y7's X1, each Y6's X1 and each Y7's XXX. How many XXX does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["Y7's X3 as u. So u = 14.\nDefine each Y6's X1 as S. So S = u = 14.\nDefine each Y7's X1 as A. So A = 14 * S = 14 * 14 = 12.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as i. So i = A + u = 12 + 14 = 3.\nDefine each Y2's X0 as Y. So Y = 2 * (A + S + i) = 2 * (12 + 14 + 3) = 19.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as F. So F = Y = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 268, "question": "The number of each Y5's X8 equals 20. How many X8 does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Y5's X8 = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 269, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y1 equals 17. The number of each Y1's X8 equals 16 times the sum of each Y1's X5, each Z7's Y0 and each Z7's Y1. The number of each Z7's Y0 equals 6. The number of each Y1's X5 equals 5 more than the sum of each Z7's YYY, each Z7's Y0 and each Z7's Y1. The number of each Y0's X5 equals the sum of each Y1's X8, each Z7's Y1 and each Y1's XXX. How many X5 does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["Y1's X5 as u. So u = 5 * (S7's Y1 + Z7's Y0 + u) = 5 * (17 + 6 + 5) = 19.\nDefine each Z7's Y1 as A. So A = 17.\nDefine each Z7's Y0 as i. So i = 6.\nDefine each Z7's YYY as Y. So Y = i + A = 6 + 17 = 0.\nDefine each Y1's X8 as F. So F = 16 * (u + i + A) = 16 * (19 + 6 + 17) = 19.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as r. So r = F + u = 19 + 19 = 15.\nDefine each Y0's X5 as l. So l = (F + A + r) = (19 + 17 + 15) = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 270, "question": "The number of each Y7's X3 equals 8 times each X3's W4. The number of each Y1's X3 equals 5 more than each Y2's X6. The number of each X6's W4 equals each Y2's X3. The number of each Y2's X3 equals 9. The number of each Y2's X6 equals the sum of each X3's W2 and each Y2's X3. The number of each X9's W2 equals 9 more than the difference of each X6's W4 and each Y2's X3. The number of each X3's W4 equals 12 times the difference of each X9's WWW and each X6's W4. The number of each X9's W4 equals the difference of each Y2's X3 and each X9's W2. The number of each X3's W2 equals 1 more than each Y7's X3. The number of each X9's W1 equals 8 times each X9's W2. How many X3 does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["Y2's X3 as u. So u = 9.\nDefine each X6's W4 as S. So S = u = 9.\nDefine each X9's W2 as A. So A = 9 * S - u = 9 * 9 - 9 = 21.\nDefine each X9's W4 as i. So i = u - A = 9 - 21 = 11.\nDefine each X9's W1 as Y. So Y = 8 * A = 8 * 21 = 7.\nDefine each X9's WWW as F. So F = Y + A + i = 7 + 21 + 11 = 16.\nDefine each X3's W4 as r. So r = 12 * F - S = 12 * 16 - 9 = 19.\nDefine each Y7's X3 as l. So l = 8 * r = 8 * 19 = 14.\nDefine each X3's W2 as V. So V = 1 * l = 1 * 14 = 14.\nDefine each Y2's X6 as q. So q = V + u = 14 + 9 = 0.\nDefine each Y1's X3 as z. So z = 5 * q = 5 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 271, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y1 equals the sum of each Z2's YYY, each Z6's Y3 and each Z2's Y3. The number of each Z2's Y3 equals 6. The number of each Z9's Y2 equals 5 times each Z9's Y3. The number of each Z9's Y3 equals 1 more than each Z2's YYY. The number of each Z6's Y3 equals the difference of each Z2's Y3 and each Z9's YYY. How many YYY does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["Z2's Y3 as u. So u = 6.\nDefine each Z2's YYY as S. So S = u = 6.\nDefine each Z9's Y3 as A. So A = 1 * S = 1 * 6 = 6.\nDefine each Z9's Y2 as i. So i = 5 * A = 5 * 6 = 7.\nDefine each Z9's YYY as Y. So Y = A + i = 6 + 7 = 13.\nDefine each Z6's Y3 as F. So F = u - Y = 6 - 13 = 16.\nDefine each Z6's Y1 as r. So r = (S + F + u) = (6 + 16 + 6) = 5.\nDefine each Z6's YYY as l. So l = r + F = 5 + 16 = 21.\nThus, the answer is 21."], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 272, "question": "The number of each X3's W4 equals 11 times each X5's WWW. The number of each X5's W0 equals 18. The number of each X4's W0 equals 19 more than each X3's WWW. How many WWW does each X4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["X5's W0 = 18. X5's WWW = 18. X3's W4 = 11 * X5's W0 = 11 * 18 = 14.\nDefine each X3's WWW as u. So u = X3's W4 = 14.\nDefine each X4's W0 as S. So S = 19 * u = 19 * 14 = 13.\nDefine each X4's WWW as A. So A = S = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 273, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y9 equals the sum of each Z9's YYY and each Z3's Y2. The number of each Z0's Y4 equals 4. The number of each Z9's Y8 equals 2 more than each Z0's Y4. The number of each Z2's Y2 equals 18 more than each Z3's YYY. The number of each Z3's Y2 equals 11 more than the sum of each Z9's YYY, each Z9's Y8 and each Z0's Y4. How many YYY does each Z2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["Z0's Y4 = 4. Z9's Y8 as u. So u = 2 * Z0's Y4 = 2 * 4 = 8.\nDefine each Z9's YYY as S. So S = u = 8.\nDefine each Z3's Y2 as A. So A = 11 * (S + u + the Z0's Y4) = 11 * (8 + 8 + 4) = 19.\nDefine each Z3's Y9 as i. So i = S + A = 8 + 19 = 4.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as Y. So Y = i + A = 4 + 19 = 0.\nDefine each Z2's Y2 as F. So F = 18 * Y = 18 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z2's YYY as r. So r = F = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 274, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y6 equals 12 more than each Z5's YYY. The number of each Z5's Y7 equals 5. How many Y6 does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["Z5's Y7 as u. So u = 5.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as S. So S = u = 5.\nDefine each Z0's Y6 as A. So A = 12 * S = 12 * 5 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 275, "question": "The number of each Y8's X1 equals 0 more than each Y3's X1. The number of each Y2's X1 equals 8 times each Y3's XXX. The number of each Y2's X5 equals the sum of each Y2's X1 and each Y8's XXX. The number of each Y3's X5 equals 14 more than the sum of each Y8's X1 and each Y8's XXX. The number of each Y3's X1 equals 2. How many X5 does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Y3's X1 as u. So u = 2.\nDefine each Y8's X1 as S. So S = 0 * u = 0 * 2 = 0.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as A. So A = S = 0.\nDefine each Y3's X5 as i. So i = 14 * S + A = 14 * 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as Y. So Y = u + i = 2 + 0 = 2.\nDefine each Y2's X1 as F. So F = 8 * Y = 8 * 2 = 16.\nDefine each Y2's X5 as r. So r = F + A = 16 + 0 = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 276, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y6 equals 3 more than each Y6's XXX. The number of each Y6's X5 equals each Y6's X6. The number of each X6's W6 equals 7. The number of each Y6's X6 equals 16 more than each X6's W6. How many Y6 does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["X6's W6 = 7. Y6's X6 as u. So u = 16 * X6's W6 = 16 * 7 = 20.\nDefine each Y6's X5 as S. So S = u = 20.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 20 + 20 = 17.\nDefine each Z7's Y6 as i. So i = 3 * A = 3 * 17 = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 277, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y8 equals 15 more than each Z8's Y0. The number of each Z8's Y0 equals 22. The number of each Z5's Y0 equals 11 times each Z0's Y8. How many Y0 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Z8's Y0 as u. So u = 22.\nDefine each Z0's Y8 as S. So S = 15 * u = 15 * 22 = 8.\nDefine each Z5's Y0 as A. So A = 11 * S = 11 * 8 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 278, "question": "The number of each X2's W8 equals 21 times the difference of each X7's W3 and each X2's W9. The number of each X2's W9 equals 9. The number of each X2's W3 equals each X7's W3. The number of each X7's W3 equals 8. How many WWW does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["X7's W3 as u. So u = 8.\nDefine each X2's W3 as S. So S = u = 8.\nDefine each X2's W9 as A. So A = 9.\nDefine each X2's W8 as i. So i = 21 * u - A = 21 * 8 - 9 = 11.\nDefine each X2's WWW as Y. So Y = S + A + i = 8 + 9 + 11 = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 279, "question": "The number of each X9's W7 equals 14. The number of each Y8's X1 equals 1 times the difference of each X1's WWW and each X9's W7. The number of each Z3's Y8 equals 15 times the sum of each X1's W3, each X1's WWW and each Y8's WWW. The number of each X1's W3 equals 18 more than each X9's W7. How many Y8 does each Z3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["X9's W7 = 14.\nDefine each X1's W3 as u. So u = 18 * X9's W7 = 18 * 14 = 22.\nDefine each X1's WWW as S. So S = u = 22.\nDefine each Y8's X1 as A. So A = 1 * S - X9's W7 = 1 * 22 - 14 = 8.\nDefine each Y8's WWW as i. So i = A * S = 8 * 22 = 15.\nDefine each Z3's Y8 as Y. So Y = 15 + (u + S + i) = 15 + (22 + 22 + 15) = 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 280, "question": "The number of each Y4's X5 equals 10. How many X5 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Y4's X5 = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 281, "question": "The number of each X5's W5 equals each Y5's WWW. The number of each Y5's X2 equals 3 times each X2's WWW. The number of each X2's W6 equals 20. The number of each X5's W6 equals 2 times the difference of each X2's W6 and each Y5's WWW. How many WWW does each X5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["X2's W6 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each X2's WWW as S. So S = u = 20.\nDefine each Y5's X2 as A. So A = 3 * S = 3 * 20 = 14.\nDefine each Y5's WWW as i. So i = A * S = 14 * 20 = 4.\nDefine each X5's W6 as Y. So Y = 2 * u - i = 2 * 20 - 4 = 13.\nDefine each X5's W5 as F. So F = i = 4.\nDefine each X5's WWW as r. So r = F + Y = 4 + 13 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 282, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y3 equals 1 times each Y3's X1. The number of each Y3's X1 equals 7. How many YYY does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["Y3's X1 as u. So u = 7.\nDefine each Z0's Y3 as S. So S = 1 * u = 1 * 7 = 7.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as A. So A = S = 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 283, "question": "The number of each X6's W5 equals each X3's WWW. The number of each X3's W3 equals 15. The number of each Y2's X3 equals 12. The number of each X3's W6 equals each Y2's X3. How many W5 does each X6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["Y2's X3 = 12. X3's W6 as u. So u = Y2's X3 = 12.\nDefine each X3's W3 as S. So S = 15.\nDefine each X3's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 15 + 12 = 4.\nDefine each X6's W5 as i. So i = A = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 284, "question": "The number of each Y2's X8 equals 2. The number of each Z8's Y8 equals each Y2's XXX. The number of each Z0's Y8 equals the sum of each Y2's X4, each Z0's Y2 and each Z8's Y8. The number of each Y2's X4 equals 14 times each Y2's X8. The number of each Z0's Y2 equals 5 times each Y2's X8. The number of each Z0's Y7 equals the sum of each Z8's Y8, each Y2's X8 and each Y2's X4. How many YYY does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y2's X8 as u. So u = 2.\nDefine each Y2's X4 as S. So S = 14 * u = 14 * 2 = 5.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 5 + 2 = 7.\nDefine each Z8's Y8 as i. So i = A = 7.\nDefine each Z0's Y7 as Y. So Y = (i + u + S) = (7 + 2 + 5) = 14.\nDefine each Z0's Y2 as F. So F = 5 * u = 5 * 2 = 10.\nDefine each Z0's Y8 as r. So r = (S + F + i) = (5 + 10 + 7) = 22.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as l. So l = r + Y + F = 22 + 14 + 10 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 285, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y7 equals each Y7's WWW. The number of each Y7's X5 equals 18. The number of each X5's W8 equals 2 more than each Y7's X5. How many WWW does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["Y7's X5 as u. So u = 18.\nDefine each X5's W8 as S. So S = 2 * u = 2 * 18 = 13.\nDefine each X5's WWW as A. So A = S = 13.\nDefine each Y7's WWW as i. So i = u * A = 18 * 13 = 4.\nDefine each Z7's Y7 as Y. So Y = i = 4.\nDefine each Z7's WWW as F. So F = Y * i = 4 * 4 = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 286, "question": "The number of each Y5's X5 equals 4. How many X5 does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["Y5's X5 = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 287, "question": "The number of each Y3's X7 equals 15 times each X7's WWW. The number of each X0's W9 equals 0. The number of each Y4's X8 equals 14 times each X0's W9. The number of each X7's W9 equals 0 times each Y4's X8. The number of each X8's W6 equals each Y3's WWW. How many WWW does each X8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["X0's W9 = 0. Y4's X8 = 14 * X0's W9 = 14.\nDefine each X7's W9 as u. So u = 0 * Y4's X8 = 0 * 14 = 0.\nDefine each X7's WWW as S. So S = u = 0.\nDefine each Y3's X7 as A. So A = 15 * S = 15 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as i. So i = A * S = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X8's W6 as Y. So Y = i = 0.\nDefine each X8's WWW as F. So F = Y = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 288, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y9 equals 14 more than each Z3's Y2. The number of each Z3's Y5 equals 4 more than each Z3's Y9. The number of each Z3's Y0 equals 4 more than each Z3's Y9. The number of each Z3's Y2 equals 5. The number of each Z6's Y5 equals 12 more than each Z3's YYY. How many Y5 does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["Z3's Y2 as u. So u = 5.\nDefine each Z3's Y9 as S. So S = 14 * u = 14 * 5 = 1.\nDefine each Z3's Y5 as A. So A = 4 * S = 4 * 1 = 4.\nDefine each Z3's Y0 as i. So i = 4 * S = 4 * 1 = 4.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as Y. So Y = S + A + i + u = 1 + 4 + 4 + 5 = 14.\nDefine each Z6's Y5 as F. So F = 12 * Y = 12 * 14 = 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 289, "question": "The number of each Y1's X0 equals 16 times each Z0's YYY. The number of each Z0's Y1 equals 16. How many XXX does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Z0's Y1 as u. So u = 16.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as S. So S = u = 16.\nDefine each Y1's X0 as A. So A = 16 * S = 16 * 16 = 3.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as i. So i = A = 3.\nDefine each Z0's XXX as Y. So Y = u * i = 16 * 3 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 290, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y3 equals 8 more than each Z0's Y0. The number of each Z0's Y5 equals 12 times each Z0's Y0. The number of each X0's W0 equals the difference of each Z0's YYY and each Z0's Y5. The number of each Z0's Y0 equals 1. How many W0 does each X0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Z0's Y0 as u. So u = 1.\nDefine each Z0's Y5 as S. So S = 12 * u = 12 * 1 = 12.\nDefine each Z0's Y3 as A. So A = 8 * u = 8 * 1 = 8.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as i. So i = S + A + u = 12 + 8 + 1 = 21.\nDefine each X0's W0 as Y. So Y = i - S = 21 - 12 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 291, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y8 equals the difference of each Y6's X9 and each Z2's Y6. The number of each Z0's Y5 equals 9 more than the difference of each Z6's YYY and each Z6's Y5. The number of each Z6's Y5 equals each Y6's X9. The number of each Y6's X9 equals 14 times the difference of each Z2's Y6 and each Y9's X7. The number of each Y9's X7 equals 3 times the sum of each Z9's Y5 and each Z2's Y6. The number of each Z2's Y6 equals 8. The number of each Z9's Y5 equals each Z2's Y6. The number of each Y5's X7 equals 11 more than the sum of each Z6's YYY, each Y9's X7 and each Z6's Y8. How many XXX does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Z2's Y6 as u. So u = 8.\nDefine each Z9's Y5 as S. So S = u = 8.\nDefine each Y9's X7 as A. So A = 3 * S + u = 3 * 8 + 8 = 9.\nDefine each Y6's X9 as i. So i = 14 * u - A = 14 * 8 - 9 = 11.\nDefine each Z6's Y5 as Y. So Y = i = 11.\nDefine each Z6's Y8 as F. So F = i - u = 11 - 8 = 3.\nDefine each Z6's YYY as r. So r = F + Y = 3 + 11 = 14.\nDefine each Y5's X7 as l. So l = 11 * (r + A + F) = 11 * (14 + 9 + 3) = 19.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as V. So V = l = 19.\nDefine each Z0's Y5 as q. So q = 9 + r - Y = 9 + 14 - 11 = 12.\nDefine each Z0's XXX as z. So z = q * V = 12 * 19 = 21.\nThus, the answer is 21."], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 292, "question": "The number of each Y8's X5 equals 20. The number of each X7's W4 equals 7 times each Y8's X5. The number of each Y3's X7 equals the difference of each X7's WWW and each X7's W4. The number of each Z2's Y2 equals the sum of each X7's W4 and each Y3's WWW. How many Y2 does each Z2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Y8's X5 = 20. Y3's X7 = X7's W4 - u = 7 - 20 = 10.\nDefine each X7's W4 as u. So u = 7 * Y8's X5 = 7 * 20 = 2.\nDefine each X7's WWW as S. So S = u = 2.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as A. So A = Y3's X7 * S = 10 * 2 = 20.\nDefine each Z2's Y2 as i. So i = u + A = 2 + 20 = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 293, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y4 equals 10 times each Z3's Y8. The number of each Z3's Y0 equals 1 times each Z8's Y0. The number of each Z8's Y0 equals 10. The number of each X3's W2 equals the difference of each Z3's Y0 and each Z3's YYY. The number of each X3's W0 equals 1 more than the difference of each Z3's Y8 and each Z3's YYY. The number of each Z3's Y8 equals 21 times each Z8's Y0. How many WWW does each X3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Z8's Y0 = 10. Z3's Y8 as u. So u = 21 * S = 21 * 10 = 3.\nDefine each Z3's Y4 as S. So S = 10 * u = 10 * 3 = 7.\nDefine each Z3's Y0 as A. So A = 1 * S = 1 * 7 = 7.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as i. So i = S + A + u = 7 + 7 + 3 = 17.\nDefine each X3's W0 as Y. So Y = 1 * u - i = 1 * 3 - 17 = 9.\nDefine each X3's W2 as F. So F = A - i = 7 - 17 = 13.\nDefine each X3's WWW as r. So r = Y + F = 9 + 13 = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 294, "question": "The number of each X8's W6 equals 6. The number of each X7's W4 equals 8 times the sum of each X8's WWW and each X8's W6. How many W4 does each X7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["X8's W6 as u. So u = 6.\nDefine each X8's WWW as S. So S = u = 6.\nDefine each X7's W4 as A. So A = 8 * S + u = 8 * 6 + 6 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 295, "question": "The number of each Y2's X9 equals 2 times each X9's WWW. The number of each X9's W4 equals 19 more than each X5's W3. The number of each Z8's Y8 equals 16 more than each Y2's WWW. The number of each X5's W3 equals 10. How many Y8 does each Z8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["X5's W3 = 10. X9's W4 as u. So u = 19 * X5's W3 = 19 * 10 = 6.\nDefine each X9's WWW as S. So S = u = 6.\nDefine each Y2's X9 as A. So A = 2 * S = 2 * 6 = 12.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as i. So i = A * S = 12 * 6 = 3.\nDefine each Z8's Y8 as Y. So Y = 16 * i = 16 * 3 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 296, "question": "The number of each Y3's X0 equals 9. The number of each Y4's X3 equals 9 times each Y7's X0. The number of each Y9's X3 equals 19 more than each Y4's XXX. The number of each Y4's X0 equals 11. The number of each Y7's X0 equals each Y3's X0. How many X3 does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Y3's X0 = 9. Y7's X0 = u = 9.\nDefine each Y4's X0 as S. So S = 11.\nDefine each Y4's X3 as A. So A = 9 * Y7's X0 = 9.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as i. So i = S + A = 11 + 9 = 20.\nDefine each Y9's X3 as Y. So Y = 19 * i = 19 * 20 = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 297, "question": "The number of each X9's W3 equals 4. How many W3 does each X9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["X9's W3 = 4. So 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 298, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y8 equals the difference of each Z2's XXX and each Z2's Y8. The number of each Y8's X3 equals 6 more than each Z2's Y8. The number of each Z2's Y8 equals 16. How many XXX does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["Z2's Y8 as u. So u = 16.\nDefine each Y8's X3 as S. So S = 6 * u = 6 * 16 = 4.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as A. So A = S = 4.\nDefine each Z2's XXX as i. So i = u * A = 16 * 4 = 18.\nDefine each Z9's Y8 as Y. So Y = i - u = 18 - 16 = 2.\nDefine each Z9's XXX as F. So F = Y * A = 2 * 4 = 8.\nThus, the answer is 8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 299, "question": "The number of each X2's W6 equals 6 times the sum of each X7's WWW, each X7's W8 and each X7's W6. The number of each X7's W8 equals 2 more than each X7's W6. The number of each X7's W6 equals 3. How many W6 does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["X7's W6 as u. So u = 3.\nDefine each X7's W8 as S. So S = 2 * u = 2 * 3 = 6.\nDefine each X7's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 6 + 3 = 9.\nDefine each X2's W6 as i. So i = 6 * (A + S + u) = 6 * (9 + 6 + 3) = 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 300, "question": "The number of each X4's W0 equals 8. The number of each Y6's X8 equals 18 times each X4's W0. How many X8 does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["X4's W0 = 8. Y6's X8 = 18 * X4's W0 = 18 * 8 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 301, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y8 equals the sum of each Z5's Y8 and each Z4's YYY. The number of each Z4's Y8 equals each Y8's X5. The number of each Z4's Y1 equals 3 more than each Z4's Y8. The number of each Y1's X5 equals each Z0's YYY. The number of each Z0's Y1 equals each Z7's YYY. The number of each Y8's X5 equals 21 times each Z5's Y8. The number of each Y1's X6 equals 3. The number of each Z7's Y1 equals each Y8's X5. The number of each Y1's X1 equals 22. The number of each Z5's Y8 equals 6. The number of each Z4's Y5 equals 6. The number of each Z0's Y8 equals 21 more than each Z7's Y1. How many XXX does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["Z5's Y8 = 6. Y8's X5 as u. So u = 21 * Z5's Y8 = 21 * 6 = 11.\nDefine each Z4's Y8 as S. So S = u = 11.\nDefine each Z4's Y5 as A. So A = 6.\nDefine each Z4's Y1 as i. So i = 3 + S = 3 + 11 = 14.\nDefine each Z4's YYY as Y. So Y = S + A + i = 11 + 6 + 14 = 8.\nDefine each Z7's Y8 as F. So F = the Z5's Y8 + Y = 6 + 8 = 14.\nDefine each Z7's Y1 as r. So r = u = 11.\nDefine each Z7's YYY as l. So l = r + F = 11 + 14 = 2.\nDefine each Z0's Y1 as V. So V = l = 2.\nDefine each Z0's Y8 as q. So q = 21 * r = 21 * 11 = 1.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as z. So z = q + V = 1 + 2 = 3.\nDefine each Y1's X5 as A. So A = S = 11.\nDefine each Y1's X6 as i. So i = 3.\nDefine each Y1's X1 as Y. So Y = 22.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as F. So F = Y + A + i = 22 + 11 + 3 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 302, "question": "The number of each Y3's X5 equals 22 times each Y4's XXX. The number of each Y4's X5 equals 17 times each Y3's X6. The number of each Y4's X4 equals 3 more than each Y4's X5. The number of each Y3's X6 equals 17. The number of each Y4's X6 equals 14 times each Y3's X6. How many X5 does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["Y3's X6 as u. So u = 17.\nDefine each Y4's X5 as S. So S = 17 * u = 17 * 17 = 13.\nDefine each Y4's X6 as A. So A = 14 * u = 14 * 17 = 8.\nDefine each Y4's X4 as i. So i = 3 * S = 3 * 13 = 16.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as Y. So Y = S + A + i = 13 + 8 + 16 = 14.\nDefine each Y3's X5 as F. So F = 22 * Y = 22 * 14 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 303, "question": "The number of each Y3's X1 equals 2 times each Y3's X7. The number of each Y3's X7 equals 2. The number of each Z0's Y3 equals 11 times each Y3's X7. How many XXX does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["Y3's X7 as u. So u = 2.\nDefine each Y3's X1 as S. So S = 2 * u = 2 * 2 = 4.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 4 + 2 = 6.\nDefine each Z0's Y3 as i. So i = 11 * u = 11 * 2 = 22.\nDefine each Z0's XXX as Y. So Y = i * A = 22 * 6 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 304, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y0 equals 14. How many Y0 does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Z9's Y0 = 14. So 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 305, "question": "The number of each Y9's X3 equals 20 times each Z0's Y7. The number of each Y0's X0 equals 9 more than the sum of each Z4's YYY and each Z4's Y0. The number of each Z4's Y7 equals 18. The number of each Z4's Y9 equals 11. The number of each Y0's X3 equals the difference of each Z4's Y9 and each Z4's Y0. The number of each Z4's Y0 equals 20 times each Z4's Y9. The number of each Z0's Y7 equals 10 times each Y0's XXX. How many X3 does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["Y0's X3 as u. So u = Z4's Y9 - Z4's Y0 = 11 - 20 = 14.\nDefine each Z4's Y7 as S. So S = 18.\nDefine each Z4's Y9 as A. So A = 11.\nDefine each Z4's Y0 as i. So i = 20 * A = 20 * 11 = 13.\nDefine each Z4's YYY as Y. So Y = S + A + i = 18 + 11 + 13 = 19.\nDefine each Y0's X0 as F. So F = 9 * Y + i = 9 * 19 + 13 = 19.\nDefine each Y0's X3 as r. So r = A - i = 11 - 13 = 21.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as l. So l = r + F = 21 + 19 = 17.\nDefine each Z0's Y7 as V. So V = 10 * l = 10 * 17 = 9.\nDefine each Y9's X3 as q. So q = 20 * V = 20 * 9 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 306, "question": "The number of each Y6's X4 equals each Y8's X4. The number of each Y2's X6 equals 10 times each Z1's YYY. The number of each Y2's X3 equals 10 more than each Z1's YYY. The number of each X4's W5 equals the difference of each X4's W4 and each Y2's XXX. The number of each X4's W4 equals 17 more than each Y2's XXX. The number of each X4's W9 equals the sum of each Y2's X3 and each Y6's X4. The number of each Z1's Y2 equals 15. The number of each Y8's X4 equals the difference of each Y2's X4 and each Z1's XXX. The number of each Y2's X4 equals the sum of each Y2's X6 and each Z1's Y2. The number of each X3's W0 equals 18 times each X4's WWW. How many W0 does each X3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Z1's Y2 as u. So u = 15.\nDefine each Z1's YYY as S. So S = u = 15.\nDefine each Y2's X6 as A. So A = 10 * S = 10 * 15 = 12.\nDefine each Y2's X4 as i. So i = A + u = 12 + 15 = 4.\nDefine each Y2's X3 as Y. So Y = 10 * S = 10 * 15 = 12.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as F. So F = Y + A + i = 12 + 12 + 4 = 5.\nDefine each Z1's XXX as r. So r = u * F = 15 * 5 = 6.\nDefine each Y8's X4 as l. So l = i - r = 4 - 6 = 21.\nDefine each Y6's X4 as V. So V = l = 21.\nDefine each X4's W9 as q. So q = Y + V = 12 + 21 = 10.\nDefine each X4's W4 as z. So z = 17 * F = 17 * 5 = 16.\nDefine each X4's W5 as A. So A = Z - F = 16 - 5 = 11.\nDefine each X4's WWW as i. So i = A + q + Z = 11 + 10 + 16 = 14.\nDefine each X3's W0 as Y. So Y = 18 * i = 18 * 14 = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 307, "question": "The number of each Z4's Y5 equals 2 times the difference of each Y8's X9 and each Y2's X9. The number of each Y2's X9 equals 22. The number of each Y8's X9 equals 15 times each Z3's YYY. The number of each Z3's Y2 equals 3 more than each Y2's X9. How many Y5 does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Y2's X9 = 22. Z3's Y2 = 3 * Y2's X9 = 3 * 22 = 20.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as u. So u = Z3's Y2 = 20.\nDefine each Y8's X9 as S. So S = 15 * u = 15 * 20 = 1.\nDefine each Z4's Y5 as A. So A = 2 * S - Y2's X9 = 2 * 1 - 22 = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 308, "question": "The number of each Y1's X7 equals each Z1's Y1. The number of each Z8's Y1 equals 7. The number of each Z1's Y1 equals 10. The number of each Z8's Y7 equals each Y1's X7. How many YYY does each Z8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["Z1's Y1 as u. So u = 10.\nDefine each Y1's X7 as S. So S = u = 10.\nDefine each Z8's Y7 as A. So A = S = 10.\nDefine each Z8's Y1 as i. So i = 7.\nDefine each Z8's YYY as Y. So Y = i + A = 7 + 10 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 309, "question": "The number of each Y6's X8 equals 5. How many X8 does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Y6's X8 = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 310, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y5 equals the sum of each Z7's Y4, each Z7's Y7 and each Z7's Y5. The number of each Z3's Y7 equals 2. The number of each Z0's Y4 equals 20 times each Z0's Y5. The number of each Z7's Y7 equals 11 times each Z0's YYY. The number of each Z3's Y4 equals 18. The number of each Z7's Y4 equals 9. The number of each Z0's Y5 equals 15 more than the difference of each Z7's Y4 and each Z7's Y5. The number of each Z7's Y5 equals 7 more than each Z7's Y4. The number of each Z0's Y7 equals 11 more than each Z7's Y5. How many YYY does each Z3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["7 + Z7's Y4 as u. So u = 9.\nDefine each Z7's Y5 as S. So S = 7 * u = 7 * 9 = 17.\nDefine each Z0's Y5 as A. So A = 15 * u - S = 15 * 9 - 17 = 19.\nDefine each Z0's Y4 as i. So i = 20 * A = 20 * 19 = 12.\nDefine each Z0's Y7 as Y. So Y = 11 * S = 11 * 17 = 3.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as F. So F = Y + A + i = 3 + 19 + 12 = 11.\nDefine each Z7's Y7 as r. So r = 11 * F = 11 * 11 = 6.\nDefine each Z3's Y5 as l. So l = (u + r + S) = (9 + 6 + 17) = 9.\nDefine each Z3's Y4 as V. So V = 18.\nDefine each Z3's Y7 as q. So q = 2.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as z. So z = q + V + l = 2 + 18 + 9 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 311, "question": "The number of each X4's W0 equals 13 more than each Y9's X4. The number of each Y9's X4 equals 17. The number of each X4's W1 equals each X4's W0. How many WWW does each X4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Y9's X4 = 17. X4's W0 = 13 * Y9's X4 = 13 * 17 = 14.\nDefine each X4's W1 as u. So u = X4's W0 = 14.\nDefine each X4's WWW as S. So S = u + X4's W0 = 14 + 14 = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 312, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y3 equals 10. The number of each Z5's Y7 equals each Z6's Y3. How many Y7 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Z6's Y3 = 10. Z5's Y7 = 10.\nDefine each Z6's Y3 as u. So u = 10.\nDefine each Z5's Y7 as S. So S = u = 10.\nDefine each Z6's Y3 as A. So A = 10.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as i. So i = S + u = 10 + 10 = 20.\nDefine each Z6's Y3 as Y. So Y = 10.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as F. So F = S + u = 10 + 10 = 20.\nDefine each Z6's Y3 as r. So r = 10.\nDefine each Z5's Y7 as l. So l = r = 10.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as V. So V = l + S + u = 10 + 10 + 10 = 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 313, "question": "The number of each X1's W7 equals 9 more than each Y6's WWW. The number of each Y8's X4 equals each X4's WWW. The number of each Y6's X5 equals 20. The number of each X5's W5 equals 0. The number of each X4's W3 equals 1 more than the difference of each X1's WWW and each X1's W7. How many WWW does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Y6's X5 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each X5's W5 as S. So S = 0.\nDefine each X5's WWW as A. So A = S = 0.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as i. So i = u * A = 20 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X1's W7 as Y. So Y = 9 * i = 9 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X1's WWW as F. So F = Y = 0.\nDefine each X4's W3 as r. So r = 1 * F - Y = 1 * 0 - 0 = 0.\nDefine each X4's WWW as l. So l = r = 0.\nDefine each Y8's X4 as V. So V = l = 0.\nDefine each Y8's WWW as q. So q = V * l = 0 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 314, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y5 equals 7. How many YYY does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["Z7's Y5 = 7. So 7.\nDefine each Z7's YYY as u. So u = Z7's YYY = 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 315, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y2 equals the sum of each Y2's X3 and each Y5's XXX. The number of each Z9's Y4 equals 13 times each Y4's X1. The number of each Y2's X3 equals 14 more than each Y5's XXX. The number of each Z6's Y5 equals each Z3's Y2. The number of each Y5's X3 equals the difference of each Y5's X1 and each Z9's Y4. The number of each Y4's X1 equals 10. The number of each Y5's X1 equals each Z9's Y4. The number of each Y2's X0 equals the difference of each Z6's Y5 and each Y5's X3. How many X0 does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["Y4's X1 = 10. Z9's Y4 = 13 + Y4's X1 = 13 + 10 = 0.\nDefine each Y5's X1 as u. So u = Z9's Y4 = 0.\nDefine each Y5's X3 as S. So S = u - Z9's Y4 = 0 - 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y2's X3 as i. So i = 14 * A = 14 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z3's Y2 as Y. So Y = i + A = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z6's Y5 as F. So F = Y = 0.\nDefine each Y2's X0 as r. So r = F - S = 0 - 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 316, "question": "The number of each Y9's X3 equals 9 times the difference of each Z1's Y2 and each Z1's Y9. The number of each Z1's Y6 equals 17. The number of each Z1's Y2 equals 19 times the difference of each Z1's Y6 and each Z1's Y9. The number of each Y9's X7 equals the difference of each Z1's YYY and each Z1's Y9. The number of each Z1's Y9 equals 17. How many XXX does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Z1's Y9 as u. So u = 17.\nDefine each Z1's Y6 as S. So S = 17.\nDefine each Z1's Y2 as A. So A = 19 * S - u = 19 * 17 - 17 = 1.\nDefine each Z1's YYY as i. So i = S + A + u = 17 + 1 + 17 = 12.\nDefine each Y9's X7 as Y. So Y = i - u = 12 - 17 = 18.\nDefine each Y9's X3 as F. So F = 9 * A - u = 9 * 1 - 17 = 15.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as r. So r = Y + F = 18 + 15 = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 317, "question": "The number of each X0's W5 equals 3. How many W5 does each X0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["X0's W5 = 3. So 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 318, "question": "The number of each X4's W5 equals 2 more than the difference of each X1's W5 and each X1's WWW. The number of each X2's W1 equals 19 more than the sum of each X1's WWW, each X1's W5 and each X4's W5. The number of each X1's W5 equals 20. How many W1 does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["X1's W5 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each X1's WWW as S. So S = u = 20.\nDefine each X4's W5 as A. So A = 2 * u - S = 2 * 20 - 20 = 20.\nDefine each X2's W1 as i. So i = 19 * (S + u + A) = 19 * (20 + 20 + 20) = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 319, "question": "The number of each Y4's X8 equals 5 more than each X8's W3. The number of each Y3's X5 equals the sum of each Y4's WWW and each Y4's X4. The number of each X8's W3 equals each X4's W9. The number of each X5's W0 equals 20. The number of each X4's W9 equals 13 more than each X5's W0. The number of each X4's W0 equals 18 more than the sum of each X8's W3 and each X4's W9. The number of each X8's W0 equals 9 times each X5's W0. The number of each Y4's X4 equals 6 more than the difference of each X4's W9 and each X4's WWW. How many XXX does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["X5's W0 = 20. X4's W9 as u. So u = 13 * X5's W0 = 13 * 20 = 7.\nDefine each X8's W3 as S. So S = u = 7.\nDefine each X4's W0 as A. So A = 18 * S + u = 18 * 7 + 7 = 18.\nDefine each X4's WWW as i. So i = A + u = 18 + 7 = 2.\nDefine each Y4's X4 as Y. So Y = 6 * u - i = 6 * 7 - 2 = 19.\nDefine each Y4's X8 as F. So F = 5 + S = 5 + 7 = 12.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as r. So r = Y + F = 19 + 12 = 8.\nDefine each Y3's X5 as l. So l = r + Y = 8 + 19 = 4.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as V. So V = l = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 320, "question": "The number of each Y7's X1 equals 12. How many X1 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["Y7's X1 = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 321, "question": "The number of each Y8's X4 equals 17. The number of each Y8's X5 equals 0. The number of each Y8's X1 equals 10 more than the difference of each Y8's X5 and each Y8's X4. How many XXX does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Y8's X5 as u. So u = 0.\nDefine each Y8's X4 as S. So S = 17.\nDefine each Y8's X1 as A. So A = 10 * u - S = 10 * 0 - 17 = 6.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as i. So i = S + A + u = 17 + 6 + 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 322, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y5 equals 7. How many Y5 does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["Z1's Y5 = 7. So 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 323, "question": "The number of each X5's W1 equals 20. The number of each Z0's Y6 equals each Z8's WWW. The number of each Y6's X5 equals each Y0's X4. The number of each Y0's X4 equals the sum of each X5's W1 and each X5's WWW. The number of each Z8's Y6 equals 21 more than the sum of each X5's W1 and each Y6's X5. How many WWW does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["X5's W1 = 20. X5's WWW = 20. X5's WWW = 20. X5's WWW = 20. X5's WWW = 20. X5's WWW = 20. X5's WWW = 20. X5's WWW = 20. X5's WWW = 20. X5's WWW = 20. X5's WWW = 20. X5's WWW = 20. X5's WWW = 20. X5's WWW = 20. X5's WWW = 20. X5's WWW = 20. X5's WWW = 20. X5's WWW = 20. X5's WWW = 20. X5's W1 as u. So u = 20. X5's WWW as S. So S = u = 20. X5's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 20 + 20 = 17. X5's WWW as i. So i = S + u + A = 17 + 20 + 17 = 8.\nDefine each Y0's X4 as Y. So Y = u + i = 20 + 8 = 5.\nDefine each Y6's X5 as F. So F = Y = 5.\nDefine each Z8's Y6 as r. So r = 21 * u + F = 21 * 20 + 5 = 11.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as l. So l = F * i = 5 * 8 = 17.\nDefine each Z8's WWW as V. So V = r * l = 11 * 17 = 3.\nDefine each Z0's Y6 as q. So q = V = 3.\nDefine each Z0's WWW as z. So z = q * l = 3 * 17 = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 324, "question": "The number of each Y4's X8 equals 15 more than the sum of each Y9's X8, each Y9's XXX and each Y4's X9. The number of each Y9's X8 equals 8. The number of each Y4's X9 equals 4 times the difference of each Y9's XXX and each Y9's X8. How many XXX does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["Y9's X8 as u. So u = 8.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as S. So S = u = 8.\nDefine each Y4's X9 as A. So A = 4 * S - u = 4 * 8 - 8 = 1.\nDefine each Y4's X8 as i. So i = 15 * (u + S + A) = 15 * (8 + 8 + 1) = 19.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as Y. So Y = A + i = 1 + 19 = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 325, "question": "The number of each X2's W9 equals 18 more than the sum of each X0's WWW and each Y4's X0. The number of each Z0's Y4 equals the sum of each Y7's X2, each Z8's WWW and each Z8's Y7. The number of each Y4's X2 equals 20 times each X0's WWW. The number of each Y4's X0 equals 5 more than each Y4's X2. The number of each X0's W9 equals 5. The number of each Y7's X2 equals 9 times the difference of each X2's WWW and each X2's W9. The number of each X2's W0 equals each Y4's X0. The number of each Z8's Y7 equals 9 more than each Y7's X2. How many YYY does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["X0's W9 as u. So u = 5.\nDefine each X0's WWW as S. So S = u = 5.\nDefine each Y4's X2 as A. So A = 20 * S = 20 * 5 = 8.\nDefine each Y4's X0 as i. So i = 5 * A = 5 * 8 = 17.\nDefine each X2's W0 as Y. So Y = i = 17.\nDefine each X2's W9 as F. So F = 18 * S + i = 18 * 5 + 17 = 11.\nDefine each X2's WWW as r. So r = Y + F = 17 + 11 = 5.\nDefine each Y7's X2 as l. So l = 9 * r - F = 9 * 5 - 11 = 19.\nDefine each Y7's WWW as V. So V = l * r = 19 * 5 = 3.\nDefine each Z8's Y7 as q. So q = 9 + l = 9 + 19 = 5.\nDefine each Z8's WWW as z. So z = q * V = 5 * 3 = 15.\nDefine each Z0's Y4 as A. So A = (l + Z8's WWW + q) = (19 + 15 + 5) = 16.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as i. So i = A = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 326, "question": "The number of each X6's W4 equals each X9's W5. The number of each X6's W5 equals 19. The number of each X9's W5 equals 5 times each X6's W5. How many W4 does each X6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["X6's W5 as u. So u = 19.\nDefine each X9's W5 as S. So S = 5 * u = 5 * 19 = 3.\nDefine each X6's W4 as A. So A = S = 3.\nDefine each X6's WWW as i. So i = u + A = 19 + 3 = 22.\nDefine each Y1's X0 as Y. So Y = 23.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as F. So F = Y = 23.\nDefine each X3's W3 as r. So r = 3.\nDefine each X3's WWW as l. So l = r = 3.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as V. So V = Y = 23.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as A. So A = Y = 23.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as i. So i = Y + A = 23 + 23 = 13.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 327, "question": "The number of each Z2's Y8 equals 16 more than each Z2's Y5. The number of each Z9's Y5 equals 18 more than the sum of each Z2's Y8 and each Z2's YYY. The number of each Z2's Y5 equals 21. The number of each Z9's Y8 equals each Z9's Y5. How many Y8 does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["Z2's Y5 as u. So u = 21.\nDefine each Z2's Y8 as S. So S = 16 * u = 16 * 21 = 14.\nDefine each Z2's YYY as A. So A = S + u + u = 14 + 21 + 21 = 10.\nDefine each Z9's Y5 as i. So i = 18 * S + A = 18 * 14 + 10 = 19.\nDefine each Z9's Y8 as Y. So Y = i = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 328, "question": "The number of each Y1's X6 equals 13 times each Z7's Y2. The number of each Z7's Y2 equals each X6's W9. The number of each X6's W9 equals 19. How many XXX does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["X6's W9 = 19. So 19.\nDefine each Z7's Y2 as u. So u = X6's W9 = 19.\nDefine each Y1's X6 as S. So S = 13 * u = 13 * 19 = 17.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as A. So A = S = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 329, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y4 equals 5 more than each X7's WWW. The number of each Y2's X7 equals 21 more than the sum of each Z5's Y4 and each X7's W3. The number of each X7's W3 equals 20. The number of each Y2's X6 equals 18 times the sum of each X7's WWW and each Y2's X7. How many X6 does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["X7's W3 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each X7's WWW as S. So S = u = 20.\nDefine each Z5's Y4 as A. So A = 5 * S = 5 * 20 = 8.\nDefine each Y2's X7 as i. So i = 21 * A + u = 21 * 8 + 20 = 10.\nDefine each Y2's X6 as Y. So Y = 18 * S + i = 18 * 20 + 10 = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 330, "question": "The number of each X7's W6 equals 9. How many WWW does each X7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["X7's W6 = 9. X7's WWW = 9. X7's WWW = 9. X7's WWW = 9. X7's WWW = 9. X7's WWW = 9. X7's WWW = 9. X7's WWW = 9. X7's WWW = 9. X7's WWW = 9. X7's WWW = 9. X7's W6 as u. So u = 9. X7's WWW as S. So S = u = 9. X7's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 9 + 9 = 18. X7's WWW as i. So i = S + u = 18 + 9 = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 331, "question": "The number of each X5's W5 equals 0 times each Z2's YYY. The number of each Z4's Y2 equals 2 more than each Z2's WWW. The number of each Y9's X1 equals 3. The number of each Y2's X5 equals 8 times each X5's W5. The number of each Z2's Y2 equals 1 more than each Y9's X1. The number of each Y6's X6 equals 22 times each Z3's Y9. The number of each Z3's Y9 equals the sum of each Z4's WWW and each Y2's X5. How many X6 does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y9's X1 as u. So u = 3.\nDefine each Z2's Y2 as S. So S = 1 * u = 1 * 3 = 3.\nDefine each Z2's YYY as A. So A = S = 3.\nDefine each X5's W5 as i. So i = 0 * A = 0 * 3 = 0.\nDefine each X5's WWW as Y. So Y = i = 0.\nDefine each Y2's X5 as F. So F = 8 * i = 8 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as r. So r = F * Y = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z2's WWW as l. So l = S * r = 3 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z4's Y2 as V. So V = 2 * l = 2 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z4's WWW as q. So q = V * r = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z3's Y9 as z. So z = q + F = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y6's X6 as A. So A = 22 * S = 22 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 332, "question": "The number of each Y7's X6 equals 14 times the difference of each X6's W4 and each X6's WWW. The number of each Z6's Y7 equals 13 times the difference of each Y7's WWW and each X6's W4. The number of each X6's W4 equals 21. How many WWW does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["X6's W4 as u. So u = 21.\nDefine each X6's WWW as S. So S = u = 21.\nDefine each Y7's X6 as A. So A = 14 * u - S = 14 * 21 - 21 = 20.\nDefine each Y7's WWW as i. So i = A * S = 20 * 21 = 6.\nDefine each Z6's Y7 as Y. So Y = 13 + i - u = 13 + 6 - 21 = 21.\nDefine each Z6's WWW as F. So F = Y * i = 21 * 6 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 333, "question": "The number of each X8's W0 equals 3. The number of each X4's W5 equals 1 times each Y1's XXX. The number of each Y1's X9 equals 18 times each X8's W0. How many W5 does each X4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["X8's W0 = 3. Y1's X9 = 18 * X8 = 18 * 3 = 8.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as u. So u = Y1's X9 = 18.\nDefine each X4's W5 as S. So S = 1 * u = 1 * 18 = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 334, "question": "The number of each Y5's X2 equals 20 times each X2's W9. The number of each Y3's X2 equals the sum of each Y5's X2 and each X2's WWW. The number of each Z1's Y3 equals 18 times each Z5's WWW. The number of each Z5's Y5 equals 2 more than each X2's W9. The number of each X2's W9 equals 7. The number of each Z8's Y3 equals 7 more than each Z1's WWW. How many WWW does each Z8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["X2's W9 as u. So u = 7.\nDefine each X2's WWW as S. So S = u = 7.\nDefine each Y5's X2 as A. So A = 20 * u = 20 * 7 = 2.\nDefine each Y5's WWW as i. So i = A * S = 2 * 7 = 14.\nDefine each Z5's Y5 as Y. So Y = 2 * u = 2 * 7 = 14.\nDefine each Z5's WWW as F. So F = Y * i = 14 * 14 = 12.\nDefine each Z1's Y3 as r. So r = 18 + F = 18 + 12 = 7.\nDefine each Y3's X2 as l. So l = A + S = 2 + 7 = 9.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as V. So V = l * S = 9 * 7 = 17.\nDefine each Z1's WWW as q. So q = r * V = 7 * 17 = 4.\nDefine each Z8's Y3 as z. So z = 7 * q = 7 * 4 = 5.\nDefine each Z8's WWW as A. So A = z * V = 5 * 17 = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 335, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y7 equals 20. The number of each Z3's Y2 equals each Z3's Y7. The number of each Z3's Y9 equals 3 times each Z3's Y1. The number of each Z3's Y1 equals 22 more than each Z3's Y7. How many YYY does each Z3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Z3's Y7 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each Z3's Y1 as S. So S = 22 * u = 22 * 20 = 3.\nDefine each Z3's Y2 as A. So A = u = 20.\nDefine each Z3's Y9 as i. So i = 3 * S = 3 * 3 = 9.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as Y. So Y = S + A + u + i = 3 + 20 + 20 + 9 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 336, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y4 equals 9. The number of each Z9's Y4 equals 17 more than each Z7's Y4. How many Y4 does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["Z7's Y4 = 9. Z9's Y4 = 17 * Z7's Y4 = 17 * 9 = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 337, "question": "The number of each X1's W2 equals 20. The number of each X3's W6 equals 14 more than the difference of each X1's W6 and each X2's W5. The number of each X3's W5 equals 16 times each X1's WWW. The number of each X2's W2 equals 6. The number of each X1's W5 equals 10 more than each X2's W2. The number of each X3's W2 equals each X3's W5. The number of each X2's W5 equals each X3's W5. The number of each X1's W6 equals 12 more than each X2's W2. The number of each X2's W6 equals 12 times each X3's WWW. How many W6 does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["12 * X2's W2 = 13. X1's W5 as u. So u = 10 * X2's W2 = 10 * 13 = 15.\nDefine each X1's W2 as S. So S = 20.\nDefine each X1's W6 as A. So A = 12 * S = 12 * 20 = 10.\nDefine each X1's WWW as i. So i = S + A + u = 20 + 10 + 15 = 22.\nDefine each X3's W5 as Y. So Y = 16 * i = 16 * 22 = 7.\nDefine each X2's W5 as F. So F = Y = 7.\nDefine each X3's W6 as r. So r = 14 * A - F = 14 * 10 - 7 = 19.\nDefine each X3's W2 as l. So l = Y = 7.\nDefine each X3's WWW as V. So V = l + Y + r = 7 + 7 + 19 = 10.\nDefine each X2's W6 as q. So q = 12 * V = 12 * 10 = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 338, "question": "The number of each Y6's X7 equals 3 times each X7's W9. The number of each Y5's X7 equals 1 more than the sum of each Y6's X7 and each Y5's X5. The number of each X7's W9 equals 8. The number of each Y5's X5 equals 17 more than the sum of each Y6's X7 and each X7's W9. The number of each X5's W9 equals each Y5's XXX. How many W9 does each X5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["X7's W9 = 8. Y6's X7 = 3 * X7's W9 = 3 * 8 = 1.\nDefine each Y5's X5 as u. So u = 17 * A + X7's W9 = 17 * 8 + 8 = 6.\nDefine each Y5's X7 as S. So S = 1 * A + u = 1 * 8 + 6 = 14.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 14 + 6 = 20.\nDefine each X5's W9 as i. So i = A = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 339, "question": "The number of each X2's W1 equals 4 more than each X1's W1. The number of each X2's W7 equals 9 more than each X8's WWW. The number of each X1's W1 equals 14. The number of each X1's W4 equals 14 more than each X2's W7. The number of each X8's W7 equals 0 times each X2's W1. The number of each X4's W1 equals 10 more than each X1's W4. The number of each X4's W4 equals 2 times each X4's W1. How many WWW does each X4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["X1's W1 as u. So u = 14.\nDefine each X2's W1 as S. So S = 4 * u = 4 * 14 = 10.\nDefine each X8's W7 as A. So A = 0 * S = 0 * 10 = 0.\nDefine each X8's WWW as i. So i = A = 0.\nDefine each X2's W7 as Y. So Y = 9 * i = 9 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X1's W4 as F. So F = 14 * Y = 14 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X4's W1 as r. So r = 10 * F = 10 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X4's W4 as l. So l = 2 * r = 2 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X4's WWW as V. So V = l + r = 0 + 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 340, "question": "The number of each Z2's Y1 equals 13. The number of each X8's W8 equals 7 more than each Z2's Y1. How many W8 does each X8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Z2's Y1 = 13. X8's W8 = 7 * Z2's Y1 = 7 * 13 = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 341, "question": "The number of each Y1's X7 equals 4 times each Z2's Y8. The number of each Z2's Y8 equals 22. How many XXX does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Z2's Y8 as u. So u = 22.\nDefine each Y1's X7 as S. So S = 4 * u = 4 * 22 = 19.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as A. So A = S = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 342, "question": "The number of each Y1's X1 equals the difference of each Y5's X9 and each Y1's X9. The number of each Y1's X5 equals 13 times each Y5's X9. The number of each Y5's X9 equals 1. The number of each Y1's X9 equals the difference of each Y1's X5 and each Y5's X9. How many XXX does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Y5's X9 = 1. Y1's X5 as u. So u = 13 + Y5's X9 = 13 + 1 = 14.\nDefine each Y1's X9 as S. So S = u - Y5's X9 = 14 - 1 = 13.\nDefine each Y1's X1 as A. So A = Y5's X9 - S = 1 - 13 = 11.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as i. So i = S + A + u = 13 + 11 + 14 = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 343, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y3 equals 15. The number of each Y4's X2 equals 2 times each Z5's Y3. How many X2 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["Z5's Y3 = 15. Y4's X2 = 2 * Z5's Y3 = 2 * 15 = 7.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as u. So u = Z5's Y3 = 15.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as S. So S = Y4's X2 = 7.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as A. So A = i = 3.\nDefine each Z5's XXX as i. So i = Z5's Y3 * A = 15 * 3 = 22.\nDefine each X2's WWW as Y. So Y = S = 7.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as F. So F = i = 22.\nDefine each Z5's WWW as r. So r = Z5's Y3 * F = 15 * 22 = 8.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as l. So l = i = 22.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as V. So V = Z5's Y3 = 15.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as q. So q = Y = 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 344, "question": "The number of each Y9's X0 equals each Y9's X3. The number of each Y5's X3 equals 11. The number of each Y9's X3 equals 0 times the difference of each Y5's X3 and each Y6's X0. The number of each Y6's X0 equals each Y5's X3. How many X0 does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y5's X3 = 11. Y6's X0 = Y5's X3 = 11.\nDefine each Y6's X0 as u. So u = Y5's X3 = 11.\nDefine each Y9's X3 as S. So S = 0 * Y5's X3 - u = 0 * 11 - 11 = 12.\nDefine each Y9's X0 as A. So A = S = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 345, "question": "The number of each Y1's X7 equals each X9's W6. The number of each Y1's X9 equals 11 times each X9's WWW. The number of each Y5's X7 equals the sum of each Y8's WWW and each X9's WWW. The number of each Y5's X9 equals 10. The number of each X9's W6 equals each Y5's X9. The number of each X7's W2 equals 18 more than the difference of each X9's W6 and each Y5's X9. The number of each X7's W6 equals each Y5's X9. The number of each Y8's X7 equals 10 more than each Y1's WWW. The number of each Y8's X9 equals the difference of each Y1's X9 and each X9's WWW. How many X7 does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Y5's X9 = 10. X9's W6 = Y5's X9 = 10. X9's WWW as u. So u = u = 10.\nDefine each Y1's X9 as S. So S = 11 * u = 11 * 10 = 18.\nDefine each X7's W6 as A. So A = Y5's X9 = 10.\nDefine each X7's W2 as i. So i = 18 * u - Y5's X9 = 18 * 10 - 10 = 19.\nDefine each X7's WWW as Y. So Y = A + i = 10 + 19 = 6.\nDefine each Y1's X7 as F. So F = u = 10.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as r. So r = S * u + F * Y = 18 * 10 + 10 * 6 = 11.\nDefine each Y8's X7 as l. So l = 10 * r = 10 * 11 = 18.\nDefine each Y8's X9 as V. So V = S - u = 18 - 10 = 8.\nDefine each Y8's WWW as q. So q = V * u + l * Y = 8 * 10 + 18 * 6 = 19.\nDefine each Y5's X7 as z. So z = q + u = 19 + 10 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 346, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y8 equals 18. The number of each Z3's Y6 equals 21 more than each Z1's Y8. How many Y6 does each Z3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Z1's Y8 = 18. Z3's Y6 = 21 * Z1's Y8 = 21 * 18 = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 347, "question": "The number of each X9's W0 equals 5 times each X8's W1. The number of each X8's W4 equals each X8's W6. The number of each X9's W6 equals each X8's W0. The number of each X8's W1 equals 11 times each X0's W0. The number of each X0's W4 equals 0 times each X6's W0. The number of each X8's W6 equals 6 more than each X9's W6. The number of each X6's W0 equals 2. The number of each X8's W0 equals 12 more than each X9's W0. The number of each X0's W0 equals each X0's W4. How many W4 does each X8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["X6's W0 = 2.\nDefine each X0's W4 as u. So u = 0 * S = 0 * 2 = 0.\nDefine each X0's W0 as S. So S = u = 0.\nDefine each X8's W1 as A. So A = 11 * S = 11 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X9's W0 as i. So i = 5 * A = 5 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X8's W0 as Y. So Y = 12 * i = 12 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X9's W6 as F. So F = Y = 0.\nDefine each X8's W6 as r. So r = 6 * F = 6 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X8's W4 as l. So l = r = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 348, "question": "The number of each X4's W9 equals 11. The number of each Z6's Y7 equals 9 more than each Z4's XXX. The number of each Y8's X7 equals each Z4's Y8. The number of each Z4's Y8 equals 8 times each X4's W9. How many Y7 does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["X4's W9 = 11. Z4's Y8 as u. So u = 8 * X4's W9 = 8 * 11 = 19.\nDefine each Y8's X7 as S. So S = u = 19.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as A. So A = S = 19.\nDefine each Z4's XXX as i. So i = u * A = 19 * 19 = 16.\nDefine each Z6's Y7 as Y. So Y = 9 * i = 9 * 16 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 349, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y4 equals 8. The number of each Y1's X6 equals 13 more than the sum of each Z5's YYY and each Z5's Y1. The number of each Z5's Y1 equals 14 more than each Z3's YYY. The number of each Z3's Y1 equals 20. The number of each Y4's X8 equals each Z3's XXX. The number of each Y1's X5 equals 4 times the sum of each Z5's YYY and each Z5's Y1. How many XXX does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Z3's Y1 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as S. So S = u = 20.\nDefine each Z5's Y1 as A. So A = 14 * S = 14 * 20 = 4.\nDefine each Z5's Y4 as i. So i = 8.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as Y. So Y = i + A = 8 + 4 = 12.\nDefine each Y1's X6 as F. So F = 13 * Y + A = 13 * 12 + 4 = 20.\nDefine each Y1's X5 as r. So r = 4 * Y + A = 4 * 12 + 4 = 19.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as l. So l = r + F = 19 + 20 = 16.\nDefine each Z3's XXX as V. So V = u * l = 20 * 16 = 21.\nDefine each Y4's X8 as q. So q = V = 21.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as z. So z = q = 21.\nDefine each Z5's XXX as A. So A = i * Z + A * l = 8 * 21 + 4 * 16 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 350, "question": "The number of each Y8's X9 equals 1. The number of each Y0's X9 equals 4. The number of each Y8's X3 equals 11 more than the difference of each Y0's X3 and each Y8's X9. The number of each Z0's Y0 equals 10 more than the sum of each Y0's X9, each Z0's Y8 and each Y0's X3. The number of each Y0's X3 equals 22 times each Y8's X9. The number of each Z1's Y0 equals 2 times the difference of each Y8's XXX and each Z0's XXX. The number of each Z0's Y8 equals 18 times the sum of each Y8's XXX, each Y0's XXX and each Y8's X9. How many Y0 does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Y8's X9 as u. So u = 1.\nDefine each Y0's X3 as S. So S = 22 * u = 22 * 1 = 22.\nDefine each Y8's X3 as A. So A = 11 * S - u = 11 * 22 - 1 = 11.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as i. So i = A + u = 11 + 1 = 12.\nDefine each Y0's X9 as Y. So Y = 4.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as F. So F = Y + S = 4 + 22 = 3.\nDefine each Z0's Y8 as r. So r = 18 + (i + F + u) = 18 + (12 + 3 + 1) = 11.\nDefine each Z0's Y0 as l. So l = 10 * (Y + r + S) = 10 * (4 + 11 + 22) = 19.\nDefine each Z0's XXX as V. So V = l * F + r * i = 19 * 3 + 11 * 12 = 19.\nDefine each Z1's Y0 as q. So q = 2 * i - V = 2 * 12 - 19 = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 351, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y5 equals 2. How many YYY does each Z8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Z8's Y5 = 2. Z8's YYY = Z8.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 352, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y4 equals 22. How many Y4 does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["Z9's Y4 as u. So u = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 353, "question": "The number of each X4's W2 equals 2 more than each Z4's Y9. The number of each X3's W2 equals the sum of each X3's W4, each Y9's X0 and each Y9's X4. The number of each X3's W4 equals 2. The number of each Y6's X0 equals the sum of each Z5's Y9, each Z9's Y5 and each Y9's X4. The number of each Y9's X0 equals 2 times each Y9's X4. The number of each Z4's Y9 equals 17 more than the sum of each Y6's X0 and each Y9's X4. The number of each Y5's X3 equals 5 more than the sum of each Y6's X0, each X4's WWW and each Z4's Y9. The number of each Y9's X4 equals 9 more than each X3's W4. The number of each Z5's Y9 equals the sum of each Z9's Y5 and each X3's W4. The number of each Z9's Y5 equals each X3's W2. How many XXX does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["X3's W4 as u. So u = 2.\nDefine each Y9's X4 as S. So S = 9 * u = 9 * 2 = 18.\nDefine each Y9's X0 as A. So A = 2 * S = 2 * 18 = 13.\nDefine each X3's W2 as i. So i = (u + A + S) = (2 + 13 + 18) = 10.\nDefine each Z9's Y5 as Y. So Y = i = 10.\nDefine each Z5's Y9 as F. So F = Y + u = 10 + 2 = 12.\nDefine each Y6's X0 as r. So r = (F + Y + S) = (12 + 10 + 18) = 17.\nDefine each Z4's Y9 as l. So l = 17 * r + S = 17 * 17 + 18 = 19.\nDefine each X4's W2 as V. So V = 2 * l = 2 * 19 = 15.\nDefine each X4's WWW as q. So q = V = 15.\nDefine each Y5's X3 as z. So z = 5 * (r + q + l) = 5 * (17 + 15 + 19) = 19.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as A. So A = z = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 354, "question": "The number of each Z2's Y0 equals each Z2's Y2. The number of each Z2's Y2 equals the sum of each Y2's X6 and each Y2's XXX. The number of each Y2's X6 equals 11 times each Y0's X9. The number of each Y2's X9 equals 18 more than each Y0's X9. The number of each Y0's X9 equals 22. How many YYY does each Z2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["Y0's X9 as u. So u = 22.\nDefine each Y2's X9 as S. So S = 18 * u = 18 * 22 = 5.\nDefine each Y2's X6 as A. So A = 11 * u = 11 * 22 = 12.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as i. So i = S + A = 5 + 12 = 17.\nDefine each Z2's Y2 as Y. So Y = A + i = 12 + 17 = 6.\nDefine each Z2's Y0 as F. So F = Y = 6.\nDefine each Z2's YYY as r. So r = F + Y = 6 + 6 = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 355, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y6 equals 16. The number of each Y6's X4 equals the sum of each Y2's X4, each Y6's X3 and each Z9's Y2. The number of each Z1's Y6 equals 12 more than each Z9's XXX. The number of each Y6's X3 equals 22 times each Z1's Y6. The number of each Z9's Y2 equals 17 times each X4's W0. The number of each X4's W0 equals 2 times each Z6's Y6. The number of each Y2's X4 equals the sum of each Z6's Y6 and each X4's W0. How many X4 does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["Z6's Y6 = 16.\nDefine each X4's W0 as u. So u = 2 * Z6's Y6 = 2 * 16 = 9.\nDefine each Y2's X4 as S. So S = Z6's Y6 + u = 16 + 9 = 2.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as A. So A = S = 2.\nDefine each Z9's Y2 as i. So i = 17 * u = 17 * 9 = 15.\nDefine each Z9's XXX as Y. So Y = i * A = 15 * 2 = 7.\nDefine each Z1's Y6 as F. So F = 12 * Y = 12 * 7 = 15.\nDefine each Y6's X3 as r. So r = 22 * F = 22 * 15 = 8.\nDefine each Y6's X4 as l. So l = (S + r + i) = (2 + 8 + 15) = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 356, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y8 equals 13. How many Y8 does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["Z1's Y8 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 357, "question": "The number of each Y3's X4 equals the sum of each X8's W1 and each Y5's X1. The number of each Z2's Y5 equals 19. The number of each Y5's X1 equals 12 more than each X8's W1. The number of each X4's W1 equals each X8's W4. The number of each X8's W1 equals 1 more than each Z2's Y5. The number of each Y0's X4 equals 4 more than each X4's W1. The number of each X8's W4 equals 2 more than each Y3's X4. The number of each Z1's Y0 equals the sum of each Y0's X8 and each Y5's X1. The number of each Y0's X8 equals 10 more than each Y0's X4. How many XXX does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Y3's X4 + Y5's X1 = 12 + 12 = 1.\nDefine each X8's W4 as u. So u = 2 * Y3's X4 = 2 * 1 = 2.\nDefine each X4's W1 as S. So S = u = 2.\nDefine each Y0's X4 as A. So A = 4 * S = 4 * 2 = 8.\nDefine each Y0's X8 as i. So i = 10 * A = 10 * 8 = 11.\nDefine each Z1's Y0 as Y. So Y = i + u = 11 + 2 = 13.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as F. So F = A + i = 8 + 11 = 19.\nDefine each Z2's Y5 as r. So r = 19.\nDefine each X8's W1 as l. So l = 1 * r = 1 * 19 = 19.\nDefine each Y5's X1 as V. So V = 12 * l = 12 * 19 = 21.\nDefine each Y3's X4 as q. So q = l + V = 19 + 21 = 17.\nDefine each Z1's XXX as z. So z = Y * F = 13 * 19 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 358, "question": "The number of each X0's W0 equals 3. The number of each Y0's X0 equals 17 times each X0's WWW. The number of each Z8's Y9 equals 21 times each X9's WWW. The number of each Z2's Y9 equals each Z8's WWW. The number of each X9's W0 equals 1 times each Y0's X9. The number of each Y0's X9 equals 19 more than the sum of each X0's WWW and each Y0's X0. The number of each Y9's X9 equals 21 times each Y0's WWW. How many WWW does each Z2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["X0's W0 as u. So u = 3.\nDefine each X0's WWW as S. So S = u = 3.\nDefine each Y0's X0 as A. So A = 17 * S = 17 * 3 = 5.\nDefine each Y0's X9 as i. So i = 19 * S + A = 19 * 3 + 5 = 18.\nDefine each X9's W0 as Y. So Y = 1 * i = 1 * 18 = 18.\nDefine each X9's WWW as F. So F = Y = 18.\nDefine each Y0's WWW as r. So r = i * F + A * S = 18 * 18 + 5 * 3 = 19.\nDefine each Y9's X9 as l. So l = 21 * r = 21 * 19 = 8.\nDefine each Y9's WWW as V. So V = l * F = 8 * 18 = 6.\nDefine each Z8's Y9 as q. So q = 21 * F = 21 * 18 = 10.\nDefine each Z8's WWW as z. So z = q * V = 10 * 6 = 14.\nDefine each Z2's Y9 as A. So A = z = 14.\nDefine each Z2's WWW as i. So i = A * V = 14 * 6 = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 359, "question": "The number of each Z4's Y3 equals 20 times each Z6's Y6. The number of each Z2's Y8 equals 7 more than the sum of each Z6's Y6, each Z4's Y6 and each Z4's Y3. The number of each Z4's Y6 equals each Z4's Y3. The number of each Z6's Y6 equals 3. How many YYY does each Z2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Z6's Y6 as u. So u = 3.\nDefine each Z4's Y3 as S. So S = 20 * u = 20 * 3 = 14.\nDefine each Z4's Y6 as A. So A = S = 14.\nDefine each Z2's Y8 as i. So i = 7 * (u + A + S) = 7 * (3 + 14 + 14) = 19.\nDefine each Z2's YYY as Y. So Y = i = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 360, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y2 equals 10 more than each Z0's Y9. The number of each Z1's Y6 equals the difference of each Z0's Y2 and each Z1's Y9. The number of each Z0's Y6 equals 1 more than each Z0's Y2. The number of each Z1's Y2 equals 13 more than each Y9's X0. The number of each Y9's X0 equals 2. The number of each Y9's X7 equals 5 more than each Z1's Y2. The number of each Z1's Y9 equals the sum of each Y2's XXX and each Z1's Y2. The number of each Z2's Y2 equals each Z0's YYY. The number of each Z0's Y9 equals 13 more than each Y9's X7. The number of each Y6's X7 equals each Z0's Y2. The number of each Y2's X7 equals the sum of each Y6's XXX and each Z1's Y2. The number of each Y2's X0 equals the sum of each Y9's X0 and each Y9's X7. The number of each Y6's X0 equals 18 times each Z2's YYY. How many Y6 does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 361, "question": "The number of each Y6's X1 equals 6 times each Y6's X4. The number of each Y6's X4 equals 12. How many XXX does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Y6's X4 as u. So u = 12.\nDefine each Y6's X1 as S. So S = 6 * u = 6 * 12 = 3.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 3 + 12 = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 362, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y4 equals 15. The number of each Y3's X5 equals 8 times each Z5's YYY. The number of each Y4's X0 equals 5 more than each Y3's X5. The number of each Z5's Y6 equals 3. The number of each Z5's Y3 equals 20 more than each Z5's Y4. How many X0 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Z5's Y6 as u. So u = 3.\nDefine each Z5's Y4 as S. So S = 15.\nDefine each Z5's Y3 as A. So A = 20 * S = 20 * 15 = 1.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as i. So i = S + A + u = 15 + 1 + 3 = 19.\nDefine each Y3's X5 as Y. So Y = 8 * i = 8 * 19 = 14.\nDefine each Y4's X0 as F. So F = 5 * Y = 5 * 14 = 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 363, "question": "The number of each Y6's X7 equals each X7's WWW. The number of each X7's W6 equals 6. How many WWW does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["X7's W6 as u. So u = 6.\nDefine each X7's WWW as S. So S = u = 6.\nDefine each Y6's X7 as A. So A = S = 6.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as i. So i = A * S = 6 * 6 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 364, "question": "The number of each X4's W5 equals 6. How many WWW does each X4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["X4's W5 as u. So u = 6.\nDefine each X4's WWW as S. So S = u = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 365, "question": "The number of each X6's W7 equals 10 times each X6's W2. The number of each X6's W2 equals 17. The number of each X1's W2 equals 11 times the difference of each X6's W7 and each X6's W2. How many W2 does each X1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["X6's W2 = 17. X6's W7 = 10 * X6's W2 = 10.\nDefine each X6's W2 as u. So u = 17.\nDefine each X6's W7 as S. So S = 10 * u = 10 * 17 = 9.\nDefine each X1's W2 as A. So A = 11 * S - u = 11 * 9 - 17 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 366, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y9 equals 2. The number of each Z1's Y3 equals 15 more than the sum of each Z5's Y3, each Z5's Y8 and each Z1's Y9. The number of each Z1's Y9 equals 8 more than each Z5's Y8. The number of each Z5's Y8 equals 9 more than each Z5's Y3. The number of each Z3's Y3 equals 17. The number of each Z5's Y9 equals the sum of each Z5's Y8 and each Z1's Y3. The number of each Z3's Y8 equals 5 more than each Z5's Y9. The number of each Z5's Y3 equals 13. How many YYY does each Z3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["Z5's Y3 as u. So u = 13.\nDefine each Z5's Y8 as S. So S = 9 * u = 9 * 13 = 2.\nDefine each Z1's Y9 as A. So A = 8 * S = 8 * 2 = 16.\nDefine each Z1's Y3 as i. So i = 15 * (u + S + A) = 15 * (13 + 2 + 16) = 19.\nDefine each Z5's Y9 as Y. So Y = S + i = 2 + 19 = 21.\nDefine each Z3's Y8 as F. So F = 5 * Y = 5 * 21 = 13.\nDefine each Z3's Y3 as r. So r = 17.\nDefine each Z3's Y9 as l. So l = 2.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as V. So V = l + r + F = 2 + 17 + 13 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 367, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y8 equals 19 more than each Z2's YYY. The number of each Z0's Y7 equals 18. The number of each Z2's Y7 equals 1 more than each Z0's Y7. The number of each Z2's Y8 equals 8 times each Z2's Y7. How many Y8 does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Z0's Y7 as u. So u = 18.\nDefine each Z2's Y7 as S. So S = 1 * u = 1 * 18 = 18.\nDefine each Z2's Y8 as A. So A = 8 * S = 8 * 18 = 6.\nDefine each Z2's YYY as i. So i = S + A = 18 + 6 = 1.\nDefine each Z0's Y8 as Y. So Y = 19 * i = 19 * 1 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 368, "question": "The number of each X0's W2 equals 22 more than the sum of each X9's WWW, each X9's W6 and each X8's W2. The number of each X0's W3 equals 15 more than the sum of each X8's W2, each X8's WWW and each X9's WWW. The number of each X8's W2 equals 7. The number of each X9's W6 equals 6 more than the difference of each X8's W2 and each X8's WWW. How many WWW does each X0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["X8's W2 as u. So u = 7.\nDefine each X8's WWW as S. So S = u = 7.\nDefine each X9's W6 as A. So A = 6 * u - S = 6 * 7 - 7 = 12.\nDefine each X9's WWW as i. So i = A = 12.\nDefine each X0's W3 as Y. So Y = 15 * (u + S + i) = 15 * (7 + 7 + 12) = 19.\nDefine each X0's W2 as F. So F = 22 + (i + A + u) = 22 + (12 + 12 + 7) = 7.\nDefine each X0's WWW as r. So r = F + Y = 7 + 19 = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 369, "question": "The number of each Y0's X7 equals 20 more than each Y9's X7. The number of each Y9's X8 equals the difference of each Y9's X7 and each Z5's YYY. The number of each Z3's Y9 equals 12 times each Z5's Y9. The number of each Z3's Y0 equals each Y9's X8. The number of each Y2's X2 equals 13 times each Z2's XXX. The number of each Y0's X2 equals the difference of each Y9's X7 and each Y0's X7. The number of each Z2's Y0 equals 5 more than each Y9's X7. The number of each Z5's Y0 equals 3 more than each Y9's X7. The number of each Z5's Y9 equals 17 times each Y2's X2. The number of each Y9's X7 equals 14. How many YYY does each Z3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["Y9's X7 as u. So u = 14.\nDefine each Y0's X7 as S. So S = 20 * u = 20 * 14 = 4.\nDefine each Y0's X2 as A. So A = u - S = 14 - 4 = 10.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as i. So i = S + A = 4 + 10 = 14.\nDefine each Z2's Y0 as Y. So Y = 5 * u = 5 * 14 = 1.\nDefine each Z2's XXX as F. So F = Y * i = 1 * 14 = 14.\nDefine each Y2's X2 as r. So r = 13 * F = 13 * 14 = 21.\nDefine each Z5's Y9 as l. So l = 17 * r = 17 * 21 = 12.\nDefine each Z5's Y0 as V. So V = 3 * u = 3 * 14 = 19.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as q. So q = V + l = 19 + 12 = 8.\nDefine each Y9's X8 as z. So z = u - q = 14 - 8 = 6.\nDefine each Z3's Y0 as A. So A = S = 6.\nDefine each Z3's Y9 as i. So i = 12 * l = 12 * 12 = 6.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as Y. So Y = i + A = 6 + 6 = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 370, "question": "The number of each Y6's X7 equals each Y7's X3. The number of each Y7's X3 equals 5. How many X7 does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Y7's X3 as u. So u = 5.\nDefine each Y6's X7 as S. So S = u = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 371, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y2 equals 5. How many YYY does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Z0's Y2 as u. So u = 5.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as S. So S = u = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 372, "question": "The number of each Y2's X8 equals each Z0's Y2. The number of each Z5's Y0 equals each Y2's XXX. The number of each Y0's X1 equals 2 times each Z0's Y8. The number of each Y2's X1 equals 21. The number of each Z5's Y2 equals 14. The number of each Y2's X6 equals 10. The number of each Z0's Y2 equals 3 more than each Y0's X1. The number of each Z5's Y8 equals the difference of each Y2's X8 and each Y2's X6. The number of each Z0's Y8 equals 18. How many YYY does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["Z0's Y8 as u. So u = 18.\nDefine each Y0's X1 as S. So S = 2 * u = 2 * 18 = 13.\nDefine each Z0's Y2 as A. So A = 3 * S = 3 * 13 = 16.\nDefine each Y2's X8 as i. So i = A = 16.\nDefine each Y2's X6 as Y. So Y = 10.\nDefine each Y2's X1 as F. So F = 21.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as r. So r = Y + F + i = 10 + 21 + 16 = 1.\nDefine each Z5's Y0 as l. So l = r = 1.\nDefine each Z5's Y2 as V. So V = 14.\nDefine each Z5's Y8 as q. So q = i - Y = 16 - 10 = 6.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as z. So z = q + V + l = 6 + 14 + 1 = 21.\nThus, the answer is 21."], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 373, "question": "The number of each Y5's X0 equals 22. The number of each Y9's X0 equals each Z1's Y5. The number of each Z1's Y5 equals each Y5's X0. The number of each Y9's X3 equals 14 more than the difference of each Z1's Y5 and each Y5's X0. How many XXX does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["Y5's X0 = 22. Z1's Y5 = u = 22.\nDefine each Y9's X3 as u. So u = 14 * Z1's Y5 - u = 14 * 22 - 22 = 10.\nDefine each Y9's X0 as S. So S = Z1's Y5 = 22.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 22 + 10 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 374, "question": "The number of each Y8's X3 equals 14 more than the difference of each Y7's X1 and each Y1's X3. The number of each Y8's X1 equals 21 times the difference of each Y8's X5 and each Y7's X1. The number of each Y8's X5 equals the sum of each Y1's X3 and each Y7's X1. The number of each Y1's X3 equals 13 times each Y7's X1. The number of each Y7's X1 equals 9. How many XXX does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Y7's X1 as u. So u = 9.\nDefine each Y1's X3 as S. So S = 13 * u = 13 * 9 = 2.\nDefine each Y8's X5 as A. So A = S + u = 2 + 9 = 11.\nDefine each Y8's X1 as i. So i = 21 * A - u = 21 * 11 - 9 = 19.\nDefine each Y8's X3 as Y. So Y = 14 * u - S = 14 * 9 - 2 = 19.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as F. So F = Y + i + A = 19 + 19 + 11 = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 375, "question": "The number of each X7's W7 equals 17 times each X8's W1. The number of each Y7's X9 equals each X7's W7. The number of each X8's W1 equals 12 more than each Z6's Y1. The number of each Z6's Y1 equals 1. How many X9 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Z6's Y1 as u. So u = 1.\nDefine each X8's W1 as S. So S = 12 * u = 12 * 1 = 12.\nDefine each X7's W7 as A. So A = 17 * S = 17 * 12 = 20.\nDefine each Y7's X9 as i. So i = A = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 376, "question": "The number of each Y9's X5 equals 17 times each Y9's X1. The number of each Y1's X1 equals 6 more than the sum of each Y9's X1, each Y9's XXX and each Y9's X5. The number of each Y9's X1 equals 6. How many XXX does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Y9's X1 as u. So u = 6.\nDefine each Y9's X5 as S. So S = 17 * u = 17 * 6 = 10.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 10 + 6 = 16.\nDefine each Y1's X1 as i. So i = 6 * (u + A + S) = 6 * (6 + 16 + 10) = 19.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as Y. So Y = i = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 377, "question": "The number of each Y2's X3 equals 3 times each Y3's X3. The number of each Y7's X1 equals 4 more than the sum of each Y3's X3 and each Y2's X3. The number of each Y3's X3 equals 4. The number of each Y2's X1 equals 11 more than the sum of each Y7's X1, each Y2's X3 and each Y3's X3. How many X1 does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Y3's X3 = 4. Y2's X3 as u. So u = 3 * Y3's X3 = 3 * 4 = 12.\nDefine each Y7's X1 as S. So S = 4 * u + u = 4 * 12 + 12 = 14.\nDefine each Y2's X1 as A. So A = 11 * (S + u + Y3's X3) = 11 * (14 + 12 + 4) = 19.\nDefine each X3's WWW as i. So i = u * i = 12 * 1 = 12.\nDefine each Y3's X3 as Y. So Y = 4.\nDefine each Y2's X3 as F. So F = 3 + Y = 3 + 4 = 7.\nDefine each Y7's X1 as r. So r = 4 + Y + F = 4 + 4 + 7 = 15.\nDefine each Y2's X1 as l. So l = 11 * (r + F + Y) = 11 * (15 + 7 + 4) = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 378, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y8 equals 6. The number of each Z9's Y5 equals 6 times each Z9's Y8. How many Y5 does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["Z9's Y8 = 6. Z9's Y5 = 6 * Z9's Y8 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 379, "question": "The number of each Y8's X1 equals 22. The number of each Y9's X3 equals 12 more than each Y8's X1. The number of each Y0's X1 equals 8 times the sum of each Y9's XXX, each Y9's X1 and each Y9's X6. The number of each Y9's X1 equals 1 more than each Y8's X1. The number of each Y9's X6 equals 6 more than the sum of each Y9's X3 and each Y8's X1. How many X1 does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 380, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y7 equals 14 more than each Z5's Y1. The number of each Z5's Y1 equals 4 more than each Z7's Y2. The number of each Z5's Y7 equals 4 more than each Y7's XXX. The number of each Y7's X5 equals the sum of each Z5's Y1 and each Z7's YYY. The number of each Z7's Y2 equals 18. How many Y7 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["Z7's Y2 as u. So u = 18.\nDefine each Z5's Y1 as S. So S = 4 * u = 4 * 18 = 3.\nDefine each Z7's Y7 as A. So A = 14 * S = 14 * 3 = 19.\nDefine each Z7's YYY as i. So i = u + A + S = 18 + 19 + 3 = 17.\nDefine each Y7's X5 as Y. So Y = S + i = 3 + 17 = 20.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as F. So F = Y = 20.\nDefine each Z5's Y7 as r. So r = 4 * F = 4 * 20 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 381, "question": "The number of each X2's W2 equals 4. The number of each X2's W9 equals the sum of each Z6's Y1, each Y1's X6 and each Z6's XXX. The number of each Z6's Y1 equals each X2's W2. The number of each X6's W9 equals 19 more than the sum of each Z6's Y1 and each Y2's X6. The number of each Y2's X6 equals the difference of each Z6's Y1 and each X2's W9. The number of each Y1's X6 equals 19 times the sum of each Z6's Y1 and each X2's W2. How many WWW does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["Y1's X6 as u. So u = 19 * Z6's Y1 + X2's W2 = 19 * 1 + 22 = 18.\nDefine each X2's W2 as S. So S = 4.\nDefine each Z6's Y1 as A. So A = S = 4.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as i. So i = u = 18.\nDefine each Z6's XXX as Y. So Y = A * i = 4 * 18 = 3.\nDefine each X2's W9 as F. So F = (A + u + Y) = (4 + 18 + 3) = 2.\nDefine each Y2's X6 as r. So r = A - F = 4 - 2 = 2.\nDefine each X6's W9 as l. So l = 19 + A + r = 19 + 4 + 2 = 2.\nDefine each X6's WWW as V. So V = l = 2.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as q. So q = u * V = 18 * 2 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 382, "question": "The number of each Y7's X4 equals 4. The number of each Y0's X2 equals 15 times the difference of each Y7's X4 and each Y7's XXX. How many X2 does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y7's X4 as u. So u = 4.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as S. So S = u = 4.\nDefine each Y0's X2 as A. So A = 15 * u - S = 15 * 4 - 4 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 383, "question": "The number of each Y9's X8 equals 3 times each X2's W5. The number of each Y8's X2 equals 6 times each Y9's XXX. The number of each Y9's X2 equals the sum of each Y5's X2 and each X8's W5. The number of each X8's W1 equals 12 more than each Y8's X2. The number of each X8's W5 equals 13 more than each Y5's X2. The number of each Z2's Y5 equals 17 times the sum of each Y9's X2, each X2's W5 and each Z4's Y9. The number of each Z2's Y8 equals 12 times each Y8's X2. The number of each Y5's X8 equals 16 times each Z4's Y8. The number of each Z2's Y9 equals each Y9's X8. The number of each Z4's Y8 equals 20. The number of each Y8's X8 equals the difference of each Z2's YYY and each Y5's X2. The number of each X2's W5 equals 14 times each X8's W5. The number of each Z4's Y9 equals each X8's W1. The number of each Y5's X2 equals 10 times each Y5's X8. How many X8 does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 384, "question": "The number of each X3's W9 equals the sum of each X3's W7 and each Z1's Y0. The number of each X7's W9 equals 9 more than each X3's W9. The number of each Z4's Y3 equals each X7's WWW. The number of each Y0's X7 equals 18 times the sum of each X3's W7 and each Z4's Y3. The number of each Z1's Y0 equals 2. The number of each X3's W7 equals 6 more than each Z1's Y0. The number of each X7's W7 equals 13 times each X3's WWW. How many X7 does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 385, "question": "The number of each X0's W6 equals the sum of each Z4's Y7, each Y9's X6 and each X6's W6. The number of each Y7's X6 equals each X6's WWW. The number of each Y9's X6 equals 6. The number of each Y7's X0 equals each X0's W6. The number of each X6's W3 equals 1 more than the sum of each X6's W6, each Z4's Y7 and each Y9's X6. The number of each Y9's X0 equals each Z0's XXX. The number of each Z4's Y7 equals 6 times each Y9's X6. The number of each Z0's Y7 equals 10 more than the sum of each X0's W6, each Y9's X6 and each Y7's X0. The number of each X6's W6 equals 3 times the sum of each Z4's Y7 and each Y9's X6. How many X0 does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["Y9's X6 as u. So u = 6.\nDefine each Z4's Y7 as S. So S = 6 * u = 6 * 6 = 13.\nDefine each X6's W6 as A. So A = 3 * S + u = 3 * 13 + 6 = 15.\nDefine each X6's W3 as i. So i = 1 * (A + S + u) = 1 * (15 + 13 + 6) = 11.\nDefine each X6's WWW as Y. So Y = A + i = 15 + 11 = 3.\nDefine each Y7's X6 as F. So F = Y = 3.\nDefine each Y7's X0 as r. So r = A = 15.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as l. So l = r + F = 15 + 3 = 18.\nDefine each Z0's Y7 as V. So V = 10 * (r + u + l) = 10 * (15 + 6 + 18) = 19.\nDefine each Z0's XXX as q. So q = V * l = 19 * 18 = 20.\nDefine each Y9's X0 as z. So z = q = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 386, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y2 equals the sum of each Z4's YYY, each Z4's Y9 and each Z4's Y2. The number of each Z7's Y9 equals the sum of each Z4's YYY, each Z4's Y9 and each Z4's Y2. The number of each Z4's Y9 equals 20. The number of each Z4's Y2 equals 17 times each Z4's Y9. How many YYY does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Z4's Y9 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each Z4's Y2 as S. So S = 17 * u = 17 * 20 = 18.\nDefine each Z4's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 18 + 20 = 15.\nDefine each Z7's Y9 as i. So i = (A + u + S) = (15 + 20 + 18) = 7.\nDefine each Z7's Y2 as Y. So Y = (A + u + S) = (15 + 20 + 18) = 7.\nDefine each Z7's YYY as F. So F = Y + i = 7 + 7 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 387, "question": "The number of each Y5's X6 equals 16. The number of each Y1's X4 equals each Y0's X4. The number of each Y1's X5 equals each Y5's X6. The number of each Y0's X4 equals 8 more than each Y5's X6. How many XXX does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["Y5's X6 = 16. Y0's X4 = 8 * Y5's X6 = 8 * 16 = 13.\nDefine each Y1's X4 as u. So u = S = 13.\nDefine each Y1's X5 as S. So S = Y5's X6 = 16.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 16 + 13 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 388, "question": "The number of each Y1's X4 equals each Y3's X9. The number of each Y9's X8 equals the sum of each Y3's X4, each Y1's X4, each Y9's X9 and each Y3's X9. The number of each Y9's X9 equals each Y3's X4. The number of each Y6's X9 equals the sum of each Y9's XXX and each Y3's X9. The number of each Y3's X9 equals 14. The number of each Y3's X4 equals 14 more than the sum of each Y1's X4 and each Y3's X9. The number of each Y1's X9 equals 21 times each Y6's XXX. How many X9 does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["Y3's X9 as u. So u = 14.\nDefine each Y1's X4 as S. So S = u = 14.\nDefine each Y3's X4 as A. So A = 14 * S + u = 14 * 14 + 14 = 3.\nDefine each Y9's X9 as i. So i = A = 3.\nDefine each Y9's X8 as Y. So Y = (A + S + i + u) = (3 + 14 + 3 + 14) = 11.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as F. So F = Y + i = 11 + 3 = 14.\nDefine each Y6's X9 as r. So r = F + u = 14 + 14 = 5.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as l. So l = r = 5.\nDefine each Y1's X9 as V. So V = 21 * l = 21 * 5 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 389, "question": "The number of each X9's W1 equals 17 times the difference of each Z5's Y0 and each Z4's Y9. The number of each X4's W1 equals 8. The number of each Z4's Y9 equals 20. The number of each Y9's X9 equals 11 times the difference of each Y0's WWW and each Z5's Y0. The number of each Y0's X4 equals 7 more than the difference of each Z5's Y0 and each X9's W1. The number of each Z5's Y0 equals 12 more than each Z4's Y9. How many X9 does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["Z4's Y9 = 20. Z5's Y0 = 12 * Z4's Y9 = 12 * 20 = 10.\nDefine each X9's W1 as u. So u = 17 * Z5's Y0 - Z4's Y9 = 17 * 10 - 20 = 17.\nDefine each Y0's X4 as S. So S = 7 * Z5's Y0 - u = 7 * 10 - 17 = 11.\nDefine each X4's W1 as A. So A = 8.\nDefine each X4's WWW as i. So i = A = 8.\nDefine each Y0's WWW as Y. So Y = S * i = 11 * 8 = 19.\nDefine each Y9's X9 as F. So F = 11 * Y - Z5's Y0 = 11 * 19 - 10 = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 390, "question": "The number of each X8's W6 equals 6. How many W6 does each X8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["X8's W6 = 6. So X8's W6 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 391, "question": "The number of each X0's W0 equals 22 times each Y9's XXX. The number of each X5's W2 equals each Y6's X5. The number of each Y9's X0 equals 20. The number of each X5's W0 equals the difference of each Y9's X5 and each X0's W0. The number of each X0's W2 equals 17 more than each Y6's WWW. The number of each Y9's X5 equals 7 more than each Y6's XXX. The number of each Y6's X5 equals 20 times each Y9's X0. How many W2 does each X0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Y9's X0 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each Y6's X5 as S. So S = 20 * u = 20 * 20 = 9.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as A. So A = S = 9.\nDefine each Y9's X5 as i. So i = 7 * A = 7 * 9 = 17.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as Y. So Y = u + i = 20 + 17 = 14.\nDefine each X0's W0 as F. So F = 22 * Y = 22 * 14 = 9.\nDefine each X5's W0 as r. So r = i - F = 17 - 9 = 8.\nDefine each X5's W2 as l. So l = S = 9.\nDefine each X5's WWW as V. So V = l + r = 9 + 8 = 17.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as q. So q = S * V = 9 * 17 = 15.\nDefine each X0's W2 as z. So z = 17 * q = 17 * 15 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 392, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y8 equals 7. The number of each Z6's Y0 equals 6 more than each Z7's Y8. The number of each Z6's Y8 equals 1 times each Z6's Y0. How many Y8 does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["Z7's Y8 = 7. Z6's Y0 = 6 + Z7's Y8 = 6 + 7 = 13.\nDefine each Z6's Y8 as u. So u = 1 * Z6's Y0 = 1 * 13 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 393, "question": "The number of each Y4's X7 equals each Z8's XXX. The number of each Y7's X7 equals 16 times each Z2's Y9. The number of each Z8's Y7 equals each Y7's X7. The number of each Z2's Y9 equals 15. The number of each Y7's X5 equals each Z2's Y9. How many XXX does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Z2's Y9 = 15. Y7's X5 as u. So u = Z2's Y9 = 15.\nDefine each Y7's X7 as S. So S = 16 * Z2's Y9 = 16 * 15 = 10.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 10 + 15 = 2.\nDefine each Z8's Y7 as i. So i = S = 10.\nDefine each Z8's XXX as Y. So Y = i * A = 10 * 2 = 20.\nDefine each Y4's X7 as F. So F = Y = 20.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as r. So r = F = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 394, "question": "The number of each X8's W7 equals each Y3's X3. The number of each Y3's X3 equals 8 times the sum of each Y5's WWW and each Y5's X3. The number of each X3's W3 equals 11. The number of each Y5's X3 equals 7 times the sum of each X3's W3 and each X3's WWW. How many W7 does each X8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["X3's W3 as u. So u = 11.\nDefine each X3's WWW as S. So S = u = 11.\nDefine each Y5's X3 as A. So A = 7 * u + S = 7 * 11 + 11 = 19.\nDefine each Y5's WWW as i. So i = A * S = 19 * 11 = 2.\nDefine each Y3's X3 as Y. So Y = 8 + i + A = 8 + 2 + 19 = 6.\nDefine each X8's W7 as F. So F = Y = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 395, "question": "The number of each Y3's X0 equals 19. The number of each Z5's Y4 equals 10 times each Y3's XXX. How many Y4 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Y3's X0 = 19. Y3's XXX = 19. Y4's XXX = 19. Z5's Y4 = 10 * Y3's X0 = 10 * 19 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 396, "question": "The number of each Y4's X3 equals the sum of each Y5's X1 and each X3's W9. The number of each Z2's Y5 equals the sum of each Z3's WWW and each X1's WWW. The number of each Z3's Y5 equals 16 more than the difference of each Y4's X3 and each Y5's X1. The number of each X3's W9 equals 19. The number of each X1's W9 equals the difference of each Y4's WWW and each Z3's Y5. The number of each Y5's X1 equals 7 more than the sum of each X3's W9 and each X3's WWW. How many WWW does each Z2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["X3's W9 as u. So u = 19.\nDefine each X3's WWW as S. So S = u = 19.\nDefine each Y5's X1 as A. So A = 7 * u + S = 7 * 19 + 19 = 14.\nDefine each Y4's X3 as i. So i = A + u = 14 + 19 = 10.\nDefine each Y5's WWW as Y. So Y = A * S = 14 * 19 = 13.\nDefine each Z3's Y5 as F. So F = 16 * i - A = 16 * 10 - 14 = 16.\nDefine each Z3's WWW as r. So r = F * Y = 16 * 13 = 1.\nDefine each Z2's Y5 as l. So l = r + Y = 1 + 13 = 14.\nDefine each Z2's WWW as V. So V = l * Y = 14 * 13 = 21.\nThus, the answer is 21."], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 397, "question": "The number of each X3's W8 equals 8 times the sum of each Z2's Y9, each Z5's Y3 and each Y3's X3. The number of each Z5's Y3 equals 15. The number of each Z5's Y2 equals 13 times the difference of each Y3's X0 and each Y2's X3. The number of each X0's W8 equals 2. The number of each Y3's X3 equals 8 times each Y3's X0. The number of each Y3's X0 equals 5 times each X0's W8. The number of each Y2's X3 equals 19 times the difference of each Z5's Y3 and each X0's W8. The number of each Z2's Y9 equals the sum of each Y3's XXX, each Z5's Y3, each Z5's XXX and each Y3's X0. How many WWW does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Y2's X3 as u. So u = 19 * Z5's Y3 - X0's W8 = 19 * 5 - 2 = 11.\nDefine each Z5's Y2 as S. So S = 13 + u - u = 13 + 11 - 11 = 13.\nDefine each X0's W8 as A. So A = 2.\nDefine each Y3's X0 as i. So i = 5 * A = 5 * 2 = 10.\nDefine each Y3's X3 as Y. So Y = 8 * i = 8 * 10 = 11.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as F. So F = Y + i = 11 + 10 = 21.\nDefine each Z5's Y3 as r. So r = 15.\nDefine each Y2's X3 as l. So l = 19 * r - A = 19 * 15 - 2 = 14.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as V. So V = l * A = 14 * 2 = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 398, "question": "The number of each Y0's X5 equals 6 times the difference of each Y8's X2 and each Y8's XXX. The number of each Y8's X2 equals 2 more than each Y0's X2. The number of each Y0's X2 equals 11. The number of each Y8's X9 equals 22 more than each Y8's X5. The number of each Y8's X5 equals 6 times each Y8's X2. How many X5 does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["Y0's X2 as u. So u = 11.\nDefine each Y8's X2 as S. So S = 2 * u = 2 * 11 = 22.\nDefine each Y8's X5 as A. So A = 6 * S = 6 * 22 = 17.\nDefine each Y8's X9 as i. So i = 22 * A = 22 * 17 = 6.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as Y. So Y = S + A + i = 22 + 17 + 6 = 22.\nDefine each Y0's X5 as F. So F = 6 * S - Y = 6 * 22 - 22 = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 399, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y6 equals each Z9's Y7. The number of each Z9's Y7 equals 20. How many Y6 does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Z9's Y7 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each Z9's Y6 as S. So S = u = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 400, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y8 equals 22 more than each X2's W2. The number of each Z1's Y9 equals 10. The number of each Y1's X0 equals each Y8's X2. The number of each Y8's X2 equals 7 more than each Z1's Y9. The number of each X0's W2 equals 15 times the sum of each Z3's YYY and each X2's WWW. The number of each Z3's Y1 equals 11 times each Z0's WWW. The number of each X2's W2 equals 13 times each Z1's Y9. How many WWW does each Z3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["Z1's Y9 = 10. X2's W2 as u. So u = 13 * Z1's Y9 = 13 * 10 = 15.\nDefine each Z0's Y8 as S. So S = 22 * u = 22 * 15 = 8.\nDefine each Y8's X2 as A. So A = 7 * Z1's Y9 = 7 * 10 = 1.\nDefine each X2's WWW as i. So i = u = 15.\nDefine each Y8's WWW as Y. So Y = A * i = 1 * 15 = 15.\nDefine each Z0's WWW as F. So F = S * Y = 8 * 15 = 5.\nDefine each Z3's Y1 as r. So r = 11 * F = 11 * 5 = 9.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as l. So l = r = 9.\nDefine each X0's W2 as V. So V = 15 * l + i = 15 * 9 + 15 = 21.\nDefine each X0's WWW as q. So q = V = 21.\nDefine each Z3's WWW as z. So z = r * q = 9 * 21 = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 401, "question": "The number of each Y0's X0 equals each Z5's Y3. The number of each Z5's Y3 equals 22. How many X0 does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["Z5's Y3 as u. So u = 22.\nDefine each Y0's X0 as S. So S = u = 22.\nDefine each lollip0 as A. So A = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDefine each l0. So l = 20.\nDef"], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 402, "question": "The number of each Z4's Y2 equals 6 times each Y2's XXX. The number of each Y2's X8 equals 2 times each Y7's X2. The number of each Y7's X2 equals 14. The number of each Y3's X0 equals the sum of each Y2's X8 and each Z4's XXX. How many X0 does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["Y7's X2 as u. So u = 14.\nDefine each Y2's X8 as S. So S = 2 * u = 2 * 14 = 5.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as A. So A = S = 5.\nDefine each Z4's Y2 as i. So i = 6 * A = 6 * 5 = 7.\nDefine each Z4's XXX as Y. So Y = i * A = 7 * 5 = 12.\nDefine each Y3's X0 as F. So F = S + Y = 5 + 12 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 403, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y6 equals the sum of each Z7's Y2 and each Z3's Y7. The number of each Z3's Y9 equals 5 times each Z7's Y6. The number of each Z3's Y6 equals 12. The number of each Z3's Y7 equals 16 times each Z7's Y2. The number of each Z0's Y2 equals 20 times each Z3's Y6. The number of each Z7's Y2 equals 7 times each Z0's Y2. The number of each Z0's Y7 equals the sum of each Z3's Y9 and each Z7's Y2. How many Y7 does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["Z3's Y6 as u. So u = 12.\nDefine each Z0's Y2 as S. So S = 20 * u = 20 * 12 = 10.\nDefine each Z7's Y2 as A. So A = 7 * S = 7 * 10 = 1.\nDefine each Z3's Y7 as i. So i = 16 * A = 16 * 1 = 16.\nDefine each Z7's Y6 as Y. So Y = A + i = 1 + 16 = 17.\nDefine each Z3's Y9 as F. So F = 5 * Y = 5 * 17 = 16.\nDefine each Z0's Y7 as r. So r = F + A = 16 + 1 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 404, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y1 equals 0 times each Y7's WWW. The number of each X6's W5 equals 5. The number of each Y1's X6 equals each Z0's YYY. The number of each Y1's X4 equals 1 times each Y1's X6. The number of each Y7's X6 equals 7 more than each X6's W5. How many XXX does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["X6's W5 = 5. Y7's X6 as u. So u = 7 * X6's W5 = 7 * 5 = 12.\nDefine each X6's WWW as S. So S = X6's W5 = 5.\nDefine each Y7's WWW as A. So A = u * S = 12 * 5 = 14.\nDefine each Z0's Y1 as i. So i = 0 * A = 0 * 14 = 0.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as Y. So Y = i = 0.\nDefine each Y1's X6 as F. So F = Y = 0.\nDefine each Y1's X4 as r. So r = 1 * F = 1 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as l. So l = r + F = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z0's XXX as V. So V = i * l = 0 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 405, "question": "The number of each Y3's X2 equals 18. The number of each Y8's X0 equals 21 more than each Z8's Y8. The number of each Z8's Y8 equals 22 times each Y3's X2. The number of each Z7's Y3 equals 16 times the sum of each Y3's X2 and each Z8's XXX. The number of each Y8's X6 equals 1 more than each Y8's X0. How many Y3 does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Y3's X2 as u. So u = 18.\nDefine each Z8's Y8 as S. So S = 22 * u = 22 * 18 = 5.\nDefine each Y8's X0 as A. So A = 21 * S = 21 * 5 = 13.\nDefine each Y8's X6 as i. So i = 1 * A = 1 * 13 = 13.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as Y. So Y = A + i = 13 + 13 = 3.\nDefine each Z8's XXX as F. So F = S * Y = 5 * 3 = 15.\nDefine each Z7's Y3 as r. So r = 16 * u + F = 16 * 18 + 15 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 406, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y0 equals 5. How many Y0 does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Z1's Y0 = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 407, "question": "The number of each X1's W4 equals the sum of each X7's W8 and each Z8's WWW. The number of each Y2's X7 equals each Z0's Y2. The number of each X7's W8 equals each Z8's XXX. The number of each Z0's Y2 equals 22. The number of each Z8's Y2 equals the sum of each Z0's Y2, each Y2's XXX and each Y2's X7. How many WWW does each X1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["Z0's Y2 = 22. Y2's X7 = Z0's Y2 = 22.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as u. So u = u = 22.\nDefine each Z8's Y2 as S. So S = (S + u + u) = (22 + 22 + 22) = 20.\nDefine each Z8's XXX as A. So A = S * u = 20 * 22 = 3.\nDefine each X7's W8 as i. So i = A = 3.\nDefine each X7's WWW as Y. So Y = i = 3.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as F. So F = u * Y = 22 * 3 = 20.\nDefine each Z8's WWW as r. So r = S * F = 20 * 20 = 9.\nDefine each X1's W4 as l. So l = i + r = 3 + 9 = 12.\nDefine each X1's WWW as V. So V = l = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 408, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y1 equals 21 times each X2's W8. The number of each Z3's Y1 equals the sum of each X2's W8, each Z0's XXX and each Y1's X3. The number of each X2's W8 equals each X3's W8. The number of each Y7's X3 equals 19 times each Z3's Y1. The number of each X3's W8 equals 18. The number of each Y1's X3 equals each Z0's Y1. How many X3 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["X3's W8 = 18. X2's W8 = u = 18.\nDefine each Z0's Y1 as u. So u = 21 * u = 21 * 18 = 10.\nDefine each Y1's X3 as S. So S = u = 10.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as A. So A = S = 10.\nDefine each Z0's XXX as i. So i = u * A = 10 * 10 = 8.\nDefine each Z3's Y1 as Y. So Y = (u + i + S) = (10 + 8 + 10) = 5.\nDefine each Y7's X3 as F. So F = 19 * Y = 19 * 5 = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 409, "question": "The number of each Y5's X6 equals the difference of each Z0's Y5 and each Y7's XXX. The number of each Y7's X7 equals 21 times each Y7's X6. The number of each Y7's X6 equals 10 more than each Z0's Y5. The number of each Z0's Y5 equals 8. How many X6 does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["Z0's Y5 as u. So u = 8.\nDefine each Y7's X6 as S. So S = 10 * u = 10 * 8 = 11.\nDefine each Y7's X7 as A. So A = 21 * S = 21 * 11 = 1.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as i. So i = S + A = 11 + 1 = 12.\nDefine each Y5's X6 as Y. So Y = u - i = 8 - 12 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 410, "question": "The number of each Y2's X0 equals 19. The number of each Y2's X7 equals 16 times each Y2's X0. How many X7 does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Y2's X0 as u. So u = 19.\nDefine each Y2's X7 as S. So S = 16 * u = 16 * 19 = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 411, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y0 equals 8 times each Y1's X5. The number of each Y1's X5 equals 18. The number of each Z1's Y7 equals 18 times the difference of each Z1's Y0 and each Y7's X0. The number of each Y7's X0 equals 19 times the sum of each Y1's X5 and each Z1's Y0. How many Y7 does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Y1's X5 as u. So u = 18.\nDefine each Z1's Y0 as S. So S = 8 * u = 8 * 18 = 6.\nDefine each Y7's X0 as A. So A = 19 * u + S = 19 * 18 + 6 = 17.\nDefine each Z1's Y7 as i. So i = 18 + S - A = 18 + 6 - 17 = 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 412, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y0 equals the difference of each X7's WWW and each X7's W3. The number of each Y6's X1 equals the sum of each X7's W3 and each X1's W3. The number of each Y0's X7 equals 11 times the sum of each Z1's Y6 and each X1's W6. The number of each Z1's Y6 equals 18. The number of each X1's W6 equals 16 times each Z1's Y6. The number of each X1's W3 equals the sum of each X1's W6, each X7's WWW and each Y0's X7. The number of each Y6's X7 equals each Z7's Y0. The number of each X7's W3 equals the sum of each X1's W6 and each Z1's Y6. The number of each X7's W6 equals 16 more than each Y0's X7. How many XXX does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["Z1's Y6 = 18. X1's W6 as u. So u = 16 * Z1's Y6 = 16 * 18 = 12.\nDefine each Y0's X7 as S. So S = 11 * u + u = 11 * 12 + 12 = 5.\nDefine each X7's W6 as A. So A = 16 * S = 16 * 5 = 11.\nDefine each X7's W3 as i. So i = u + Z1's Y6 = 12 + 18 = 7.\nDefine each X7's WWW as Y. So Y = A + i = 11 + 7 = 18.\nDefine each Z7's Y0 as F. So F = Y - i = 18 - 7 = 11.\nDefine each Y6's X7 as r. So r = F = 11.\nDefine each X1's W3 as l. So l = (u + Y + S) = (12 + 18 + 5) = 12.\nDefine each Y6's X1 as V. So V = i + l = 7 + 12 = 19.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as q. So q = V + r = 19 + 11 = 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 413, "question": "The number of each X6's W2 equals 7. The number of each Z6's Y2 equals 6 more than each Z5's Y0. The number of each Y0's X7 equals 0 times each Z6's YYY. The number of each Y3's X6 equals the sum of each Y0's XXX and each X6's W2. The number of each Y2's X6 equals 2 times each Y0's XXX. The number of each Z5's Y0 equals 13 more than each X6's W2. The number of each Y2's X0 equals each Z5's Y0. The number of each Y2's X7 equals 11 more than each Y3's X6. The number of each Y0's X0 equals each Z6's Y2. How many XXX does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["X6's W2 = 7. Z5's Y0 = 13 + X6's W2 = 13 + 7 = 20.\nDefine each Z6's Y2 as u. So u = 6 * Z5's Y0 = 6 * 20 = 5.\nDefine each Z6's YYY as S. So S = u = 5.\nDefine each Y0's X7 as A. So A = 0 * S = 0 * 5 = 0.\nDefine each Y0's X0 as i. So i = u = 5.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as Y. So Y = i + A = 5 + 0 = 5.\nDefine each Y2's X6 as F. So F = 2 * Y = 2 * 5 = 10.\nDefine each Y3's X6 as r. So r = Y + F = 5 + 10 = 15.\nDefine each Y2's X7 as l. So l = 11 * r = 11 * 15 = 4.\nDefine each Y2's X0 as V. So V = Z5's Y0 = 20.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as q. So q = V + l + F = 20 + 4 + 10 = 11.\nDefine each Z6's XXX as z. So z = u * q = 5 * 11 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 414, "question": "The number of each X5's W6 equals 1 more than the sum of each Y6's X4 and each Y1's X4. The number of each Y6's X4 equals 6 more than the difference of each Y0's WWW and each Y0's XXX. The number of each Y0's X4 equals 15 more than each Y1's X4. The number of each X4's W6 equals each Y0's XXX. The number of each Y1's X4 equals 13. How many W6 does each X5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["Y1's X4 = 13. Y0's X4 as u. So u = 15 * Y1's X4 = 15 * 13 = 11.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as S. So S = u = 11.\nDefine each X4's W6 as A. So A = S = 11.\nDefine each X4's WWW as i. So i = A = 11.\nDefine each Y0's WWW as Y. So Y = u * i = 11 * 11 = 6.\nDefine each Y6's X4 as F. So F = 6 * Y - S = 6 * 6 - 11 = 19.\nDefine each X5's W6 as r. So r = 1 * F + Y = 1 * 19 + 6 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 415, "question": "The number of each Y3's X5 equals 19 times each Z0's Y1. The number of each Z0's Y1 equals 4. The number of each X5's W7 equals 4 more than the difference of each Z0's YYY and each Z0's Y1. How many WWW does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Z0's Y1 as u. So u = 4.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as S. So S = u = 4.\nDefine each X5's W7 as A. So A = 4 * S - u = 4 * 4 - 4 = 12.\nDefine each X5's WWW as i. So i = A = 12.\nDefine each Y3's X5 as Y. So Y = 19 * u = 19 * 4 = 7.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as F. So F = Y * i = 7 * 12 = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 416, "question": "The number of each Y1's X8 equals 14. The number of each X7's W5 equals 1 more than each Y1's X8. How many W5 does each X7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Y1's X8 = 14. X7's W5 = 1 * Y1's X8 = 1 * 14 = 14.\nDefine each Y1's X8 as u. So u = 14.\nDefine each X7's WWW as S. So S = X7's W5 = 14.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as A. So A = u * S = 14 * 14 = 12.\nDefine each X3's WWW as i. So i = X3's WWW = 3.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as Y. So Y = u * A = 14 * 12 = 7.\nDefine each X3's WWW as F. So F = i = 3.\nDefine each Y1's X8 as r. So r = 14.\nDefine each X7's WWW as l. So l = X7's W5 = 14.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as V. So V = u * A + r * l = 14 * 7 + 14 * 14 = 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 417, "question": "The number of each Y7's X4 equals 12. The number of each Y0's X4 equals 15 more than each Y7's X4. The number of each Y0's X1 equals the difference of each Y0's X4 and each Y7's X4. How many XXX does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Y7's X4 = 12. Y0's X4 as u. So u = 15 * Y7's X4 = 15 * 12 = 19.\nDefine each Y0's X1 as S. So S = u - Y7's X4 = 19 - 12 = 7.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 7 + 19 = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 418, "question": "The number of each Y4's X0 equals the sum of each X0's W2 and each X2's W3. The number of each X0's W3 equals each X2's W3. The number of each Y1's X2 equals each Y4's X0. The number of each Y4's X2 equals each Y1's XXX. The number of each X2's W3 equals 21. The number of each Y1's X0 equals each Y1's X2. The number of each X0's W2 equals 0 more than each X0's W3. How many X2 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["X2's W3 = 21. X0's W3 as u. So u = 21.\nDefine each X0's W2 as S. So S = 0 * u = 0 * 21 = 0.\nDefine each Y4's X0 as A. So A = S + u = 0 + 21 = 21.\nDefine each Y1's X2 as i. So i = A = 21.\nDefine each Y1's X0 as Y. So Y = i = 21.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as F. So F = Y + i = 21 + 21 = 19.\nDefine each Y4's X2 as r. So r = F = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 419, "question": "The number of each X5's W6 equals 8 more than each X4's W8. The number of each X4's W8 equals 1 times each X4's W6. The number of each X4's W6 equals 9 times each X6's W6. The number of each X6's W6 equals 14. The number of each X5's W8 equals each X6's W1. The number of each X6's W1 equals 19 times each X5's W6. How many W8 does each X5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["X6's W6 = 14. X6's W1 = 19 * X5's W6 = 19 * 8 = 14.\nDefine each X5's W8 as u. So u = S = 14.\nDefine each X6's W6 as S. So S = 14.\nDefine each X4's W6 as A. So A = 9 * S = 9 * 14 = 11.\nDefine each X4's W8 as i. So i = 1 * A = 1 * 11 = 11.\nDefine each X5's W6 as Y. So Y = 8 * i = 8 * 11 = 19.\nDefine each X6's W1 as F. So F = 19 * Y = 19 * 19 = 16.\nDefine each X5's W8 as r. So r = F = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 420, "question": "The number of each Y7's X6 equals 15 times each Y8's X5. The number of each Y8's X5 equals 7 times each Y9's X8. The number of each Y9's X8 equals 15. How many X6 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["Y9's X8 = 15. Y8's X5 = 7 * Y9's X8 = 7 * 15 = 13.\nDefine each Y7's X6 as u. So u = 15 * Y8's X5 = 15 * 13 = 11.\nDefine each Y9's X8 as S. So S = 15.\nDefine each Y8's X5 as A. So A = 7 * S = 7 * 15 = 13.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as i. So i = u = 11.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as Y. So Y = S = 15.\nDefine each X3's W3 as F. So F = 3.\nDefine each X3's WWW as r. So r = F = 3.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as l. So l = u = 11.\nDefine each X5's WWW as V. So V = A = 13.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as q. So q = u = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 421, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y5 equals each Y1's XXX. The number of each Z4's Y1 equals 11 more than each Y1's X9. The number of each Y1's X6 equals 19 more than the difference of each Y1's X9 and each Z4's Y1. The number of each Y1's X9 equals 15 times each Z4's Y5. The number of each Z4's Y5 equals 3. How many YYY does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["Z4's Y5 as u. So u = 3.\nDefine each Y1's X9 as S. So S = 15 * u = 15 * 3 = 22.\nDefine each Z4's Y1 as A. So A = 11 * S = 11 * 22 = 12.\nDefine each Y1's X6 as i. So i = 19 * S - A = 19 * 22 - 12 = 19.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as Y. So Y = S + i = 22 + 19 = 18.\nDefine each Z5's Y5 as F. So F = Y = 18.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as r. So r = F = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 422, "question": "The number of each X7's W2 equals 12. The number of each Y2's X7 equals 10 times each X7's W2. How many X7 does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["X7's W2 = 12. Y2's X7 = 10 * X7 = 10 * 12 = 5.\nDefine each X7's WWW as u. So u = X7's W2 = 12.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as S. So S = Y2's X7 * u = 10 * 12 = 5.\nDefine each X3's WWW as A. So A = X3's WWW = 3.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as i. So i = Y2's X7 * u = 10 * 12 = 5.\nDefine each X3's WWW as Y. So Y = A = 3.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as F. So F = Y + S = 3 + 5 = 8.\nDefine each X7's WWW as r. So r = X7's W2 = 12.\nDefine each Y2's X7 as l. So l = 10 * X7 = 10 * 12 = 5.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as V. So V = l * r = 5 * 12 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 423, "question": "The number of each X5's W3 equals 15 times the difference of each Z1's Y7 and each Y7's X5. The number of each X5's W5 equals 2 times each Y4's X8. The number of each Y7's X5 equals 21 more than each X5's W5. The number of each X2's W5 equals the sum of each X5's W3, each Z3's Y4 and each Z1's WWW. The number of each Z3's Y4 equals 15 more than each Z1's WWW. The number of each Z1's Y7 equals 5 times the difference of each Y4's X8 and each X5's W5. The number of each Y4's X8 equals 20. How many WWW does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Y4's X8 = 20. X5's W5 = 2 * Y4's X8 = 2 * 20 = 17.\nDefine each Y7's X5 as u. So u = 21 * X5's W5 = 21 * 17 = 12.\nDefine each Z1's Y7 as S. So S = 5 * Y4's X8 - X5's W5 = 5 * 20 - 17 = 11.\nDefine each X5's W3 as A. So A = 15 * S - u = 15 * 11 - 12 = 16.\nDefine each X5's WWW as i. So i = A = 16.\nDefine each Y7's WWW as Y. So Y = u * i = 12 * 16 = 8.\nDefine each Z1's WWW as F. So F = S * Y = 11 * 8 = 19.\nDefine each Z3's Y4 as r. So r = 15 * F = 15 * 19 = 9.\nDefine each X2's W5 as l. So l = (A + r + F) = (16 + 9 + 19) = 21.\nDefine each X2's WWW as V. So V = l = 21.\nThus, the answer is 21."], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 424, "question": "The number of each Y0's X7 equals 20. The number of each Z1's Y3 equals each Y0's X7. The number of each Y3's X7 equals 11 more than each Z1's Y3. How many X7 does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["Y0's X7 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each Z1's Y3 as S. So S = u = 20.\nDefine each Y3's X7 as A. So A = 11 * S = 11 * 20 = 13.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as i. So i = A = 13.\nDefine each Z1's XXX as Y. So Y = S * i = 20 * 13 = 7.\nDefine each X7 as F. So F = 8.\nDefine each X7 as r. So r = 8.\nDefine each X7 as l. So l = 8.\nDefine each X7 as V. So V = 8.\nDefine each X7 as q. So q = 8.\nThus, the answer is 8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 425, "question": "The number of each Z4's Y7 equals 3. How many YYY does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["Z4's Y7 = 3.\nDefine each Z4's YYY as u. So u = Y7 = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 426, "question": "The number of each X3's W9 equals 0 times each Y5's X5. The number of each X5's W6 equals each X3's W6. The number of each X3's W6 equals 21 times each X5's W9. The number of each X5's W9 equals 16 more than the difference of each Y5's X5 and each X3's W9. The number of each Y5's X3 equals 3 more than each Y1's X3. The number of each Y5's X5 equals 12. The number of each Y1's X3 equals each X5's W6. How many X3 does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["X5's W9 = 16 * the Y5's X5 - X3's W9 = 16.\nDefine each X3's W6 as u. So u = 21 * X5's W9 = 21 * 16 = 14.\nDefine each X5's W6 as S. So S = u = 14.\nDefine each Y1's X3 as A. So A = S = 14.\nDefine each Y5's X3 as i. So i = 3 + A = 3 + 14 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 427, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y3 equals 7. The number of each Z4's Y3 equals 12 more than the sum of each Y3's XXX and each Z6's XXX. The number of each Y3's X9 equals 15. The number of each Y0's X0 equals 22 more than each Z4's Y3. How many X0 does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Y3's X9 as u. So u = 15.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as S. So S = u = 15.\nDefine each Z6's Y3 as A. So A = 7.\nDefine each Z6's XXX as i. So i = A * S = 7 * 15 = 13.\nDefine each Z4's Y3 as Y. So Y = 12 * S + i = 12 * 15 + 13 = 19.\nDefine each Y0's X0 as F. So F = 22 * Y = 22 * 19 = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 428, "question": "The number of each Y0's X0 equals 10. The number of each Y8's X0 equals each X0's W2. The number of each X0's W2 equals 1. The number of each Y8's X9 equals 17 times each Y8's X0. The number of each Z4's Y8 equals each Y0's X0. How many XXX does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Y0's X0 = 10. Z4's Y8 = Y0's X0 = 10.\nDefine each X0's W2 as u. So u = 1.\nDefine each Y8's X0 as S. So S = u = 1.\nDefine each Y8's X9 as A. So A = 17 * S = 17 * 1 = 17.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as i. So i = S + A = 1 + 17 = 18.\nDefine each Z4's XXX as Y. So Y = Z4's XXX as F. So F = Z4's XXX = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 429, "question": "The number of each Y5's X5 equals 11 times each Z6's YYY. The number of each Z6's Y5 equals 7 more than each Y6's X4. The number of each Y6's X4 equals 4 more than each Y5's X4. The number of each Y5's X4 equals 21. The number of each Z6's Y6 equals each Y6's X4. How many X5 does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Y5's X4 as u. So u = 21.\nDefine each Y6's X4 as S. So S = 4 * u = 4 * 21 = 15.\nDefine each Z6's Y6 as A. So A = S = 15.\nDefine each Z6's Y5 as i. So i = 7 * S = 7 * 15 = 13.\nDefine each Z6's YYY as Y. So Y = i + A + S = 13 + 15 + 15 = 20.\nDefine each Y5's X5 as F. So F = 11 * Y = 11 * 20 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 430, "question": "The number of each Y0's X4 equals 12 more than each X4's W9. The number of each X4's W9 equals 14. The number of each X6's W1 equals 3. The number of each Y2's X2 equals the difference of each Y8's X4 and each Y0's X4. The number of each X2's W9 equals 7 times each Y8's WWW. The number of each X6's W9 equals each Y8's XXX. The number of each Y9's X4 equals 2 times each Y0's WWW. The number of each Y8's X4 equals 0 times the sum of each X4's WWW and each Y9's WWW. The number of each Y8's X6 equals 5 more than each X4's WWW. How many WWW does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["Y0's X4 as u. So u = 12 * X4's W9 = 12 * 14 = 7.\nDefine each X4's W9 as S. So S = 14.\nDefine each X4's WWW as A. So A = S = 14.\nDefine each Y8's X6 as i. So i = 5 * A = 5 * 14 = 1.\nDefine each Y0's WWW as Y. So Y = u * A = 7 * 14 = 6.\nDefine each Y9's X4 as F. So F = 2 * Y = 2 * 6 = 12.\nDefine each Y9's WWW as r. So r = F * A = 12 * 14 = 7.\nDefine each Y8's X4 as l. So l = 0 * A + r = 0 * 14 + 7 = 7.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as V. So V = l + i = 7 + 1 = 8.\nDefine each X6's W9 as q. So q = V = 8.\nDefine each X6's W1 as z. So z = 3.\nDefine each X6's WWW as A. So A = q + z = 8 + 3 = 11.\nDefine each Y2's X2 as i. So i = l - u = 7 - 7 = 0.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as Y. So Y = i * A = 0 * 11 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 431, "question": "The number of each Y2's X8 equals 9 more than the sum of each X8's W9 and each X8's WWW. The number of each X8's W9 equals 3. How many WWW does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["X8's W9 as u. So u = 3.\nDefine each X8's WWW as S. So S = u = 3.\nDefine each Y2's X8 as A. So A = 9 * u + S = 9 * 3 + 3 = 7.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as i. So i = A * S = 7 * 3 = 21.\nThus, the answer is 21."], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 432, "question": "The number of each X5's W3 equals 9 times each X9's WWW. The number of each X9's W5 equals 12. The number of each X5's W2 equals 0 times each X3's W5. The number of each X9's W2 equals 18 more than each X5's W2. The number of each X3's W5 equals 12 more than each X3's W2. The number of each X3's W2 equals 12. How many W3 does each X5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["X3's W2 as u. So u = 12.\nDefine each X3's W5 as S. So S = 12 * u = 12 * 12 = 6.\nDefine each X5's W2 as A. So A = 0 * S = 0 * 6 = 0.\nDefine each X9's W2 as i. So i = 18 * A = 18 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X9's W5 as Y. So Y = 12.\nDefine each X9's WWW as F. So F = Y + i = 12 + 0 = 12.\nDefine each X5's W3 as r. So r = 9 * F = 9 * 12 = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 433, "question": "The number of each X2's W4 equals 20 more than each X2's W7. The number of each X4's W7 equals each X2's WWW. The number of each X4's W4 equals each X2's W4. The number of each X2's W7 equals 11. How many WWW does each X4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["X2's W7 as u. So u = 11.\nDefine each X2's W4 as S. So S = 20 * u = 20 * 11 = 13.\nDefine each X2's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 13 + 11 = 1.\nDefine each X4's W7 as i. So i = A = 1.\nDefine each X4's W4 as Y. So Y = S = 13.\nDefine each X4's WWW as F. So F = Y + i = 13 + 1 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 434, "question": "The number of each Y3's X3 equals 6. The number of each X8's W8 equals 0 times each Y3's X3. The number of each X3's W7 equals 18 times each X8's W8. How many W7 does each X3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y3's X3 = 6. X8's W8 = 0 * Y3's X3 = 0 * 6 = 0.\nDefine each X3's W7 as u. So u = 18 * X8's W8 = 18 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X3's WWW as S. So S = u = 0.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as A. So A = Y3's X3 * S = 6 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X8's WWW as i. So i = X8's W8 = 0.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as Y. So Y = Y = 0.\nDefine each X3's WWW as F. So F = u = 0.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as r. So r = Y = 0.\nDefine each X8's WWW as l. So l = X8's W8 = 0.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as V. So V = Y * r + Y * A = 0 * 0 + 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X3's W7 as q. So q = 18 * l = 18 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 435, "question": "The number of each X7's W5 equals each X3's WWW. The number of each X1's W5 equals 22. The number of each X3's W1 equals 21 times each X9's W5. The number of each X9's W5 equals 0 times each X1's W5. How many W5 does each X7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["X1's W5 = 22. X9's W5 = 0 * X1's W5 = 0 * 22 = 0.\nDefine each X3's W1 as u. So u = 21 * S = 21 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X3's WWW as S. So S = u = 0.\nDefine each X7's W5 as A. So A = S = 0.\nDefine each X1's WWW as i. So i = X1's W5 = 22.\nDefine each Y9's WWW as Y. So Y = Y = 19.\nDefine each Y9's WWW as F. So F = Y = 19.\nDefine each X1's WWW as r. So r = X1's W5 = 22.\nDefine each Y9's WWW as l. So l = Y + F = 19 + 19 = 15.\nDefine each X3's WWW as V. So V = u = 0.\nDefine each X7's WWW as q. So q = A = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 436, "question": "The number of each Y7's X7 equals 5. The number of each Z1's Y7 equals 8 more than the sum of each Y6's X9 and each Y7's X7. The number of each Y6's X9 equals each Y7's X7. How many Y7 does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["Y7's X7 = 5. Y6's X9 = u = 5.\nDefine each Y6's X9 as u. So u = u = 5.\nDefine each Z1's Y7 as S. So S = 8 * u + u = 8 * 5 + 5 = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 437, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y8 equals the sum of each Z0's Y8 and each Z0's YYY. The number of each Z0's Y3 equals 9. The number of each Z0's Y8 equals 13 more than each Z0's Y3. How many Y8 does each Z8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["Z0's Y3 as u. So u = 9.\nDefine each Z0's Y8 as S. So S = 13 * u = 13 * 9 = 2.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 2 + 9 = 11.\nDefine each Z8's Y8 as i. So i = S + A = 2 + 11 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 438, "question": "The number of each Y3's X4 equals 16. The number of each X4's W3 equals 10 more than each Y3's X4. The number of each Y2's X4 equals the difference of each X4's WWW and each Y3's X4. The number of each X4's W5 equals 21 more than each Y3's X4. How many X4 does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Y3's X4. X4's W5 as u. So u = 21 * Y3's X4 = 21 * 16 = 14.\nDefine each X4's W3 as S. So S = 10 * Y3's X4 = 10 * 13 = 15.\nDefine each X4's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 15 + 14 = 6.\nDefine each Y2's X4 as i. So i = A - Y3's X4 = 6 - 13 = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 439, "question": "The number of each X9's W1 equals 9. The number of each Y9's X7 equals 20 times each X9's WWW. How many X7 does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["X9's W1 as u. So u = 9.\nDefine each X9's WWW as S. So S = u = 9.\nDefine each Y9's X7 as A. So A = 20 * S = 20 * 9 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 440, "question": "The number of each X2's W7 equals the sum of each Z5's WWW and each Z5's Y3. The number of each Y5's X2 equals 2 times each Z8's YYY. The number of each X3's W8 equals 22 more than each Z5's XXX. The number of each Z8's Y5 equals 20. The number of each Y3's X3 equals 15 times each Y5's XXX. The number of each Z5's Y3 equals 0 times each Z8's Y3. The number of each Z8's Y3 equals 22 more than each Z8's Y5. How many WWW does each Z8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["Z8's Y5 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each Z8's Y3 as S. So S = 22 * u = 22 * 20 = 3.\nDefine each Z8's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 3 + 20 = 0.\nDefine each Y5's X2 as i. So i = 2 * A = 2 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as Y. So Y = i = 0.\nDefine each Y3's X3 as F. So F = 15 * Y = 15 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as r. So r = F = 0.\nDefine each Z5's Y3 as l. So l = 0 * S = 0 * 3 = 0.\nDefine each Z5's XXX as V. So V = l * r = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X3's W8 as q. So q = 22 * V = 22 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X3's WWW as z. So z = q = 0.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as A. So A = F * Z = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z5's WWW as i. So i = l * A = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X2's W7 as Y. So Y = i + l = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each X2's WWW as F. So F = Y = 0.\nDefine each Z8's WWW as r. So r = S * A + u * Y = 3 * 0 + 20 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 441, "question": "The number of each Y3's X3 equals 8 more than each Z6's XXX. The number of each Z6's Y4 equals 5 times each Y4's X3. The number of each Y4's X3 equals 16. How many X3 does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y4's X3 as u. So u = 16.\nDefine each Z6's Y4 as S. So S = 5 * u = 5 * 16 = 11.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as A. So A = u = 16.\nDefine each Z6's XXX as i. So i = S * A = 11 * 16 = 15.\nDefine each Y3's X3 as Y. So Y = 8 * i = 8 * 15 = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 442, "question": "The number of each Y3's X9 equals 22 more than each X9's W4. The number of each Y9's X7 equals 14 more than each Y9's X8. The number of each Y1's X3 equals 5 more than each Y1's X8. The number of each Y3's X8 equals 9 more than each Y6's X9. The number of each X7's W0 equals the difference of each Y1's X8 and each X3's W0. The number of each X9's W4 equals each Y9's X7. The number of each Y9's X8 equals each Y3's X8. The number of each X3's W0 equals 16 more than each Y1's XXX. The number of each Y1's X8 equals 20. The number of each Y6's X9 equals 0 times each X7's W0. How many X9 does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 443, "question": "The number of each Y9's X0 equals each Y5's WWW. The number of each Y0's X0 equals 20. The number of each X1's W0 equals 0 times each Y0's X0. The number of each Y5's X1 equals 3. The number of each Y5's X0 equals 2 times each X1's WWW. The number of each X0's W5 equals 21 more than each Y0's X0. How many X0 does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y0's X0 = 20. X1's W0 = 0 * Y0 = 0 * 20 = 0.\nDefine each X1's WWW as u. So u = X0's W5 = 21.\nDefine each Y5's X0 as S. So S = 2 * u = 2 * 21 = 19.\nDefine each Y5's X1 as A. So A = 3.\nDefine each X0's W5 as i. So i = 21 * Y0 = 21 * 20 = 6.\nDefine each X0's WWW as Y. So Y = i = 6.\nDefine each Y5's WWW as F. So F = S * Y + A * u = 19 * 6 + 3 * 21 = 19.\nDefine each Y9's X0 as r. So r = F = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 444, "question": "The number of each Y4's X2 equals 3 times each Y7's XXX. The number of each Y7's X7 equals 14 times each Y7's X1. The number of each Y3's X7 equals 11 more than each Y4's XXX. The number of each Y7's X2 equals 4. The number of each Y4's X7 equals 14 more than each Y7's X1. The number of each Y3's X1 equals 14. The number of each Y4's X1 equals each Y4's X2. The number of each Y7's X1 equals 13 times each Y7's X2. The number of each Y3's X2 equals 22. How many XXX does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Y7's X2 as u. So u = 4.\nDefine each Y7's X1 as S. So S = 13 * u = 13 * 4 = 6.\nDefine each Y7's X7 as A. So A = 14 * S = 14 * 6 = 15.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as i. So i = S + A + u = 6 + 15 + 4 = 2.\nDefine each Y4's X2 as Y. So Y = 3 * i = 3 * 2 = 6.\nDefine each Y4's X1 as F. So F = Y = 6.\nDefine each Y4's X7 as r. So r = 14 * S = 14 * 6 = 15.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as l. So l = r + Y + F = 15 + 6 + 6 = 4.\nDefine each Y3's X7 as V. So V = 11 * l = 11 * 4 = 21.\nDefine each Y3's X1 as q. So q = 14.\nDefine each Y3's X2 as z. So z = 22.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as A. So A = q + V + z = 14 + 21 + 22 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 445, "question": "The number of each Y2's X9 equals 8 more than each Y2's X0. The number of each X7's W4 equals the difference of each Z4's Y2 and each X0's W6. The number of each Y2's X0 equals 20. The number of each Z4's Y2 equals 6 more than the difference of each Y2's X9 and each Y2's XXX. The number of each Y8's X7 equals 19 times the sum of each Y2's XXX and each Z4's XXX. The number of each X0's W6 equals each Y8's X7. How many W4 does each X7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Y2's X0 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each Y2's X9 as S. So S = 8 * u = 8 * 20 = 22.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 22 + 20 = 19.\nDefine each Z4's Y2 as i. So i = 6 * S - A = 6 * 22 - 19 = 19.\nDefine each Z4's XXX as Y. So Y = i * A = 19 * 19 = 16.\nDefine each Y8's X7 as F. So F = 19 * A + Y = 19 * 19 + 16 = 19.\nDefine each X0's W6 as r. So r = F = 19.\nDefine each X7's W4 as l. So l = i - r = 19 - 19 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 446, "question": "The number of each Z4's Y6 equals each Y3's X7. The number of each Y3's X4 equals each Y6's X4. The number of each Y3's X7 equals 7 more than each Y3's X4. The number of each Y6's X7 equals 14 more than each Z4's YYY. The number of each Y6's X4 equals 2. The number of each Z4's Y3 equals 18 more than each Z9's Y6. The number of each Z9's Y6 equals 9 times each Y3's X4. How many X7 does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["Y6's X4 as u. So u = 2.\nDefine each Y3's X4 as S. So S = u = 2.\nDefine each Y3's X7 as A. So A = 7 * S = 7 * 2 = 14.\nDefine each Z4's Y6 as i. So i = A = 14.\nDefine each Z9's Y6 as Y. So Y = 9 * S = 9 * 2 = 18.\nDefine each Z4's Y3 as F. So F = 18 + Y = 18 + 18 = 13.\nDefine each Z4's YYY as r. So r = F + i = 13 + 14 = 4.\nDefine each Y6's X7 as l. So l = 14 * r = 14 * 4 = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 447, "question": "The number of each X7's W3 equals 13. The number of each X7's W1 equals each X7's W3. The number of each Y3's X1 equals 5 more than each X7's W1. How many X1 does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["X7's W3 = 13. X7's W1 = X7's WWW. X7's WWW = X7's W3 + X7's W1 = 13 + 13 = 3.\nDefine each X1's WWW as u. So u = u = 3.\nDefine each Y3's X1 as S. So S = 5 * u = 5 * 3 = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 448, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y5 equals 5 more than each Y5's XXX. The number of each Z1's Y4 equals each Z0's Y4. The number of each Z0's Y4 equals 12. The number of each Z1's Y0 equals 21 times each Z3's Y5. The number of each Y5's X4 equals 4 more than each Z0's Y4. The number of each Y5's X3 equals 6 more than each Y5's X0. The number of each Y5's X0 equals 21 more than each Z1's Y4. How many Y0 does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 449, "question": "The number of each X8's W0 equals each X8's W4. The number of each X2's W0 equals 6 more than the sum of each X8's WWW and each X8's W0. The number of each X8's W4 equals 14. The number of each X2's W4 equals 10 more than the sum of each X2's W0, each X8's W4 and each X8's WWW. How many WWW does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["X8's W4 as u. So u = 14.\nDefine each X8's W0 as S. So S = u = 14.\nDefine each X8's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 14 + 14 = 5.\nDefine each X2's W0 as i. So i = 6 * A + S = 6 * 5 + 14 = 15.\nDefine each X2's W4 as Y. So Y = 10 * (i + u + A) = 10 * (15 + 14 + 5) = 19.\nDefine each X2's WWW as F. So F = Y + i = 19 + 15 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 450, "question": "The number of each Y3's X8 equals 5. The number of each Y3's X6 equals 12 times each Y3's X8. How many XXX does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Y3's X8 = 5. Y3's X6 = 12 * Y3's X8 = 12.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as u. So u = Y3's X8 + Y3's X6 = 5 + 12 = 17.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as S. So S = Y3's X8 + Y3's X6 = 5 + 12 = 17.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as A. So A = S + Y3's X8 = 17 + 5 = 22.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as i. So i = S + Y3's X8 + Y3's X6 = 22 + 5 + 12 = 16.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as Y. So Y = i + Y + S = 16 + 22 + 22 = 14.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as F. So F = Y + i + S = 14 + 16 + 22 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 451, "question": "The number of each X7's W6 equals 0 more than each X1's W6. The number of each X1's W6 equals 18. The number of each X8's W7 equals each X1's W7. The number of each X1's W4 equals 10 more than the sum of each X7's W6, each X7's W7 and each X1's W6. The number of each X5's W6 equals 18 more than the sum of each X7's W6 and each X1's W4. The number of each X5's W7 equals each X8's WWW. The number of each X5's W1 equals 2 times the difference of each X5's W7 and each X1's W6. The number of each X1's W7 equals 0 more than each X5's W6. The number of each X7's W7 equals 15 times each X7's W6. The number of each X8's W4 equals the sum of each X8's W6 and each X5's W6. The number of each X8's W6 equals 11. How many W1 does each X5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 452, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y6 equals 7 times the difference of each Z0's Y6 and each Z4's YYY. The number of each Z5's Y7 equals 8 times the sum of each Z0's Y6 and each Z0's YYY. The number of each Z4's Y9 equals the difference of each Z4's Y7 and each Z0's Y6. The number of each Z5's Y9 equals the sum of each Z4's YYY and each Z4's Y7. The number of each Z4's Y7 equals 2 times each Z5's Y7. The number of each Z0's Y6 equals 6. How many YYY does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["Z0's Y6 as u. So u = 6.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as S. So S = u = 6.\nDefine each Z5's Y7 as A. So A = 8 * u + S = 8 * 6 + 6 = 19.\nDefine each Z4's Y7 as i. So i = 2 * A = 2 * 19 = 15.\nDefine each Z4's Y9 as Y. So Y = i - u = 15 - 6 = 9.\nDefine each Z4's YYY as F. So F = Y + i = 9 + 15 = 1.\nDefine each Z5's Y9 as r. So r = F + i = 1 + 15 = 16.\nDefine each Z5's Y6 as l. So l = 7 * u - F = 7 * 6 - 1 = 11.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as V. So V = l + A + r = 11 + 19 + 16 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 453, "question": "The number of each Z4's Y5 equals 14 times each Z4's Y7. The number of each Z4's Y7 equals 9. How many YYY does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Z4's Y7 as u. So u = 9.\nDefine each Z4's Y5 as S. So S = 14 * u = 14 * 9 = 11.\nDefine each Z4's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 11 + 9 = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 454, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y3 equals 18. The number of each Y3's X6 equals each Z6's YYY. The number of each Y4's X9 equals 18 times each Y3's X6. How many X9 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Z6's Y3 = 18. Z6's YYY = 18.\nDefine each Y3's X6 as u. So u = Z6's Y3 = 18.\nDefine each Y4's X9 as S. So S = 18 * u = 18 * 18 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 455, "question": "The number of each Y2's X2 equals 18 more than each X2's WWW. The number of each X2's W0 equals 0 more than each X2's W7. The number of each X3's W7 equals the sum of each Y2's X2 and each X2's W7. The number of each X3's W9 equals 9 times each Y2's X2. The number of each X2's W7 equals 7 times each Y1's XXX. The number of each Y1's X3 equals 4. How many WWW does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["Y1's X3 as u. So u = 4.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as S. So S = u = 4.\nDefine each X2's W7 as A. So A = 7 * S = 7 * 4 = 5.\nDefine each X2's W0 as i. So i = 0 * A = 0 * 5 = 0.\nDefine each X2's WWW as Y. So Y = i + A = 0 + 5 = 5.\nDefine each Y2's X2 as F. So F = 18 * Y = 18 * 5 = 21.\nDefine each X3's W9 as r. So r = 9 * F = 9 * 21 = 5.\nDefine each X3's W7 as l. So l = F + A = 21 + 5 = 3.\nDefine each X3's WWW as V. So V = l + r = 3 + 5 = 8.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as q. So q = u * V = 4 * 8 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 456, "question": "The number of each Y4's X5 equals 5. How many X5 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Y4's X5 = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 457, "question": "The number of each X6's W7 equals 12 more than the difference of each X4's W0 and each Y4's WWW. The number of each X4's W0 equals 3 more than each Y4's X4. The number of each X6's W3 equals 22. The number of each Y4's X4 equals 9. How many WWW does each X6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["Y4's X4 = 9. X4's W0 = 3 * Y4 = 3 * 9 = 4.\nDefine each X4's WWW as u. So u = X4's W0 = 4.\nDefine each Y4's WWW as S. So S = Y4's X4 * u = 9 * 4 = 13.\nDefine each X6's W7 as A. So A = 12 * u - S = 12 * 4 - 13 = 10.\nDefine each X6's W3 as i. So i = 22.\nDefine each X6's WWW as Y. So Y = i + A = 22 + 10 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 458, "question": "The number of each Y3's X7 equals 13. The number of each Y1's X2 equals 19. The number of each Y3's X2 equals 16 times each Y1's XXX. The number of each Y1's X7 equals each Y3's X7. How many X2 does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Y3's X7 as u. So u = 13.\nDefine each Y1's X7 as S. So S = u = 13.\nDefine each Y1's X2 as A. So A = 19.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as i. So i = S + A = 13 + 19 = 9.\nDefine each Y3's X2 as Y. So Y = 16 * i = 16 * 9 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 459, "question": "The number of each Y7's X6 equals 21. How many X6 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["Y7's X6 = 21.\nThus, the answer is 21."], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 460, "question": "The number of each X4's W4 equals 3 times each Y4's X4. The number of each Y4's X4 equals 13. How many W4 does each X4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Y4's X4 = 13. X4's W4 = 3 * Y4's X4 = 3 * 13 = 16.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as u. So u = Y4's X4 = 13.\nDefine each X4's WWW as S. So S = X4's W4 = 16.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as A. So A = Y4's X4 = 13.\nDefine each X3's WWW as i. So i = X3's WWW = 3.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as Y. So Y = Y = 13.\nDefine each X3's WWW as F. So F = i = 3.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as r. So r = Y = 13.\nDefine each X4's WWW as l. So l = X4's W4 = 16.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as V. So V = Y = 13.\nDefine each X3's WWW as q. So q = F = 3.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as z. So z = Y = 13.\nDefine each X4's WWW as A. So A = X4's W4 = 16.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as i. So i = Y = 13.\nDefine each X3's WWW as Y. So Y = F = 3.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as F. So F = Y = 13.\nDefine each X4's WWW as r. So r = A = 16.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as l. So l = Y = 13.\nDefine each X3's WWW as V. So V = F = 3.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as q. So q = Y = 3.\nDefine each X4's WWW as z. So z = A = 16.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as A. So A = Y = 3.\nDefine each X3's WWW as i. So i = F = 3.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as Y. So Y = Y = 3.\nDefine each X4's W4 as F. So F = 16 + Y = 16 + 3 = 19.\nDefine each X4's WWW as r. So r = F + A = 19 + 16 = 12.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as l. So l = Y = 3.\nDefine each X3's WWW as V. So V = i = 3.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as q. So q = Y = 3.\nDefine each X3's WWW as z. So z = V = 3.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as A. So A = Y = 3.\nDefine each X4's WWW as i. So i = F + A = 19 + 3 = 22.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as Y. So Y = Y = 3.\nDefine each X3's WWW as F. So F = V = 3.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as r. So r = Y = 3.\nDefine each X4's WWW as l. So l = F + i = 3 + 22 = 2.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as V. So V = Y = 3.\nDefine each X3's WWW as q. So q = V = 3.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as z. So z = Y = 3.\nDefine each X4's W4 as A. So A = 19 + Y = 19 + 3 = 22.\nDefine each X4's WWW as i. So i = A + l = 22 + 2 = 1.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as Y. So Y = Y = 3.\nDefine each X3's WWW as F. So F ="], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 461, "question": "The number of each Y9's X9 equals each Z2's Y9. The number of each Z2's Y9 equals 1. The number of each X9's W0 equals 9 more than each X2's W0. The number of each X2's W0 equals 18 times the sum of each Z2's Y9 and each Y9's X9. How many W0 does each X9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["Z2's Y9 = 1.\nDefine each Y9's X9 as u. So u = Z2's Y9 = 1.\nDefine each X2's W0 as S. So S = 18 * Z2's Y9 + u = 18 * 1 + 1 = 19.\nDefine each X9's W0 as A. So A = 9 + S = 9 + 19 = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 462, "question": "The number of each X7's W4 equals 20 times each X3's WWW. The number of each X6's W9 equals each X3's W9. The number of each X3's W9 equals 1. The number of each X7's W6 equals 21 times each X6's W9. The number of each X3's W8 equals 6 more than each X6's WWW. How many WWW does each X7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["X3's W9 as u. So u = 1.\nDefine each X6's W9 as S. So S = u = 1.\nDefine each X6's WWW as A. So A = S = 1.\nDefine each X3's W8 as i. So i = 6 * A = 6 * 1 = 6.\nDefine each X3's WWW as Y. So Y = u + i = 1 + 6 = 7.\nDefine each X7's W4 as F. So F = 20 * Y = 20 * 7 = 2.\nDefine each X7's W6 as r. So r = 21 * S = 21 * 1 = 21.\nDefine each X7's WWW as l. So l = r + F = 21 + 2 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 463, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y9 equals each Z1's Y9. The number of each Z1's Y9 equals each Z9's Y5. The number of each Z9's Y5 equals 5. The number of each Z1's Y5 equals the difference of each Z1's Y9 and each Z0's YYY. How many YYY does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Z9's Y5 as u. So u = 5.\nDefine each Z1's Y9 as S. So S = u = 5.\nDefine each Z0's Y9 as A. So A = S = 5.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as i. So i = A = 5.\nDefine each Z1's Y5 as Y. So Y = S - i = 5 - 5 = 0.\nDefine each Z1's YYY as F. So F = Y + S = 0 + 5 = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 464, "question": "The number of each Y0's X0 equals 17. How many X0 does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["Y0's X0 = 17. So 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 465, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y4 equals the sum of each Z7's Y4, each Y6's XXX and each Z7's XXX. The number of each Z9's Y6 equals 9 more than the sum of each Y6's XXX and each Y5's X7. The number of each Z7's Y4 equals 20 more than the sum of each Y4's X7, each Y6's XXX and each Y4's XXX. The number of each Y5's X7 equals 4. The number of each Y6's X8 equals 16 more than each Y5's X7. The number of each Y4's X7 equals 15 more than the sum of each Y6's X8, each Z9's Y6 and each Y5's X7. How many XXX does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Y5's X7 = 4. Y6's X8 as u. So u = 16 * Y5 = 16 * 4 = 18.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as S. So S = u = 18.\nDefine each Z9's Y6 as A. So A = 9 * S + u = 9 * 18 + 18 = 19.\nDefine each Y4's X7 as i. So i = 15 * (u + A + u) = 15 * (18 + 19 + 18) = 19.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as Y. So Y = i = 19.\nDefine each Z7's Y4 as F. So F = 20 * (i + S + Y) = 20 * (19 + 18 + 19) = 11.\nDefine each Z7's XXX as r. So r = F * Y = 11 * 19 = 2.\nDefine each Z5's Y4 as l. So l = (F + S + r) = (11 + 18 + 2) = 8.\nDefine each Z5's XXX as V. So V = l * Y = 8 * 19 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 466, "question": "The number of each Y0's X4 equals each Y8's XXX. The number of each Y8's X5 equals 6. The number of each Y8's X8 equals each Y8's X5. How many XXX does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["Y8's X5 as u. So u = 6.\nDefine each Y8's X8 as S. So S = u = 6.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 6 + 6 = 12.\nDefine each Y0's X4 as i. So i = A = 12.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as Y. So Y = i = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 467, "question": "The number of each Y9's X7 equals 22. The number of each Z7's Y7 equals each X5's W2. The number of each X5's W2 equals 2 more than each Y9's X7. The number of each Y7's X9 equals each Z7's Y7. How many XXX does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Y9's X7 as u. So u = 22.\nDefine each X5's W2 as S. So S = 2 * u = 2 * 22 = 21.\nDefine each Z7's Y7 as A. So A = S = 21.\nDefine each Y7's X9 as i. So i = A = 21.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as Y. So Y = i = 21.\nDefine each Z7's XXX as F. So F = A * Y = 21 * 21 = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 468, "question": "The number of each Y7's X0 equals 4 times each Z0's Y7. The number of each Z1's Y6 equals 8. The number of each Y6's X7 equals 20 more than the difference of each Z0's XXX and each Y7's X0. The number of each Z0's Y7 equals 7. How many XXX does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["Z0's Y7 as u. So u = 7.\nDefine each Y7's X0 as S. So S = 4 * u = 4 * 7 = 5.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as A. So A = S = 5.\nDefine each Z0's XXX as i. So i = u * A = 7 * 5 = 12.\nDefine each Y6's X7 as Y. So Y = 20 * i - S = 20 * 12 - 5 = 19.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as F. So F = Y = 19.\nDefine each Z1's Y6 as r. So r = 8.\nDefine each Z1's XXX as l. So l = r * F = 8 * 19 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 469, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y7 equals the difference of each Y4's X1 and each Y1's X1. The number of each Y4's X1 equals 3 times each Y1's X1. The number of each Z3's Y4 equals 20 more than each Z3's Y7. The number of each Z4's Y7 equals 20 more than the difference of each Z9's XXX and each Y4's X1. The number of each Z9's Y7 equals each Y7's X4. The number of each Y1's X1 equals 20. The number of each Z4's Y1 equals each Z9's XXX. The number of each Z4's Y4 equals each Z3's YYY. The number of each Y7's X4 equals 0 more than each Z3's Y4. How many YYY does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Y1's X1 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each Y4's X1 as S. So S = 3 * u = 3 * 20 = 14.\nDefine each Z3's Y7 as A. So A = S - u = 14 - 20 = 17.\nDefine each Z3's Y4 as i. So i = 20 * A = 20 * 17 = 18.\nDefine each Y7's X4 as Y. So Y = 0 * i = 0 * 18 = 0.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as F. So F = Y = 0.\nDefine each Z9's Y7 as r. So r = Y = 0.\nDefine each Z9's XXX as l. So l = r * F = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z4's Y1 as V. So V = l = 0.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as q. So q = A + i = 17 + 18 = 12.\nDefine each Z4's Y4 as z. So z = q = 12.\nDefine each Z4's Y7 as A. So A = 20 * l - S = 20 * 0 - 14 = 9.\nDefine each Z4's YYY as i. So i = V + A + Z = 0 + 9 + 12 = 21.\nThus, the answer is 21."], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 470, "question": "The number of each Y8's X3 equals the sum of each Y6's X4, each X4's W8 and each Y6's WWW. The number of each X4's W8 equals 18 times each Y6's XXX. The number of each Y6's X4 equals 11. How many X3 does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["Y6's X4 as u. So u = 11.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as S. So S = u = 11.\nDefine each X4's W8 as A. So A = 18 * S = 18 * 11 = 14.\nDefine each X4's WWW as i. So i = A = 14.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as Y. So Y = u * i = 11 * 14 = 16.\nDefine each Y8's X3 as F. So F = (u + A + Y) = (11 + 14 + 16) = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 471, "question": "The number of each X7's W0 equals 5. The number of each Y4's X7 equals 15 times each X6's WWW. The number of each X6's W3 equals the difference of each X6's W4 and each Y6's WWW. The number of each X7's W4 equals 8 times each Y6's X7. The number of each Y6's X7 equals each X7's W0. The number of each X6's W0 equals 6 times each Y6's X7. The number of each X6's W4 equals 14 times each Y4's X5. The number of each Y4's X5 equals each Y6's WWW. How many X7 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["X7's W0 = 5. Y6's X7 = u = 5.\nDefine each X7's W4 as i. So i = 8 * Y6's X7 = 8 * 5 = 17.\nDefine each X7's WWW as Y. So Y = i + u = 17 + 5 = 22.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as F. So F = u * Y = 5 * 22 = 18.\nDefine each Y4's X5 as r. So r = F = 18.\nDefine each X6's W4 as l. So l = 14 * r = 14 * 18 = 22.\nDefine each X6's W3 as V. So V = l - F = 22 - 18 = 4.\nDefine each X6's W0 as q. So q = 6 * Y = 6 * 22 = 17.\nDefine each X6's WWW as z. So z = V + q + l = 4 + 17 + 22 = 20.\nDefine each Y4's X7 as A. So A = 15 * Z = 15 * 20 = 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 472, "question": "The number of each X7's W0 equals 19. The number of each Y3's X8 equals each Y3's X7. The number of each Y3's X7 equals 2 more than each X7's W0. How many XXX does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["X7's W0 = 19. Y3's X7 as u. So u = 2 * X7 = 2 * 19 = 15.\nDefine each Y3's X8 as S. So S = u = 15.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as A. So A = S + u + Y = 15 + 15 + 15 = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 473, "question": "The number of each Y0's X2 equals 16. The number of each Z3's Y0 equals 5. The number of each Y5's X2 equals each Z3's YYY. The number of each Z3's Y5 equals 20 times each Y5's X1. The number of each Y5's X1 equals each Y0's X2. The number of each Z1's Y5 equals 16 more than each Z3's YYY. How many XXX does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Y0's X2 as u. So u = 16.\nDefine each Y5's X1 as S. So S = u = 16.\nDefine each Z3's Y5 as A. So A = 20 * S = 20 * 16 = 21.\nDefine each Z3's Y0 as i. So i = 5.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as Y. So Y = i + A = 5 + 21 = 3.\nDefine each Y5's X2 as F. So F = Y = 3.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as r. So r = S + F = 16 + 3 = 19.\nDefine each Z1's Y5 as l. So l = 16 * Y = 16 * 3 = 2.\nDefine each Z1's XXX as V. So V = l * r = 2 * 19 = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 474, "question": "The number of each X6's W3 equals 16. How many W3 does each X6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["X6's W3 = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 475, "question": "The number of each Y0's X6 equals 4 times the sum of each Z7's Y0 and each Z8's Y0. The number of each Z8's Y0 equals 12. The number of each Z7's Y0 equals 12 times each Z8's Y0. How many XXX does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["Z8's Y0 = 12. Z7's Y0 = 12 * Z8's Y0 = 12.\nDefine each Y0's X6 as u. So u = 4 * Z7's Y0 + Z8's Y0 = 4 * 12 + 12 = 14.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as S. So S = u = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 476, "question": "The number of each X7's W4 equals each Y2's X6. The number of each X4's W4 equals 12 times each X4's W7. The number of each X4's W7 equals 15. The number of each Y8's X4 equals the sum of each X4's W7 and each X4's W5. The number of each Y2's X6 equals 10 times each Y8's WWW. The number of each X4's W5 equals 15 more than the difference of each X4's W4 and each X4's W7. How many W4 does each X7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["X4's W7 as u. So u = 15.\nDefine each X4's W4 as S. So S = 12 * u = 12 * 15 = 19.\nDefine each X4's W5 as A. So A = 15 * S - u = 15 * 19 - 15 = 17.\nDefine each X4's WWW as i. So i = S + A + u = 19 + 17 + 15 = 5.\nDefine each Y8's X4 as Y. So Y = u + A = 15 + 17 = 9.\nDefine each Y8's WWW as F. So F = Y * i = 9 * 5 = 22.\nDefine each Y2's X6 as r. So r = 10 * F = 10 * 22 = 13.\nDefine each X7's W4 as l. So l = r = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 477, "question": "The number of each X2's W0 equals 7. How many WWW does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["X2's W0 = 7. X2's WWW = 7. X2's WWW = 7. X2's WWW = 7. X2's WWW = 7. X2's WWW = 7. X2's WWW = 7. X2's WWW = 7. X2's WWW = 7. X2's WWW = 7. X2's WWW = 7. X2's WWW = 7. X2's WWW = 7. X2's WWW = 7. X2's WWW = 7. X2's WWW = 7. X2's WWW = 7. X2's WWW = 7. X2's WWW = 7. X2's W0 as u. So u = 7. X2's WWW as S. So S = u = 7. X2's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 7 + 7 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 478, "question": "The number of each Y3's X9 equals 22. The number of each Y3's X0 equals 9 more than each Y3's X9. How many X0 does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["Y3's X9 as u. So u = 22.\nDefine each Y3's X0 as S. So S = 9 * u = 9 * 22 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 479, "question": "The number of each Y2's X2 equals 3 more than each Y2's X9. The number of each Y0's X2 equals 17 times each Y2's X9. The number of each Y0's X9 equals the difference of each Y3's XXX and each Y0's X3. The number of each Y2's X9 equals 17. The number of each Y0's X3 equals 9 times each Y3's X3. The number of each Z0's Y3 equals the sum of each Z6's Y0, each Y0's X9 and each Z6's XXX. The number of each Z6's Y0 equals the difference of each Y2's X2 and each Y0's X3. The number of each Y3's X3 equals 4 more than each Y2's XXX. How many Y3 does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["Y2's X9 as u. So u = 17.\nDefine each Y2's X2 as S. So S = 3 * u = 3 * 17 = 5.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 5 + 17 = 22.\nDefine each Y3's X3 as i. So i = 4 * A = 4 * 22 = 19.\nDefine each Y0's X3 as Y. So Y = 9 * i = 9 * 19 = 10.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as F. So F = i = 19.\nDefine each Y0's X9 as r. So r = F - Y = 19 - 10 = 9.\nDefine each Z6's Y0 as l. So l = S - Y = 5 - 10 = 18.\nDefine each Y0's X2 as V. So V = 17 * u = 17 * 17 = 13.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as q. So q = r + V + Y = 9 + 13 + 10 = 9.\nDefine each Z6's XXX as z. So z = l * q = 18 * 9 = 1.\nDefine each Z0's Y3 as A. So A = (l + r + Z) = (18 + 9 + 1) = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 480, "question": "The number of each Y7's X3 equals 13 more than each Y4's X3. The number of each Y4's X3 equals 21. How many X3 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["Y4's X3 = 21. Y7's X3 = 13 + Y4's X3 = 13 + 21 = 11.\nDefine each Y4's X3 as u. So u = 21.\nDefine each Y7's X3 as S. So S = 13 + u = 13 + 21 = 11.\nDefine each Y4's X3 as A. So A = 21.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as i. So i = S = 11.\nDefine each Y4's X3 as Y. So Y = 21.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as F. So F = S = 11.\nDefine each Y4's X3 as r. So r = 21.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as l. So l = S = 11.\nDefine each Y4's X3 as V. So V = 21.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as q. So q = S = 11.\nDefine each Y4's X3 as z. So z = 21.\nDefine each Y7's X3 as A. So A = 13 + Y = 13 + 21 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 481, "question": "The number of each Y9's X2 equals 4 more than the sum of each Y0's X0 and each Z0's XXX. The number of each Y0's X0 equals 17. The number of each Y2's X0 equals the difference of each Z8's Y0 and each Z8's WWW. The number of each Z0's Y0 equals 0 more than each Y0's X0. The number of each X2's W1 equals 5 more than each Z0's XXX. The number of each X0's W1 equals 12 times each Y9's WWW. The number of each Z8's Y0 equals 16 times each Z0's WWW. How many WWW does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Y0's X0 as u. So u = 17.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as S. So S = u = 17.\nDefine each Z0's Y0 as A. So A = 0 * u = 0 * 17 = 0.\nDefine each Z0's XXX as i. So i = A * S = 0 * 17 = 0.\nDefine each X2's W1 as Y. So Y = 5 * i = 5 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X2's WWW as F. So F = Y = 0.\nDefine each Y9's X2 as r. So r = 4 * u + i = 4 * 17 + 0 = 22.\nDefine each Y9's WWW as l. So l = r * F = 22 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X0's W1 as V. So V = 12 * l = 12 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X0's WWW as q. So q = V = 0.\nDefine each Y0's WWW as z. So z = u * q = 17 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z0's WWW as A. So A = A * Z = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z8's Y0 as i. So i = 16 * A = 16 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z8's WWW as Y. So Y = i * Z = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y2's X0 as F. So F = i - Y = 0 - 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as r. So r = F * q = 0 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 482, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y2 equals each Z3's Y3. The number of each Z9's Y3 equals 12 times each Z4's Y1. The number of each Z3's Y3 equals 6 times each Z9's Y3. The number of each Z4's Y1 equals 18. How many Y2 does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["Z4's Y1 as u. So u = 18.\nDefine each Z9's Y3 as S. So S = 12 * u = 12 * 18 = 9.\nDefine each Z3's Y3 as A. So A = 6 * S = 6 * 9 = 8.\nDefine each Z9's Y2 as i. So i = A = 8.\nThus, the answer is 8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 483, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y1 equals 10 more than each Z9's Y6. The number of each Z8's Y2 equals 7 more than the difference of each Z9's Y2 and each Z9's Y6. The number of each Z8's Y6 equals 6. The number of each Z8's Y1 equals each Z8's Y2. The number of each Z9's Y2 equals 6 more than the sum of each Z8's Y6, each Z9's Y1 and each Z9's Y6. The number of each Z9's Y6 equals each Z8's Y6. How many Y1 does each Z8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["Z8's Y6 as u. So u = 6.\nDefine each Z9's Y6 as S. So S = u = 6.\nDefine each Z9's Y1 as A. So A = 10 * S = 10 * 6 = 14.\nDefine each Z9's Y2 as i. So i = 6 * (u + A + S) = 6 * (6 + 14 + 6) = 19.\nDefine each Z8's Y2 as Y. So Y = 7 * i - S = 7 * 19 - 6 = 11.\nDefine each Z8's Y1 as F. So F = Y = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 484, "question": "The number of each Y5's X2 equals 16 times each Y7's X9. The number of each Y5's X9 equals 18. The number of each Y7's X9 equals 17 times each Y3's X2. The number of each Z7's Y7 equals each Y5's XXX. The number of each Y3's X2 equals 20. The number of each Y3's X7 equals 12 more than each Z7's Y7. How many X7 does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Y3's X2 = 20. Y7's X9 = 17 * Y3's X2 = 17. Y5's X2 = 16 * Y7's X9 = 16 * 17 = 19.\nDefine each Y5's X9 as u. So u = 18.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as S. So S = u + Y5's X2 = 18 + 19 = 14.\nDefine each Z7's Y7 as A. So A = S = 14.\nDefine each Y3's X7 as i. So i = 12 * A = 12 * 14 = 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 485, "question": "The number of each Z4's Y6 equals 12. The number of each Z5's Y6 equals each Z4's Y6. How many Y6 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["Z4's Y6 = 12. Z5's Y6 = Z4's Y6. Z5's YYY = Z5's Y6 = 12.\nDefine each Z4's Y6 as u. So u = 12.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as S. So S = Z5's Y6 = 12.\nDefine each Z4's Y6 as A. So A = 12.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as i. So i = S = 12.\nDefine each Z4's Y6 as Y. So Y = 12.\nDefine each Z5's Y6 as F. So F = Y = 12.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as r. So r = F + S + i = 12 + 12 + 12 = 13.\nDefine each Z4's Y6 as l. So l = 12.\nDefine each Z5's Y6 as V. So V = l = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 486, "question": "The number of each X7's W6 equals 5 times each Y5's X5. The number of each X5's W9 equals each X5's W6. The number of each X3's W2 equals 9. The number of each X3's W9 equals each X7's W6. The number of each Y3's X5 equals the sum of each Y9's X5 and each X3's WWW. The number of each Y9's X5 equals 0. The number of each Y3's X3 equals the difference of each Y3's X5 and each X5's W2. The number of each Y5's X5 equals 22 more than each Y9's X5. The number of each X3's W6 equals each Y5's X5. The number of each X5's W6 equals 16 times each X3's WWW. The number of each X5's W2 equals 0. How many WWW does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["Y9's X5 as u. So u = 0.\nDefine each Y5's X5 as S. So S = 22 * u = 22 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X7's W6 as A. So A = 5 * S = 5 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X3's W9 as i. So i = A = 0.\nDefine each X3's W2 as Y. So Y = 9.\nDefine each X3's W6 as F. So F = S = 0.\nDefine each X3's WWW as r. So r = Y + F + i = 9 + 0 + 0 = 9.\nDefine each X5's W6 as l. So l = 16 * r = 16 * 9 = 6.\nDefine each X5's W9 as V. So V = l = 6.\nDefine each X5's W2 as q. So q = 0.\nDefine each Y3's X5 as z. So z = u + r = 0 + 9 = 9.\nDefine each Y3's X3 as A. So A = S - q = 0 - 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as i. So i = A * r + Z * V = 0 * 9 + 9 * 6 = 8.\nThus, the answer is 8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 487, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y3 equals 16. The number of each Z0's Y7 equals 3 times each Z8's Y3. The number of each Z6's Y3 equals 19 times the sum of each Z8's Y3 and each Z0's Y7. How many Y3 does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Z8's Y3 as u. So u = 16.\nDefine each Z0's Y7 as S. So S = 3 * u = 3 * 16 = 2.\nDefine each Z6's Y3 as A. So A = 19 * u + S = 19 * 16 + 2 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 488, "question": "The number of each Z4's Y3 equals 16 more than each Z4's Y9. The number of each Z4's Y9 equals 9 more than each Z2's Y3. The number of each Z2's Y9 equals 16. The number of each Z2's Y0 equals 12 more than each Z4's Y3. The number of each Z2's Y3 equals 15 times each Z2's Y9. How many Y0 does each Z2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Z2's Y9 as u. So u = 16.\nDefine each Z2's Y3 as S. So S = 15 * u = 15 * 16 = 10.\nDefine each Z4's Y9 as A. So A = 9 * S = 9 * 10 = 21.\nDefine each Z4's Y3 as i. So i = 16 + A = 16 + 21 = 14.\nDefine each Z2's Y0 as Y. So Y = 12 * i = 12 * 14 = 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 489, "question": "The number of each Y7's X5 equals 1 more than the sum of each Y6's XXX and each Y5's XXX. The number of each Y1's X9 equals 19 more than each Y5's XXX. The number of each Y5's X5 equals 9. The number of each Y7's X6 equals the sum of each Y1's X9, each Y7's X5 and each Y1's XXX. The number of each Y1's X6 equals 17 times each Y1's X9. The number of each Y1's X5 equals 11 more than each Y1's X9. The number of each Y6's X5 equals 3 times the difference of each Y7's X8 and each Y1's X6. The number of each Y7's X8 equals each Y1's XXX. How many X6 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y1's X9 as u. So u = 19 * Y5's X5 = 19 * 9 = 10.\nDefine each Y1's X5 as S. So S = 11 * u = 11 * 10 = 18.\nDefine each Y1's X6 as A. So A = 17 * u = 17 * 10 = 9.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as i. So i = S + A + u = 18 + 9 + 10 = 14.\nDefine each Y7's X8 as Y. So Y = i = 14.\nDefine each Y6's X5 as F. So F = 3 * Y - A = 3 * 14 - 9 = 19.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as r. So r = F = 19.\nDefine each Y5's X5 as l. So l = 9.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as V. So V = l = 9.\nDefine each Y7's X5 as q. So q = 1 * r + V = 1 * 19 + 9 = 5.\nDefine each Y7's X6 as z. So z = (u + q + i) = (10 + 5 + 14) = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 490, "question": "The number of each Y3's X1 equals 15 times each X1's W0. The number of each X1's W0 equals 21. How many X1 does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["X1's W0 = 21. Y3's X1 = 15 * X1's W0 = 15 * 21 = 16.\nDefine each Y3's X1 as u. So u = 15 * X1's W0 = 15 * 21 = 16.\nDefine each X1's W0 as S. So S = 21.\nDefine each Y3's X1 as A. So A = 15 * S = 15 * 21 = 16.\nDefine each X1's WWW as i. So i = S = 21.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as Y. So Y = A * i = 16 * 21 = 14.\nDefine each X3's W3 as F. So F = 3.\nDefine each X3's WWW as r. So r = F = 3.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as l. So l = A * i + Y * Y = 16 * 21 + 14 * 14 = 19.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as V. So V = A * i = 16 * 21 = 14.\nDefine each X1's WWW as q. So q = S = 21.\nDefine each Y3's X1 as z. So z = 16 + S = 16 + 21 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 491, "question": "The number of each Y5's X9 equals each Y9's X5. The number of each Y9's X9 equals the sum of each Y0's XXX, each Z6's XXX and each Z6's Y5. The number of each Y0's X1 equals 20 times each X9's W2. The number of each Y0's X5 equals 6 times each Y5's X9. The number of each Y9's X5 equals 18. The number of each Y0's X9 equals 7 more than the difference of each Y9's X5 and each Y5's X9. The number of each X9's W2 equals 20. The number of each Z7's Y0 equals 13 more than each X9's W2. The number of each Y5's X1 equals 7 times each Z7's XXX. The number of each Z6's Y5 equals the sum of each Y5's X9, each Z7's XXX and each X9's W2. How many X9 does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Y9's X5 as u. So u = 18.\nDefine each Y5's X9 as S. So S = u = 18.\nDefine each Y0's X9 as A. So A = 7 * u - S = 7 * 18 - 18 = 16.\nDefine each X9's W2 as i. So i = 20.\nDefine each Y0's X1 as Y. So Y = 20 * i = 20 * 20 = 9.\nDefine each Y0's X5 as F. So F = 6 * S = 6 * 18 = 16.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as r. So r = F + Y + A = 16 + 9 + 16 = 18.\nDefine each Z7's Y0 as l. So l = 13 + i = 13 + 20 = 10.\nDefine each Z7's XXX as V. So V = l * r = 10 * 18 = 19.\nDefine each Y5's X1 as q. So q = 7 * V = 7 * 19 = 18.\nDefine each Z6's Y5 as z. So z = (S + V + i) = (18 + 19 + 20) = 11.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as A. So A = q + S = 18 + 18 = 13.\nDefine each Z6's XXX as i. So i = z * A = 11 * 13 = 5.\nDefine each Y9's X9 as Y. So Y = (r + i + u) = (18 + 5 + 18) = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 492, "question": "The number of each X0's W0 equals 6 times each X0's W8. The number of each X0's W6 equals 22 times each X0's W0. The number of each X0's W8 equals 17. The number of each X3's W8 equals 20 times each X0's WWW. How many W8 does each X3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["X0's W8 as u. So u = 17.\nDefine each X0's W0 as S. So S = 6 * u = 6 * 17 = 10.\nDefine each X0's W6 as A. So A = 22 * S = 22 * 10 = 13.\nDefine each X0's WWW as i. So i = S + A + u = 10 + 13 + 17 = 17.\nDefine each X3's W8 as Y. So Y = 20 * i = 20 * 17 = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 493, "question": "The number of each X1's W7 equals each Y9's X1. The number of each Y1's X6 equals the sum of each Y9's X1 and each Y9's XXX. The number of each X1's W2 equals 21 times the sum of each Y1's X2 and each X1's W7. The number of each X1's W6 equals 18 times each Y1's XXX. The number of each Y9's X1 equals 0. The number of each Y1's X2 equals each Y9's X1. How many WWW does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y9's X1 as u. So u = 0.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as S. So S = u = 0.\nDefine each Y1's X6 as A. So A = u + S = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y1's X2 as i. So i = u = 0.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as Y. So Y = i + A = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each X1's W6 as F. So F = 18 * Y = 18 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X1's W7 as r. So r = u = 0.\nDefine each X1's W2 as l. So l = 21 * i + r = 21 * 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each X1's WWW as V. So V = l + r + F = 0 + 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y9's WWW as q. So q = u * V = 0 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 494, "question": "The number of each X2's W3 equals 1 times the sum of each Y2's XXX and each Y2's X9. The number of each Y2's X9 equals 6. How many W3 does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["Y2's X9 as u. So u = 6.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as S. So S = u = 6.\nDefine each X2's W3 as A. So A = 1 * S + u = 1 * 6 + 6 = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 495, "question": "The number of each Y4's X4 equals 1. The number of each X3's W3 equals each Y4's X4. How many W3 does each X3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Y4's X4 = 1.\nDefine each X3's W3 as u. So u = Y4's X4 = 1.\nDefine each X3's WWW as S. So S = u = 1.\nDefine each Y4's WWW as A. So A = Y4's X4 * S = 1 * 1 = 1.\nDefine each X5's W3 as i. So i = 35.\nDefine each X5's WWW as Y. So Y = i = 3.\nDefine each Y4's WWW as F. So F = Y + A = 3 + 1 = 4.\nDefine each Y4's WWW as r. So r = F + A = 4 + 1 = 5.\nDefine each X3's WWW as l. So l = u = 1.\nDefine each Y4's WWW as V. So V = r + F + Y = 5 + 4 + 3 = 12.\nDefine each Y4's X4 as q. So q = 1.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as z. So z = q = 1.\nDefine each X5's W3 as A. So A = 35.\nDefine each X5's WWW as i. So i = A = 3.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as Y. So Y = q = 1.\nDefine each X3's W3 as F. So F = q = 1.\nDefine each X3's WWW as r. So r = F = 1.\nDefine each Y4's WWW as l. So l = q * S + F * Y = 1 * 1 + 1 * 1 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 496, "question": "The number of each X1's W6 equals 13 times each Z2's XXX. The number of each Y7's X1 equals 12 more than each X9's W6. The number of each X9's W4 equals 13. The number of each X1's W4 equals the difference of each X1's W6 and each Y1's XXX. The number of each Z2's Y7 equals each Y7's X1. The number of each Y1's X9 equals 18 more than each X9's W6. The number of each Z2's Y1 equals 5. The number of each Y1's X1 equals each X9's WWW. The number of each Y7's X9 equals the difference of each X9's W4 and each X9's WWW. The number of each X9's W6 equals 0. How many WWW does each X1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["X9's W6 as u. So u = 0.\nDefine each X9's W4 as S. So S = 13.\nDefine each X9's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 13 + 0 = 13.\nDefine each Y1's X1 as i. So i = A = 13.\nDefine each Y7's X1 as Y. So Y = 12 * u = 12 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y7's X9 as F. So F = S - A = 13 - 13 = 0.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as r. So r = Y + F = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z2's Y1 as l. So l = 5.\nDefine each Y1's X9 as V. So V = 18 * u = 18 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as q. So q = V + i = 0 + 13 = 13.\nDefine each Z2's Y7 as z. So z = Y = 0.\nDefine each Z2's XXX as A. So A = l * q + Z * r = 5 * 13 + 0 * 0 = 19.\nDefine each X1's W6 as i. So i = 13 * A = 13 * 19 = 17.\nDefine each X1's W4 as Y. So Y = i - q = 17 - 13 = 4.\nDefine each X1's WWW as F. So F = Y + i = 4 + 17 = 21.\nThus, the answer is 21."], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 497, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y2 equals 10 times the difference of each Y8's XXX and each Z8's XXX. The number of each Y9's X9 equals 8. The number of each Y2's X1 equals 7 times the difference of each Z3's XXX and each Y8's XXX. The number of each Z3's Y8 equals 1 times the sum of each Y9's X9 and each Z8's XXX. The number of each Z8's Y8 equals 0 times the sum of each Y9's X9 and each Y8's X1. The number of each Y8's X1 equals 3 more than each Y9's X9. How many XXX does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Y9's X9 as u. So u = 8.\nDefine each Y8's X1 as S. So S = 3 * u = 3 * 8 = 1.\nDefine each Z8's Y8 as A. So A = 0 * u + S = 0 * 8 + 1 = 1.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as i. So i = S = 1.\nDefine each Z8's XXX as Y. So Y = A * i = 1 * 1 = 1.\nDefine each Z3's Y8 as F. So F = 1 * u + Y = 1 * 8 + 1 = 9.\nDefine each Z3's XXX as r. So r = F * i = 9 * 1 = 9.\nDefine each Y2's X1 as l. So l = 7 * r - i = 7 * 9 - 1 = 19.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as V. So V = l = 19.\nDefine each Z5's Y2 as q. So q = 10 * i - Y = 10 * 1 - 1 = 9.\nDefine each Z5's XXX as z. So z = q * V = 9 * 19 = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 498, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y2 equals 6. The number of each Z0's Y2 equals the difference of each Y2's XXX and each Z6's XXX. The number of each Y2's X4 equals 13 more than each Z6's Y2. How many Y2 does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Z6's Y2 = 6. Y2's X4 as u. So u = 13 * Z6's Y2 = 13 * 6 = 9.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as S. So S = u = 9.\nDefine each Z6's XXX as A. So A = Z6's XXX as i. So i = Z6's S * S = 6 * 9 = 8.\nDefine each Z0's Y2 as Y. So Y = S - i = 9 - 8 = 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 499, "question": "The number of each Y2's X4 equals 4 more than each Z5's Y2. The number of each Y2's X5 equals each Z5's YYY. The number of each Y2's X3 equals each Z5's Y2. The number of each Z5's Y1 equals 1. The number of each Z5's Y2 equals 7 times each Z5's Y1. The number of each Z5's Y4 equals 13 times each Z5's Y1. How many XXX does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Z5's Y1 as u. So u = 1.\nDefine each Z5's Y4 as S. So S = 13 + u = 13 + 1 = 14.\nDefine each Z5's Y2 as A. So A = 7 * u = 7 * 1 = 7.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as i. So i = S + A + u = 14 + 7 + 1 = 22.\nDefine each Y2's X5 as Y. So Y = i = 22.\nDefine each Y2's X3 as F. So F = A = 7.\nDefine each Y2's X4 as r. So r = 4 * A = 4 * 7 = 5.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as l. So l = r + Y + F = 5 + 22 + 7 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 500, "question": "The number of each Y9's X8 equals 20. The number of each X6's W7 equals 1 more than each X0's W6. The number of each Y5's X8 equals 10. The number of each Y2's X0 equals the difference of each Y2's X6 and each X6's W7. The number of each X0's W7 equals 0 more than the sum of each Y5's X8 and each Y5's WWW. The number of each X8's W7 equals 17 times the sum of each Y9's X6 and each Y2's X0. The number of each X8's W6 equals the difference of each X0's W6 and each X8's W7. The number of each X0's W6 equals 3 more than the sum of each Y9's X6 and each Y9's X8. The number of each Y2's X6 equals 15 times the difference of each Y9's X8 and each X6's W7. The number of each Y9's X6 equals each Y9's X8. How many W7 does each X0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["Y9's X8 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each Y9's X6 as S. So S = u = 20.\nDefine each X0's W6 as A. So A = 3 * S + u = 3 * 20 + 20 = 1.\nDefine each X6's W7 as i. So i = 1 * A = 1 * 1 = 1.\nDefine each Y2's X6 as Y. So Y = 15 * u - i = 15 * 20 - 1 = 19.\nDefine each Y2's X0 as F. So F = Y - i = 19 - 1 = 18.\nDefine each X8's W7 as r. So r = 17 * S + F = 17 * 20 + 18 = 19.\nDefine each X8's W6 as l. So l = A - r = 1 - 19 = 5.\nDefine each X8's WWW as V. So V = l + r = 5 + 19 = 1.\nDefine each Y5's X8 as q. So q = 10.\nDefine each Y5's WWW as z. So z = q * V = 10 * 1 = 10.\nDefine each X0's W7 as A. So A = 0 * q + S = 0 * 10 + 20 = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 501, "question": "The number of each X8's W1 equals 16. The number of each X2's W9 equals 8 times each Z2's Y7. The number of each Y7's X8 equals each X8's W1. The number of each Z2's Y7 equals 9 times each Y7's WWW. How many W9 does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["X8's W1 = 16. X8's WWW = 16. Y7's X8 = X8's W1. Y7's WWW = Y7's X8 * X8's W1 = 16.\nDefine each Z2's Y7 as u. So u = 9 * Y7's WWW = 9 * 16 = 6.\nDefine each X2's W9 as S. So S = 8 * u = 8 * 6 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 502, "question": "The number of each Y6's X4 equals the difference of each Y5's X4 and each Y5's X0. The number of each Y5's X4 equals 0. The number of each Y5's X0 equals 15 more than each Y5's X4. The number of each Y6's X0 equals 17 times the sum of each Y5's X0 and each Y5's X4. How many XXX does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Y5's X4 as u. So u = 0.\nDefine each Y5's X0 as S. So S = 15 * u = 15 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y6's X0 as A. So A = 17 * S + u = 17 * 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y6's X4 as i. So i = u - S = 0 - 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as Y. So Y = A + i + u = 0 + 0 + 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 503, "question": "The number of each X0's W6 equals 8 times each X1's W9. The number of each X3's W2 equals 5 times each X3's W8. The number of each X3's W8 equals 5. The number of each X1's W9 equals 1 times each X3's WWW. How many WWW does each X0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["X3's W8 as u. So u = 5.\nDefine each X3's W2 as S. So S = 5 * u = 5 * 5 = 2.\nDefine each X3's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 2 + 5 = 7.\nDefine each X1's W9 as i. So i = 1 * A = 1 * 7 = 7.\nDefine each X0's W6 as Y. So Y = 8 * i = 8 * 7 = 10.\nDefine each X0's WWW as F. So F = Y = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 504, "question": "The number of each X2's W3 equals 14. The number of each Y5's X7 equals 2 more than each X2's W3. The number of each X7's W4 equals 12 more than the sum of each X2's W3 and each Y5's X7. The number of each Y7's X5 equals 5 more than each X7's W4. How many X5 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["X2's W3 = 14. Y5's X7 = 2 * X2's W3 = 2 * 14 = 5.\nDefine each X7's W4 as u. So u = 12 * X2's W3 + Y5's X7 = 12 * 14 + 5 = 14.\nDefine each Y7's X5 as S. So S = 5 + u = 5 + 14 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 505, "question": "The number of each Y6's X4 equals 19. How many X4 does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Y6's X4 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 506, "question": "The number of each X2's W4 equals 19. How many W4 does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["X2's W4 = 19. So 19.\nDefine each X2's WWW as u. So u = X2's W4 = 19.\nDefine each Y1's l0 as S. So S = 20.\nDefine each Y1's l0 as A. So A = 20.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as i. So i = S + A = 20 + 20 = 17.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as l. So l = S + A = 20 + 20 = 17.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as V. So V = S + A = 20 + 20 = 17.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as q. So q = S + A + V = 20 + 20 + 17 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 507, "question": "The number of each Z4's Y3 equals 0 more than each X4's W6. The number of each Y4's X1 equals 15 more than each X8's W6. The number of each X1's W0 equals 8 times each Y3's X4. The number of each Z7's Y4 equals 16 more than each Y4's XXX. The number of each Y3's X4 equals each Z4's Y3. The number of each Z8's Y7 equals 13 more than each Z1's Y3. The number of each X4's W6 equals 1. The number of each Y0's X4 equals the difference of each Y7's X6 and each Z7's Y4. The number of each Z1's Y3 equals 15 more than each Y0's X4. The number of each Y7's X6 equals 15 more than each Z7's XXX. The number of each X8's W6 equals 11 times each X1's W0. How many Y7 does each Z8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["X4's W6 = 1. Z4's Y3 = 0 * X4 = 0 * 1 = 0.\nDefine each Y3's X4 as u. So u = Z4's Y3 = 0.\nDefine each X1's W0 as S. So S = 8 * u = 8 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X8's W6 as A. So A = 11 * S = 11 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y4's X1 as i. So i = 15 * A = 15 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as Y. So Y = i = 0.\nDefine each Z7's Y4 as F. So F = 16 * Y = 16 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z7's XXX as r. So r = F * Y = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y7's X6 as l. So l = 15 * r = 15 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y0's X4 as V. So V = l - F = 0 - 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z1's Y3 as q. So q = 15 * V = 15 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z8's Y7 as z. So z = 13 + q = 13 + 0 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 508, "question": "The number of each Y3's X6 equals 3 more than each Y6's XXX. The number of each Y6's X9 equals 2 times each Y7's X9. The number of each Y3's X3 equals 4 times the difference of each Y6's X9 and each Y6's XXX. The number of each Y4's X9 equals each Y3's XXX. The number of each Y7's X9 equals 11. How many X9 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Y7's X9 = 11. Y6's X9 as u. So u = 2 * Y7's X9 = 2 * 11 = 22.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as S. So S = u = 22.\nDefine each Y3's X6 as A. So A = 3 * S = 3 * 22 = 20.\nDefine each Y3's X3 as i. So i = 4 * u - S = 4 * 22 - 22 = 20.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as Y. So Y = i + A = 20 + 20 = 17.\nDefine each Y4's X9 as F. So F = Y = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 509, "question": "The number of each X3's W9 equals the sum of each X1's W6, each Y9's X7, each Z9's WWW and each X1's WWW. The number of each X1's W6 equals the sum of each Y9's XXX, each Y9's X7 and each Z9's Y4. The number of each Y4's X1 equals 13 more than each X1's WWW. The number of each Z9's Y4 equals each Y9's XXX. The number of each Y9's X7 equals 20. How many WWW does each X3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["X1's W6 as u. So u = (Y9's X7 + Y9's XXX + Z9's Y4) = 2.\nDefine each X1's WWW as S. So S = u = 2.\nDefine each Y4's X1 as A. So A = 13 * S = 13 * 2 = 3.\nDefine each Y4's WWW as i. So i = A * S = 3 * 2 = 6.\nDefine each Z9's Y4 as Y. So Y = i = 6.\nDefine each Z9's WWW as F. So F = Y * i = 6 * 6 = 13.\nDefine each X3's W9 as r. So r = (u + Y + F + S) = (2 + 6 + 13 + 2) = 0.\nDefine each X3's WWW as l. So l = r = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 510, "question": "The number of each Y9's X6 equals 13 times each Y4's XXX. The number of each Y9's X5 equals the difference of each Y9's X0 and each Y6's X5. The number of each Y9's X0 equals 1. The number of each Y6's X5 equals 0 times each Y9's X0. The number of each Y4's X5 equals 9. The number of each Y6's X6 equals the difference of each Y9's X5 and each Y9's X0. The number of each Y4's X6 equals 20 more than each Y6's X6. The number of each Y4's X0 equals 15 more than each Y9's X5. How many X6 does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Y9's X0 as u. So u = 1.\nDefine each Y6's X5 as S. So S = 0 * u = 0 * 1 = 0.\nDefine each Y9's X5 as A. So A = u - S = 1 - 0 = 1.\nDefine each Y4's X0 as i. So i = 15 * A = 15 * 1 = 15.\nDefine each Y4's X5 as Y. So Y = 9.\nDefine each Y6's X6 as F. So F = A - u = 1 - 1 = 0.\nDefine each Y4's X6 as r. So r = 20 * F = 20 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as l. So l = Y + r + i = 9 + 0 + 15 = 1.\nDefine each Y9's X6 as V. So V = 13 * l = 13 * 1 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 511, "question": "The number of each X1's W2 equals 16. How many W2 does each X1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["X1's W2 = 16. So 16.\nDefine each X1's WWW as u. So u = X1's W2 = 16.\nDefine each Y1's l0 as S. So S = 20.\nDefine each Y1's l0 as A. So A = 20.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as i. So i = S + A = 20 + 20 = 17.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as l. So l = S + A = 20 + 20 = 17.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as V. So V = S + A = 20 + 20 = 17.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as q. So q = S + V = 20 + 17 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 512, "question": "The number of each Y7's X9 equals 20. The number of each X0's W9 equals 7 more than each Y7's X9. How many W9 does each X0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["Y7's X9 = 20. X0's W9 = 7 * Y7 = 7 * 20 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 513, "question": "The number of each Y0's X6 equals 16. The number of each Y0's X4 equals 18 times each Y0's X6. How many X4 does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["Y0's X6 as u. So u = 16.\nDefine each Y0's X4 as S. So S = 18 * u = 18 * 16 = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 514, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y4 equals the sum of each Z1's Y4 and each Y0's X3. The number of each Z1's Y0 equals 15. The number of each Y0's X6 equals 13 times each Z6's XXX. The number of each Y0's X3 equals 1 times the difference of each Z1's YYY and each Y0's X2. The number of each Z0's Y3 equals 22 times each Z1's Y3. The number of each Z1's Y4 equals 7. The number of each Y0's X2 equals the difference of each Z1's Y3 and each Z1's YYY. The number of each Y4's X3 equals 0. The number of each Y3's X6 equals each Y0's X6. The number of each Z0's Y4 equals the difference of each Z1's Y0 and each Z1's Y4. The number of each Z1's Y3 equals each Z1's Y0. How many XXX does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Z1's Y0 as u. So u = 15.\nDefine each Z1's Y3 as S. So S = u = 15.\nDefine each Z1's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 15 + 15 = 7.\nDefine each Y0's X2 as i. So i = S - A = 15 - 7 = 8.\nDefine each Y0's X3 as Y. So Y = 1 * A - i = 1 * 7 - 8 = 22.\nDefine each Z6's Y4 as F. So F = S + Y = 15 + 22 = 14.\nDefine each Y4's X3 as r. So r = 0.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as l. So l = r = 0.\nDefine each Z6's XXX as V. So V = F * l = 14 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y0's X6 as q. So q = 13 * V = 13 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y3's X6 as z. So z = q = 0.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as A. So A = z = 0.\nDefine each Z0's Y3 as i. So i = 22 * S = 22 * 15 = 8.\nDefine each Z0's Y4 as Y. So Y = u - S = 15 - 15 = 0.\nDefine each Z0's XXX as F. So F = Y * l + i * A = 0 * 0 + 8 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 515, "question": "The number of each X2's W8 equals 0 more than the sum of each X0's W0, each X0's WWW and each X0's W8. The number of each X0's W0 equals 14 times each X0's W8. The number of each X2's W0 equals 21 times the difference of each X0's W8 and each X0's W0. The number of each X0's W8 equals 12. How many WWW does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["X0's W8 as u. So u = 12.\nDefine each X0's W0 as S. So S = 14 * u = 14 * 12 = 7.\nDefine each X0's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 7 + 12 = 19.\nDefine each X2's W8 as i. So i = 0 * (S + A + u) = 0 * (7 + 19 + 12) = 0.\nDefine each X2's W0 as Y. So Y = 21 * u - S = 21 * 12 - 7 = 19.\nDefine each X2's WWW as F. So F = Y + i = 19 + 0 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 516, "question": "The number of each X4's W1 equals 16. The number of each Z6's Y3 equals the difference of each Z4's Y3 and each X4's W1. The number of each Y7's X5 equals 12 times each Z6's Y3. The number of each X5's W0 equals 11 times each Y7's X5. The number of each Z4's Y3 equals 2 more than each X4's W1. The number of each Z5's Y7 equals 6 times the sum of each X5's WWW, each X4's W1 and each Y7's WWW. How many Y7 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 517, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y7 equals 22. How many Y7 does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["Z9's Y7 = 22. So 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 518, "question": "The number of each Y4's X4 equals the sum of each Y7's X4, each Y7's X7 and each Y4's X7. The number of each Y7's X4 equals 10 times each Y4's X7. The number of each Y4's X7 equals 17 times each Y7's X7. The number of each Y7's X7 equals 0. How many X4 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y7's X7 as u. So u = 0.\nDefine each Y4's X7 as S. So S = 17 * u = 17 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y7's X4 as A. So A = 10 * S = 10 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y4's X4 as i. So i = (A + u + S) = (0 + 0 + 0) = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 519, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y4 equals the sum of each Y4's X1, each Z3's Y4, each Z3's Y2 and each Y2's XXX. The number of each Y2's X3 equals each Z3's Y2. The number of each Z3's Y4 equals 0 times the difference of each Y2's X0 and each Y2's XXX. The number of each Y2's X0 equals 2 times the difference of each Y2's X3 and each Z3's Y2. The number of each Y4's X0 equals 0 more than the sum of each Z3's Y4, each Z3's Y2 and each Y2's XXX. The number of each Y4's X1 equals 18 times the sum of each Y4's X0 and each Y2's XXX. The number of each Z3's Y2 equals 8. How many XXX does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Z3's Y2 as u. So u = 8.\nDefine each Y2's X3 as S. So S = u = 8.\nDefine each Y2's X0 as A. So A = 2 * S - u = 2 * 8 - 8 = 8.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as i. So i = S + A = 8 + 8 = 16.\nDefine each Z3's Y4 as Y. So Y = 0 * A - i = 0 * 8 - 16 = 7.\nDefine each Y4's X0 as F. So F = 0 * (Y + u + i) = 0 * (7 + 8 + 16) = 0.\nDefine each Y4's X1 as r. So r = 18 * F + i = 18 * 0 + 16 = 16.\nDefine each Z5's Y4 as l. So l = (r + Y + u + i) = (16 + 7 + 8 + 16) = 1.\nDefine each Z5's XXX as V. So V = l * i = 1 * 16 = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 520, "question": "The number of each Y4's X8 equals 10. The number of each Y6's X8 equals 4 times the difference of each Y4's XXX and each Y4's X8. How many XXX does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y4's X8 = 10. Y4's XXX as u. So u = Y4's XXX = 10.\nDefine each Y6's X8 as S. So S = 4 * u - u = 4 * 10 - 10 = 4.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as A. So A = S = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 521, "question": "The number of each X2's W0 equals 21. The number of each X2's W6 equals 8. The number of each Y6's X2 equals 19 more than the difference of each X2's WWW and each X2's W6. The number of each Y4's X0 equals 13 more than the difference of each X2's WWW and each Y6's WWW. How many X0 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["X2's W6 as u. So u = 8.\nDefine each X2's W0 as S. So S = 21.\nDefine each X2's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 21 + 8 = 6.\nDefine each Y6's X2 as i. So i = 19 * A - u = 19 * 6 - 8 = 11.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as Y. So Y = i * A = 11 * 6 = 20.\nDefine each Y4's X0 as F. So F = 13 * A - Y = 13 * 6 - 20 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 522, "question": "The number of each Y6's X9 equals each Y9's X6. The number of each Z4's Y6 equals 15 times each Y6's X9. The number of each Y9's X6 equals 18. How many YYY does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["Y9's X6 as u. So u = 18.\nDefine each Y6's X9 as S. So S = u = 18.\nDefine each Z4's Y6 as A. So A = 15 * S = 15 * 18 = 17.\nDefine each Z4's YYY as i. So i = A = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 523, "question": "The number of each X0's W5 equals 4 more than each X6's W4. The number of each Y9's X0 equals 15 more than the sum of each X0's W5 and each X6's W4. The number of each X6's W4 equals 11. How many WWW does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["X6's W4 = 11. X0's W5 as u. So u = 4 * X6's W4 = 4 * 11 = 21.\nDefine each Y9's X0 as S. So S = 15 * u + X6's W4 = 15 * 21 + 11 = 14.\nDefine each X0's WWW as A. So A = u = 21.\nDefine each Y9's WWW as i. So i = S * A = 14 * 21 = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 524, "question": "The number of each Z2's Y4 equals 5. The number of each Z2's Y5 equals 5 more than each Z2's Y4. How many YYY does each Z2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Z2's Y4 as u. So u = 5.\nDefine each Z2's Y5 as S. So S = 5 * u = 5 * 5 = 2.\nDefine each Z2's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 2 + 5 = 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 525, "question": "The number of each Z4's Y7 equals 19 more than each Z4's Y0. The number of each Z4's Y0 equals the sum of each Y7's X1 and each Y0's X2. The number of each X1's W4 equals 17 times each Z4's YYY. The number of each X2's W4 equals 14 more than each Y0's X2. The number of each X2's W1 equals each X2's W4. The number of each Y0's X2 equals 6. The number of each Y7's X1 equals the sum of each X2's W4 and each X2's W1. The number of each Z5's Y0 equals each X1's W4. How many Y0 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Y0's X2 = 6. X2's W4 as u. So u = 14 * Y0's X2 = 14 * 6 = 15.\nDefine each X2's W1 as S. So S = u = 15.\nDefine each Y7's X1 as A. So A = u + S = 15 + 15 = 7.\nDefine each Z4's Y0 as i. So i = A + Y0's X2 = 7 + 6 = 13.\nDefine each Z4's Y7 as Y. So Y = 19 * i = 19 * 13 = 17.\nDefine each Z4's YYY as F. So F = Y + i = 17 + 13 = 7.\nDefine each X1's W4 as r. So r = 17 * F = 17 * 7 = 4.\nDefine each Z5's Y0 as l. So l = r = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 526, "question": "The number of each X5's W5 equals the sum of each Z3's Y3, each Z3's WWW, each X2's WWW and each X2's W1. The number of each Y4's X2 equals each X2's WWW. The number of each Z1's Y2 equals 0 more than the sum of each Y3's WWW and each Y2's WWW. The number of each Y3's X2 equals each X2's W1. The number of each Z3's Y3 equals 17. The number of each X7's W1 equals 22 more than each X5's W5. The number of each X2's W1 equals each Z3's YYY. The number of each Y2's X7 equals each Y4's X2. How many WWW does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 527, "question": "The number of each Y5's X8 equals 22. How many XXX does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["Y5's X8 = 22. Y5's XXX = 22. Y6's X8 = 2. Y6's XXX as i. So i = Y6's X8 = 2.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as Y. So Y = Y = 2.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as F. So F = 22.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as r. So r = Y = 2.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as l. So l = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 528, "question": "The number of each Y5's X5 equals 22. The number of each Y4's X5 equals 4 more than each Y5's X5. How many X5 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["Y5's X5 = 22. Y4's X5 = 4 * Y5's X5 = 4 * 22 = 19.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as u. So u = Y4's X5 = 19.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as S. So S = Y5's X2 = 22.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each lollip0 as A. So A = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20.\nDefine each l0 = 20"], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 529, "question": "The number of each X9's W5 equals 20 times each X8's WWW. The number of each X9's W9 equals 19. The number of each X8's W9 equals 17. The number of each X8's W5 equals 17. How many WWW does each X9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["X8's W5 as u. So u = 17.\nDefine each X8's W9 as S. So S = 17.\nDefine each X8's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 17 + 17 = 11.\nDefine each X9's W5 as i. So i = 20 * A = 20 * 11 = 13.\nDefine each X9's W9 as Y. So Y = 19.\nDefine each X9's WWW as F. So F = Y + i = 19 + 13 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 530, "question": "The number of each X0's W9 equals 16. How many W9 does each X0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["X0's W9 = 16. So 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 531, "question": "The number of each Y7's X1 equals each Y5's X1. The number of each X5's W7 equals 6. The number of each X5's W8 equals 15 times each Y5's X1. The number of each Y7's X5 equals the sum of each X1's WWW, each X5's WWW and each Y7's X1. The number of each X1's W7 equals 4. The number of each Z5's Y7 equals the sum of each Z7's Y7 and each Z7's WWW. The number of each X1's W8 equals the sum of each Y5's X1, each X1's W7 and each X5's W8. The number of each Z7's Y7 equals each X1's WWW. The number of each Y5's X1 equals 22 times each X1's W7. How many Y7 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["22 * X1's W7 = 22 * 2 = 21.\nDefine each Y5's X1 as u. So u = 22 * X1's W7 = 22 * 21 = 2.\nDefine each X5's W8 as S. So S = 15 * u = 15 * 2 = 7.\nDefine each X1's W8 as A. So A = (u + X1's W7 + S) = (2 + 21 + 7) = 7.\nDefine each X1's WWW as i. So i = A = 7.\nDefine each Y7's X1 as Y. So Y = u = 2.\nDefine each X5's W7 as F. So F = 6.\nDefine each X5's WWW as r. So r = F + S = 6 + 7 = 13.\nDefine each Y7's X5 as l. So l = (i + r + Y) = (7 + 13 + 2) = 22.\nDefine each Y7's WWW as V. So V = l * r + Y * i = 22 * 13 + 2 * 7 = 19.\nDefine each Z7's Y7 as q. So q = i = 7.\nDefine each Z7's WWW as z. So z = q * V = 7 * 19 = 18.\nDefine each Z5's Y7 as A. So A = q + z = 7 + 18 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 532, "question": "The number of each Y6's X7 equals 17. The number of each Y5's X9 equals 14 more than the difference of each X9's W8 and each Y6's X7. The number of each X9's W8 equals 9 more than each Y6's X7. How many WWW does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y6's X7 = 17. X9's W8 as u. So u = 9 * Y6's X7 = 9 * 17 = 15.\nDefine each Y5's X9 as S. So S = 14 * u - Y6's X7 = 14 * 15 - 17 = 14.\nDefine each X9's WWW as A. So A = u = 15.\nDefine each Y5's WWW as i. So i = S * A = 14 * 15 = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 533, "question": "The number of each Y9's X4 equals each X4's WWW. The number of each X4's W2 equals 19. How many WWW does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Y9's X4 as u. So u = X4's W2. X4's WWW as S. So S = 19.\nDefine each Y9's WWW as A. So A = u * S = 23 * 19 = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 534, "question": "The number of each Z2's Y9 equals 7. The number of each Y9's X9 equals 0 more than the difference of each X9's W9 and each Z2's Y9. The number of each X9's W5 equals 19 more than the sum of each X8's W6, each Z6's Y8 and each X0's W5. The number of each X9's W9 equals 3. The number of each X0's W5 equals 14 more than each Z2's Y9. The number of each Z6's Y8 equals 21 more than the difference of each X8's W6 and each X0's W5. The number of each X8's W6 equals 14 more than each X0's W5. How many WWW does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["Z2's Y9 = 7. X0's W5 = 14 * Z2's Y9 = 14 * 7 = 6.\nDefine each X8's W6 as u. So u = 14 * S = 14 * 6 = 15.\nDefine each Z6's Y8 as S. So S = 21 * u - S = 21 * 15 - 21 = 18.\nDefine each X9's W5 as A. So A = 19 + (u + S + S) = 19 + (15 + 18 + 18) = 2.\nDefine each X9's W9 as i. So i = 3.\nDefine each X9's WWW as Y. So Y = A + i = 2 + 3 = 5.\nDefine each Y9's X9 as F. So F = 0 * i - Z2's Y9 = 0 * 3 - 7 = 16.\nDefine each Y9's WWW as r. So r = F * Y = 16 * 5 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 535, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y5 equals 20. The number of each Z2's Y3 equals 0 more than the difference of each Z3's Y5 and each Z5's Y5. The number of each Z5's Y5 equals each Z3's Y5. How many YYY does each Z2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Z3's Y5 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each Z5's Y5 as S. So S = u = 20.\nDefine each Z2's Y3 as A. So A = 0 * u - S = 0 * 20 - 20 = 3.\nDefine each Z2's YYY as i. So i = A = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 536, "question": "The number of each Y7's X4 equals 15. How many X4 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Y7's X4 = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 537, "question": "The number of each Z2's Y7 equals 1 times the sum of each X0's WWW, each X7's W4 and each Z1's Y7. The number of each X7's W4 equals 6 more than each Y7's X0. The number of each X0's W1 equals 18 times each Y7's X0. The number of each Y7's X0 equals 1. The number of each X0's W8 equals 7 more than each Z1's Y7. The number of each Y3's X3 equals the sum of each Z2's Y7, each Z2's YYY and each Z2's Y3. The number of each Z1's Y7 equals the difference of each Y7's X0 and each X7's W4. The number of each Z2's Y3 equals the sum of each Y7's X0 and each X7's W4. How many X3 does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Y7's X0 = 1.\nDefine each X7's W4 as u. So u = 6 * Y7's X0 = 6 * 1 = 6.\nDefine each Z1's Y7 as S. So S = Y7's X0 - u = 1 - 6 = 18.\nDefine each X0's W8 as A. So A = 7 * S = 7 * 18 = 11.\nDefine each X0's W1 as i. So i = 18 * Y7's X0 = 18 * 1 = 18.\nDefine each X0's WWW as Y. So Y = A + i = 11 + 18 = 6.\nDefine each Z2's Y7 as F. So F = 1 * (Y + u + S) = 1 * (6 + 6 + 18) = 7.\nDefine each Z2's Y3 as r. So r = Y + u = 6 + 6 = 12.\nDefine each Z2's YYY as l. So l = r + F = 12 + 7 = 19.\nDefine each Y3's X3 as V. So V = (F + l + r) = (7 + 19 + 12) = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 538, "question": "The number of each Y2's X7 equals 10. The number of each Y2's X0 equals 12 times each Y2's X7. How many X0 does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Y2's X7 as u. So u = 10.\nDefine each Y2's X0 as S. So S = 12 * u = 12 * 10 = 5.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 5 + 10 = 15.\nDefine each X0 as i. So i = 8.\nDefine each X0 as Y. So Y = 8.\nDefine each X0 as F. So F = 8.\nDefine each X0 as r. So r = 8.\nDefine each X0 as l. So l = 8.\nDefine each X0 as V. So V = 8.\nDefine each X0 as q. So q = 8.\nDefine each X0 as z. So z = 8.\nThus, the answer is 8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 539, "question": "The number of each X3's W4 equals 13 times each X9's W6. The number of each X9's W6 equals 2. How many W4 does each X3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["X9's W6 = 2. X3's W4 = 13 * X9's W6 = 13 * 2 = 3.\nDefine each X3's W4 as u. So u = 13 * X9's W6 = 13 * 2 = 3.\nDefine each X3's WWW as S. So S = u = 3.\nDefine each Y1's X0 as A. So A = 21.\nDefine each Y1's X0 as i. So i = 21.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as Y. So Y = i + A = 21 + 21 = 19.\nDefine each X9's WWW as F. So F = X9's W6 = 2.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as r. So r = i = 21.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as l. So l = i + A = 21 + 21 = 19.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as V. So V = i + A = 21 + 21 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 540, "question": "The number of each X7's W6 equals the sum of each X7's W9 and each Y0's X0. The number of each Y0's X7 equals 17. The number of each Y0's X0 equals 19 more than each Y0's X7. The number of each X7's W9 equals 16 times each Y0's XXX. How many WWW does each X7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["Y0's X7 as u. So u = 17.\nDefine each Y0's X0 as S. So S = 19 * u = 19 * 17 = 1.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 1 + 17 = 18.\nDefine each X7's W9 as i. So i = 16 * A = 16 * 18 = 12.\nDefine each X7's W6 as Y. So Y = i + S = 12 + 1 = 13.\nDefine each X7's WWW as F. So F = Y + i = 13 + 12 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 541, "question": "The number of each X2's W3 equals the sum of each Y9's X2 and each X7's WWW. The number of each X7's W3 equals 18 more than each Y9's X2. The number of each X1's W8 equals each Y9's X2. The number of each X2's W8 equals 4 more than each X2's W3. The number of each X1's W3 equals 22 more than each X2's W8. The number of each Y9's X2 equals 21. The number of each X7's W8 equals 19 times each Y9's X2. How many WWW does each X1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y9's X2 = 21. X7's W8 as u. So u = 19 * Y = 19 * 21 = 8.\nDefine each X7's W3 as S. So S = 18 * Y = 18 * 21 = 10.\nDefine each X7's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 10 + 8 = 18.\nDefine each X2's W3 as i. So i = Y + A = 21 + 18 = 16.\nDefine each X2's W8 as Y. So Y = 4 * i = 4 * 16 = 18.\nDefine each X1's W3 as F. So F = 22 * Y = 22 * 18 = 5.\nDefine each Y9's X2 as r. So r = 21.\nDefine each X1's W8 as l. So l = r = 21.\nDefine each X1's WWW as V. So V = l + F = 21 + 5 = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 542, "question": "The number of each Y4's X0 equals 7. The number of each Y6's X0 equals 9 times each X0's W0. The number of each X6's W0 equals 19 more than the sum of each Y6's X0, each X0's W0 and each Y4's X6. The number of each X0's W0 equals each Y4's X0. The number of each Y4's X6 equals 18 times the sum of each X0's W0, each Y6's WWW and each Y6's X0. The number of each Y2's X0 equals 18 times the sum of each X0's WWW, each X0's W0 and each X6's W0. How many XXX does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Y4's X0 as u. So u = 7.\nDefine each X0's W0 as S. So S = u = 7.\nDefine each Y6's X0 as A. So A = 9 * S = 9 * 7 = 17.\nDefine each X0's WWW as i. So i = S = 7.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as Y. So Y = A * i = 17 * 7 = 4.\nDefine each Y4's X6 as F. So F = 18 * (S + Y + A) = 18 * (7 + 4 + 17) = 19.\nDefine each X6's W0 as r. So r = 19 + (A + S + F) = 19 + (17 + 7 + 19) = 16.\nDefine each Y2's X0 as l. So l = 18 * (i + S + r) = 18 * (7 + 7 + 16) = 19.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as V. So V = l = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 543, "question": "The number of each Y5's X0 equals 12 more than each Y7's X0. The number of each Z6's Y5 equals 0 times each Y5's XXX. The number of each X0's W3 equals each Z6's Y5. The number of each Z1's Y5 equals 12 more than each X0's W0. The number of each Y7's X0 equals the sum of each X9's W3 and each Y7's X9. The number of each Z1's Y7 equals the sum of each Y5's X9, each X0's W3 and each X9's W3. The number of each Y7's X9 equals the difference of each X9's WWW and each X9's W3. The number of each X0's W0 equals 17. The number of each Y5's X9 equals 1 more than each X9's WWW. The number of each X9's W3 equals 22 times the sum of each X0's W0 and each Z1's Y5. How many Y7 does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 544, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y4 equals 22. How many Y4 does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["Z9's Y4 as u. So u = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 545, "question": "The number of each X0's W3 equals 2. How many W3 does each X0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["X0's W3 = 2. So 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 546, "question": "The number of each X9's W9 equals 3 times each Y7's WWW. The number of each X1's W4 equals 11. The number of each Y7's X1 equals each X1's WWW. How many W9 does each X9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["X1's W4 as u. So u = 11.\nDefine each X1's WWW as S. So S = u = 11.\nDefine each Y7's X1 as A. So A = S = 11.\nDefine each Y7's WWW as i. So i = A * S = 11 * 11 = 6.\nDefine each X9's W9 as Y. So Y = 3 * i = 3 * 6 = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 547, "question": "The number of each Y6's X2 equals each Y9's X1. The number of each Y7's X2 equals each Y7's X4. The number of each Y7's X4 equals 3. The number of each Y9's X1 equals 15 times the sum of each Y7's X2 and each Y7's X4. The number of each Y6's X1 equals the sum of each Y7's X2 and each Y6's X2. How many X1 does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Y7's X4 as u. So u = 3.\nDefine each Y7's X2 as S. So S = u = 3.\nDefine each Y9's X1 as A. So A = 15 * S + u = 15 * 3 + 3 = 2.\nDefine each Y6's X2 as i. So i = A = 2.\nDefine each Y6's X1 as Y. So Y = S + i = 3 + 2 = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 548, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y2 equals 16 more than the sum of each Y1's X8 and each Y2's XXX. The number of each Z0's Y8 equals 5 more than each Z1's Y8. The number of each Y4's X7 equals 10 more than the difference of each Z0's YYY and each Z5's Y2. The number of each Z1's Y8 equals 20 times each Z5's XXX. The number of each Y2's X8 equals 14. The number of each Y1's X8 equals 19 more than each Y2's X8. The number of each Z6's Y8 equals each Y4's X7. How many Y8 does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Y2's X8 = 14. Y2's XXX as u. So u = 14.\nDefine each Y1's X8 as S. So S = 19 * u = 19 * 14 = 13.\nDefine each Z5's Y2 as A. So A = 16 * S + u = 16 * 13 + 14 = 17.\nDefine each Z5's XXX as i. So i = A * u = 17 * 14 = 8.\nDefine each Z1's Y8 as Y. So Y = 20 * i = 20 * 8 = 22.\nDefine each Z0's Y8 as F. So F = 5 + Y = 5 + 22 = 4.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as r. So r = F = 4.\nDefine each Y4's X7 as l. So l = 10 * r - A = 10 * 4 - 17 = 11.\nDefine each Z6's Y8 as V. So V = l = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 549, "question": "The number of each X4's W4 equals 13 more than each Z9's YYY. The number of each Z9's Y0 equals 16. How many W4 does each X4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Z9's Y0 = 16. Z9's YYY = Z9's YYY = 16.\nDefine each X4's W4 as u. So u = 13 * Z9's Y0 = 13 * 16 = 1.\nDefine each X4's WWW as S. So S = u = 1.\nDefine each Y1's l0 as A. So A = 2.\nDefine each Y1's lWW as i. So i = A * S = 2 * 1 = 2.\nDefine each Z9's YYY as Y. So Y = Z9's Y0 = 16.\nDefine each X4's WWW as F. So F = u = 1.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as r. So r = A * F = 2 * 1 = 2.\nDefine each Z9's YYY as l. So l = Z9's Y0 = 16.\nDefine each X4's W4 as V. So V = 13 + l = 13 + 16 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 550, "question": "The number of each Y1's X1 equals 14 more than the difference of each Y7's WWW and each X5's WWW. The number of each Y1's X5 equals 11 times the sum of each X5's WWW, each Y7's WWW and each Y7's X5. The number of each X5's W4 equals 5. The number of each Y7's X5 equals 20 more than each X5's W4. How many XXX does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["X5's W4 as u. So u = 5.\nDefine each X5's WWW as S. So S = u = 5.\nDefine each Y7's X5 as A. So A = 20 * u = 20 * 5 = 8.\nDefine each Y7's WWW as i. So i = A * S = 8 * 5 = 17.\nDefine each Y1's X5 as Y. So Y = 11 * (S + i + A) = 11 * (5 + 17 + 8) = 19.\nDefine each Y1's X1 as F. So F = 14 + i - S = 14 + 17 - 5 = 3.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as r. So r = Y + F = 19 + 3 = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 551, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y7 equals 3. The number of each Y7's X2 equals 12 more than each Z0's YYY. The number of each Z6's Y9 equals the difference of each Z0's YYY and each Y7's XXX. The number of each Z0's Y7 equals the sum of each Z0's Y9 and each Z6's Y7. The number of each Z0's Y9 equals 14 more than each Z6's Y7. The number of each Y9's X2 equals each Z6's Y9. How many X2 does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["Z6's Y7 = 3. Z0's Y9 as u. So u = 14 * S = 14 * 3 = 19.\nDefine each Z0's Y7 as S. So S = u + S = 19 + 3 = 22.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 22 + 19 = 18.\nDefine each Y7's X2 as i. So i = 12 * A = 12 * 18 = 9.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as Y. So Y = i = 9.\nDefine each Z6's Y9 as F. So F = A - Y = 18 - 9 = 9.\nDefine each Y9's X2 as r. So r = F = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 552, "question": "The number of each Y0's X3 equals each Z0's YYY. The number of each Z0's Y5 equals 18. The number of each Y0's X4 equals 4 times each Z0's Y5. The number of each X9's W8 equals the sum of each Y0's XXX, each Y0's X4 and each Z0's Y5. How many WWW does each X9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Z0's Y5 as u. So u = 18.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as S. So S = u = 18.\nDefine each Y0's X3 as A. So A = S = 18.\nDefine each Y0's X4 as i. So i = 4 * u = 4 * 18 = 3.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as Y. So Y = A + i = 18 + 3 = 21.\nDefine each X9's W8 as F. So F = (Y + i + u) = (21 + 3 + 18) = 19.\nDefine each X9's WWW as r. So r = F = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 553, "question": "The number of each Y9's X4 equals 22 times the sum of each Y7's X4, each Y9's X2 and each Y7's XXX. The number of each Y9's X2 equals 11 more than the difference of each Y7's XXX and each Y7's X4. The number of each Y7's X4 equals 9. How many XXX does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Y7's X4 as u. So u = 9.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as S. So S = u = 9.\nDefine each Y9's X2 as A. So A = 11 * S - u = 11 * 9 - 9 = 11.\nDefine each Y9's X4 as i. So i = 22 * (u + A + S) = 22 * (9 + 11 + 9) = 19.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as Y. So Y = i + A + A = 19 + 11 + 11 = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 554, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y7 equals 6 more than each X8's WWW. The number of each X8's W9 equals 9. The number of each X8's W7 equals 7 times each X8's W9. How many Y7 does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["X8's W9 as u. So u = 9.\nDefine each X8's W7 as S. So S = 7 * u = 7 * 9 = 17.\nDefine each X8's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 17 + 9 = 3.\nDefine each Z1's Y7 as i. So i = 6 * A = 6 * 3 = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 555, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y0 equals 20 times each Z1's YYY. The number of each Z4's Y8 equals 19 times each Z0's Y8. The number of each Z1's Y8 equals 10 more than the sum of each Z4's Y0, each Z0's Y8 and each Z1's Y4. The number of each Z0's Y8 equals 20. The number of each Z4's Y0 equals 22 more than each Z0's Y8. The number of each Z0's Y4 equals 5. The number of each Z1's Y4 equals each Z4's Y8. The number of each Z4's Y4 equals the sum of each Z0's Y0, each Z1's Y8 and each Z0's Y4. The number of each Z1's Y0 equals the sum of each Z0's Y4, each Z4's Y0, each Z1's Y4 and each Z1's Y8. How many Y4 does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Z0's Y8 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each Z4's Y0 as S. So S = 22 * u = 22 * 20 = 3.\nDefine each Z1's Y8 as A. So A = 10 * (S + u + S) = 10 * (3 + 20 + 3) = 19.\nDefine each Z4's Y8 as i. So i = 19 + u = 19 + 20 = 16.\nDefine each Z1's Y4 as Y. So Y = i = 16.\nDefine each Z0's Y4 as F. So F = 5.\nDefine each Z1's Y0 as r. So r = (F + S + Y + A) = (5 + 3 + 16 + 19) = 20.\nDefine each Z1's YYY as l. So l = r + A + Y = 20 + 19 + 16 = 9.\nDefine each Z0's Y0 as V. So V = 20 * l = 20 * 9 = 19.\nDefine each Z4's Y4 as q. So q = (V + A + F) = (19 + 19 + 5) = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 556, "question": "The number of each X7's W0 equals 18. How many W0 does each X7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["X7's W0 = 18.\nDefine each X7's WWW as u. So u = X7 = 18.\nDefine each Y1's l0 as S. So S = 2.\nDefine each Y1's lWW as A. So A = S * u = 2 * 18 = 13.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's l0 as i. So i = 2.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as Y. So Y = S + i = 2 + 2 = 4.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each X3's W0 as F. So F = 2.\nDefine each X3's WWW as r. So r = F = 2.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as l. So l = S + i = 2 + 2 = 4.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as V. So V = S + i = 2 + 2 = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 557, "question": "The number of each X9's W0 equals 8 more than each X9's W1. The number of each X9's W1 equals 11. The number of each Y2's X9 equals 12 more than the sum of each X9's W1 and each X9's W0. How many WWW does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["X9's W1 as u. So u = 11.\nDefine each X9's W0 as S. So S = 8 * u = 8 * 11 = 19.\nDefine each X9's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 19 + 11 = 7.\nDefine each Y2's X9 as i. So i = 12 * u + S = 12 * 11 + 19 = 16.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as Y. So Y = i * A = 16 * 7 = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 558, "question": "The number of each Y6's X0 equals 18 times the sum of each Y6's X2, each X0's W6 and each X2's W3. The number of each X2's W4 equals 2 more than the difference of each X2's W3 and each X8's W3. The number of each Y3's X8 equals 19 times each X8's W3. The number of each X2's W3 equals 11 more than the sum of each X8's W3 and each Y3's X8. The number of each Y6's X8 equals 7 more than the sum of each Y6's X0 and each Y3's X8. The number of each X8's W3 equals 20. The number of each X0's W4 equals the sum of each Y6's X8, each X8's W3 and each Y6's XXX. The number of each Y6's X2 equals 17 more than each X0's W6. The number of each X0's W6 equals 13 more than each X2's WWW. How many W4 does each X0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["X8's W3 = 20. Y3's X8 = 19 * u = 19 * 20 = 12.\nDefine each X2's W3 as u. So u = 11 * u + Y3's X8 = 11 * 20 + 12 = 10.\nDefine each X2's W4 as S. So S = 2 * u - u = 2 * 10 - 10 = 10.\nDefine each X2's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 10 + 10 = 20.\nDefine each X0's W6 as i. So i = 13 + A = 13 + 20 = 10.\nDefine each Y6's X2 as Y. So Y = 17 * i = 17 * 10 = 9.\nDefine each Y6's X0 as F. So F = 18 + (Y + i + u) = 18 + (9 + 10 + 10) = 1.\nDefine each Y6's X8 as r. So r = 7 * F + Y = 7 * 1 + 9 = 16.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as l. So l = r + Y + F = 16 + 9 + 1 = 3.\nDefine each X8's W3 as V. So V = 20.\nDefine each Y3's X8 as q. So q = 12.\nDefine each X2's W3 as z. So z = 11 * V + q = 11 * 20 + 12 = 10.\nDefine each X2's W4 as A. So A = 10 + u - V = 10 + 10 - 20 = 0.\nDefine each X2's WWW as i. So i = A + u = 0 + 10 = 10.\nDefine each l0's W6 as Y. So Y = 13 + i = 13 + 10 = 0.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as F. So F = r + Y + F = 16 + 0 + 1 = 17.\nDefine each X0's W4 as r. So r = (r + V + l) = (16 + 20 + 17) = 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 559, "question": "The number of each X3's W6 equals 5 times the difference of each Z6's Y0 and each Z1's Y4. The number of each Y0's X3 equals each Z1's Y4. The number of each Y4's X2 equals the sum of each X3's W6, each Y0's X3 and each Z6's WWW. The number of each X2's W6 equals the sum of each Y4's XXX, each Z6's WWW and each Y0's X3. The number of each Z1's Y4 equals 18. The number of each Z6's Y0 equals 19 more than the sum of each Z1's Y4 and each Y0's X3. How many WWW does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["Z1's Y4 as u. So u = 18.\nDefine each Y0's X3 as S. So S = u = 18.\nDefine each Z6's Y0 as A. So A = 19 * u + S = 19 * 18 + 18 = 2.\nDefine each X3's W6 as i. So i = 5 * A - u = 5 * 2 - 18 = 15.\nDefine each X3's WWW as Y. So Y = i = 15.\nDefine each Y0's WWW as F. So F = S * Y = 18 * 15 = 17.\nDefine each Z6's WWW as r. So r = A * F = 2 * 17 = 11.\nDefine each Y4's X2 as l. So l = (i + S + r) = (15 + 18 + 11) = 21.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as V. So V = l = 21.\nDefine each X2's W6 as q. So q = (V + r + S) = (21 + 11 + 18) = 4.\nDefine each X2's WWW as z. So z = q = 4.\nDefine each Y4's WWW as A. So A = l * Z = 21 * 4 = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 560, "question": "The number of each Y1's X6 equals 10. How many X6 does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Y1's X6 = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 561, "question": "The number of each Y1's X4 equals 13 more than the sum of each Y7's X4 and each Z7's Y1. The number of each X1's W3 equals 22 more than each Y7's X1. The number of each Z7's Y1 equals 9 more than each Y7's X4. The number of each Z1's Y9 equals the sum of each Y1's X4 and each Z7's Y1. The number of each Z7's Y7 equals 7 times each X1's W3. The number of each Y7's X1 equals 2 more than the sum of each X4's W3 and each Z7's Y1. The number of each Y7's X4 equals 18. The number of each Y9's X1 equals each Z1's Y9. The number of each X4's W3 equals 7 more than each Y9's X1. How many Y7 does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["Y7's X4 as u. So u = 18.\nDefine each Z7's Y1 as S. So S = 9 * u = 9 * 18 = 1.\nDefine each Y1's X4 as A. So A = 13 * u + S = 13 * 18 + 1 = 10.\nDefine each Z1's Y9 as i. So i = A + S = 10 + 1 = 11.\nDefine each Y9's X1 as Y. So Y = i = 11.\nDefine each X4's W3 as F. So F = 7 * Y = 7 * 11 = 8.\nDefine each Y7's X1 as r. So r = 2 * F + S = 2 * 8 + 1 = 17.\nDefine each X1's W3 as l. So l = 22 * r = 22 * 17 = 6.\nDefine each Z7's Y7 as V. So V = 7 * l = 7 * 6 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 562, "question": "The number of each Y4's X3 equals the sum of each Y6's XXX and each Y7's XXX. The number of each X3's W1 equals 17 times each Y6's XXX. The number of each Y7's X3 equals each X3's W1. The number of each Y7's X5 equals each Y7's X3. The number of each Y7's X8 equals 7 times each Y7's X3. The number of each Y6's X5 equals each Y6's X3. The number of each Y6's X8 equals 2 more than each Y6's X3. The number of each Y4's X8 equals 14 more than each Y6's X8. The number of each Y6's X3 equals 18 times each X8's W1. The number of each X8's W1 equals 6. How many XXX does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["X8's W1 = 6. Y6's X3 as u. So u = 18 * X8's W1 = 18 * 6 = 16.\nDefine each Y6's X8 as S. So S = 2 * u = 2 * 16 = 9.\nDefine each Y6's X5 as A. So A = u = 16.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as i. So i = S + A + u = 9 + 16 + 16 = 18.\nDefine each X3's W1 as Y. So Y = 17 * i = 17 * 18 = 7.\nDefine each Y7's X3 as F. So F = Y = 7.\nDefine each Y7's X8 as r. So r = 7 * F = 7 * 7 = 3.\nDefine each Y7's X5 as l. So l = F = 7.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as V. So V = l + r + F = 7 + 3 + 7 = 17.\nDefine each Y4's X3 as q. So q = i + V = 18 + 17 = 12.\nDefine each Y4's X8 as z. So z = 14 * S = 14 * 9 = 11.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as A. So A = q + z = 12 + 11 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 563, "question": "The number of each X1's W0 equals 5. How many W0 does each X1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["X1's W0 = 5. So 5.\nDefine each X1's WWW as u. So u = X1's W0 = 5.\nDefine each Y1's l0 as S. So S = 2.\nDefine each Y1's lWW as A. So A = S * u = 2 * 5 = 10.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's l0 as i. So i = 2.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as Y. So Y = S + i = 2 + 2 = 4.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each X3's W0 as F. So F = 5.\nDefine each X3's WWW as r. So r = F = 5.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as l. So l = S + i = 2 + 2 = 4.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as V. So V = S + i = 2 + 2 = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 564, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y5 equals 0. The number of each Z2's Y5 equals 15 more than each Z2's Y0. The number of each Z1's Y0 equals 20 times each Z8's Y5. The number of each Z1's Y7 equals 1 times the sum of each Z8's Y5 and each Z1's Y0. The number of each Z2's Y0 equals 9 times each Z1's Y7. How many Y5 does each Z2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["9 + 15 = 1.\nDefine each Z8's Y5 as u. So u = 0.\nDefine each Z1's Y0 as S. So S = 20 * u = 20 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z1's Y7 as A. So A = 1 * u + S = 1 * 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z2's Y0 as i. So i = 9 * A = 9 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z2's Y5 as Y. So Y = 15 + i = 15 + 0 = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 565, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y6 equals 8. How many Y6 does each Z3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["Z3's Y6 = 8.\nThus, the answer is 8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 566, "question": "The number of each X3's W4 equals each X9's W1. The number of each X9's W1 equals 7 more than each Y9's XXX. The number of each Y2's X6 equals each X3's W4. The number of each X8's W8 equals 11 more than each Y2's WWW. The number of each X6's W4 equals 4 more than each Y2's X6. The number of each Y9's X9 equals 13. How many W8 does each X8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["Y9's X9 = 13. Y9's XXX = 13. Y9's XXX = 13. Y2's X6 = X3's W1. Y2's XXX = Y2's X6 = 3.\nDefine each X9's W1 as u. So u = 7 * Y9's XXX = 7 * 13 = 22.\nDefine each X3's W4 as S. So S = u = 22.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as A. So A = Y2's X6 * X6 = 3 * 2 = 6.\nDefine each X8's W8 as i. So i = 11 * A = 11 * 6 = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 567, "question": "The number of each Y6's X7 equals 0. The number of each Z7's Y6 equals 17 times the difference of each Y6's WWW and each X7's W0. The number of each X7's W0 equals each X2's WWW. The number of each X2's W0 equals 6. How many WWW does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["X2's W0 as u. So u = 6.\nDefine each X2's WWW as S. So S = u = 6.\nDefine each X7's W0 as A. So A = S = 6.\nDefine each X7's WWW as i. So i = A = 6.\nDefine each Y6's X7 as Y. So Y = 0.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as F. So F = Y * i = 0 * 6 = 0.\nDefine each Z7's Y6 as r. So r = 17 * F - A = 17 * 0 - 6 = 17.\nDefine each Z7's WWW as l. So l = r * F = 17 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 568, "question": "The number of each X4's W9 equals the sum of each Y1's X3, each X2's W9, each X3's WWW and each X2's WWW. The number of each X2's W9 equals 18 more than the difference of each Y1's X3 and each Y9's X2. The number of each Y3's X2 equals 19 times the sum of each Y9's X2 and each X4's W9. The number of each Y9's X2 equals 1 times the sum of each Y1's X2 and each Y1's X3. The number of each X3's W9 equals each Y9's X2. The number of each X3's W6 equals each Y9's WWW. The number of each Y1's X2 equals 9 more than each Y1's X3. The number of each Y1's X3 equals 1. How many WWW does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["Y1's X3 = 1. So Y1's X2 = 9 * u = 9 * 1 = 9.\nDefine each Y1's X2 as u. So u = 9 * u = 9 * 9 = 12.\nDefine each Y9's X2 as S. So S = 1 * u + u = 1 * 12 + 1 = 13.\nDefine each X2's W9 as A. So A = 18 * u - S = 18 * 12 - 13 = 19.\nDefine each X2's WWW as i. So i = A = 19.\nDefine each Y9's WWW as Y. So Y = S * i = 13 * 19 = 17.\nDefine each X3's W6 as F. So F = Y = 17.\nDefine each X3's W9 as r. So r = S = 13.\nDefine each X3's WWW as l. So l = r + F = 13 + 17 = 7.\nDefine each X4's W9 as V. So V = (Y + A + l + i) = (17 + 19 + 7 + 19) = 16.\nDefine each Y3's X2 as q. So q = 19 * S + V = 19 * 13 + 16 = 17.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as z. So z = q * i = 17 * 19 = 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 569, "question": "The number of each Y8's X8 equals 6. The number of each Z5's Y8 equals 8 more than each Y8's XXX. How many XXX does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Y8's X8 = 6. Y8's XXX = 6. Y8's XXX = 6. Y8's XXX = 6. Y8's XXX = 6. Y8's XXX = 6. Y8's XXX = 6. Y8's XXX = 6. Y8's XXX = 6. Y8's XXX = 6. Y8's XXX = 6. Y8's XXX = 6. Y8's XXX = 6. Y8's XXX = 6. Y8's XXX = 6. Y8's XXX = 6. Y8's XXX = 6. Y8's XXX = 6. Y8's XXX = 6. Y8's XXX = 6. Y8's XXX = 6. Y8's XXX = 6. Y8's XXX = 6. Y8's XXX = 6. Y8's XXX = 6. Y8's XXX = 6. Y8's XXX = 6. Y8's XXX = 6. Y8's XXX = 6. Y8's XXX = 6. Y8's XXX as u. So u = 6. Y8's XXX as S. So S = 6. Y8's XXX as A. So A = 6. Y8's XXX as i. So i = 6. Y8's XXX as Y. So Y = 6. Y8's XXX as F. So F = 6. Y8's XXX as r. So r = Y + i + u + S = 6 + 6 + 6 + 6 = 1.\nDefine each Z5's Y8 as l. So l = 8 * S = 8 * 1 = 8.\nDefine each Z5's XXX as V. So V = l * r = 8 * 1 = 8.\nThus, the answer is 8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 570, "question": "The number of each X5's W2 equals 7. The number of each X0's W2 equals 17 more than the difference of each X5's WWW and each X5's W2. The number of each X5's W8 equals 14. How many W2 does each X0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["X5's W8 as u. So u = 14.\nDefine each X5's W2 as S. So S = 7.\nDefine each X5's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 7 + 14 = 21.\nDefine each X0's W2 as i. So i = 17 * A - S = 17 * 21 - 7 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 571, "question": "The number of each Y6's X5 equals 16 more than the sum of each Y6's X6, each X5's WWW and each X5's W2. The number of each Y0's X5 equals 1 times the sum of each Y6's X5, each X5's W2 and each X5's WWW. The number of each X6's W2 equals 4 times the sum of each X5's WWW, each Y0's X5 and each X5's W2. The number of each X5's W2 equals each Y6's X6. The number of each Y6's X6 equals 6. How many W2 does each X6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Y6's X6 as u. So u = 6.\nDefine each X5's W2 as S. So S = u = 6.\nDefine each X5's WWW as A. So A = S = 6.\nDefine each Y6's X5 as i. So i = 16 * (u + A + S) = 16 * (6 + 6 + 6) = 15.\nDefine each Y0's X5 as Y. So Y = 1 * (i + S + A) = 1 * (15 + 6 + 6) = 4.\nDefine each X6's W2 as F. So F = 4 * (A + Y + S) = 4 * (6 + 4 + 6) = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 572, "question": "The number of each Y3's X8 equals 0. How many XXX does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y3's X8 = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's X8 = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's X8 = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's X8 = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's X8 = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's X8 = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y3's XXX = 0. Y"], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 573, "question": "The number of each Y0's X1 equals 18 more than the difference of each Y3's X9 and each Y3's XXX. The number of each Y3's X9 equals 17. How many X1 does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["Y3's X9 as u. So u = 17.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as S. So S = u = 17.\nDefine each Y0's X1 as A. So A = 18 * u - S = 18 * 17 - 17 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 574, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y4 equals 19. The number of each Z0's Y6 equals 22 more than each Z3's Y4. The number of each Z0's Y4 equals each Z3's Y4. How many YYY does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Z3's Y4 = 19. Z0's Y6 as u. So u = 22 * Z3's Y4 = 22 * 19 = 4.\nDefine each Z0's Y4 as S. So S = Z3's Y4 = 19.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 19 + 4 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 575, "question": "The number of each Y9's X0 equals 0. How many X0 does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y9's X0 = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX = 0. Y9's XXX ="], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 576, "question": "The number of each X5's W9 equals 20. How many W9 does each X5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["X5's W9 = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 577, "question": "The number of each Y8's X2 equals 12. How many X2 does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["Y8's X2 = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 578, "question": "The number of each X5's W6 equals each X4's W7. The number of each X4's W7 equals 17 times the difference of each X7's W2 and each X6's W7. The number of each X7's W2 equals 18. The number of each X6's W7 equals 0 times each X7's W2. How many W6 does each X5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["X7's W2 = 18. X6's W7 = 0 * X7's W2 = 0 * 18 = 0.\nDefine each X4's W7 as u. So u = 17 * X7's W2 - S = 17 * 18 - 0 = 7.\nDefine each X5's W6 as S. So S = u = 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 579, "question": "The number of each X9's W9 equals 4. The number of each X9's W0 equals each X9's W9. The number of each X3's W9 equals 12 times each X9's WWW. How many W9 does each X3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["X9's W9 as u. So u = 4.\nDefine each X9's W0 as S. So S = u = 4.\nDefine each X9's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 4 + 4 = 8.\nDefine each X3's W9 as i. So i = 12 * A = 12 * 8 = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 580, "question": "The number of each Y5's X5 equals 19. The number of each Y5's X1 equals the difference of each Y5's X5 and each Y4's X1. The number of each Y4's X1 equals 19. The number of each Y4's X8 equals 22 times each Y4's X1. The number of each Y5's X8 equals 7 times each Y4's X5. The number of each Y4's X5 equals 18 times each Y4's X8. The number of each Y1's X8 equals 9 more than each Y1's X5. The number of each Y1's X5 equals each Y5's XXX. How many X8 does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["Y4's X1 = 19. Y4's X8 = 22 * Y4's X1 = 22 * 19 = 4.\nDefine each Y4's X5 as u. So u = 18 * Y4's X8 = 18 * 4 = 3.\nDefine each Y5's X8 as S. So S = 7 * u = 7 * 3 = 21.\nDefine each Y5's X5 as A. So A = 19.\nDefine each Y4's X1 as i. So i = 19.\nDefine each Y5's X1 as Y. So Y = A - i = 19 - 19 = 0.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as F. So F = S + A + Y = 21 + 19 + 0 = 17.\nDefine each Y1's X5 as r. So r = F = 17.\nDefine each Y1's X8 as l. So l = 9 * r = 9 * 17 = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 581, "question": "The number of each Z2's Y5 equals 1. How many Y5 does each Z2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Z2's Y5 = 1. So 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 582, "question": "The number of each Y5's X9 equals 15 more than the sum of each Z1's YYY and each Z1's Y0. The number of each Y0's X2 equals the sum of each Y5's X9, each Z1's Y0, each X9's W5 and each X2's WWW. The number of each Z1's Y0 equals 4. The number of each X2's W7 equals the sum of each Z9's WWW and each Y5's WWW. The number of each X9's W5 equals 7. The number of each X2's W5 equals the sum of each X9's WWW and each Y5's X9. The number of each Z9's Y5 equals 7 times the sum of each Y5's WWW and each Y5's X9. How many WWW does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["Z1's Y0 as u. So u = 4.\nDefine each Z1's YYY as S. So S = u = 4.\nDefine each Y5's X9 as A. So A = 15 * S + u = 15 * 4 + 4 = 18.\nDefine each X9's W5 as i. So i = 7.\nDefine each X9's WWW as Y. So Y = i = 7.\nDefine each Y5's WWW as F. So F = A * Y = 18 * 7 = 11.\nDefine each Z9's Y5 as r. So r = 7 * F + A = 7 * 11 + 18 = 19.\nDefine each Z9's WWW as l. So l = r * F = 19 * 11 = 2.\nDefine each X2's W7 as V. So V = l + F = 2 + 11 = 13.\nDefine each X2's W5 as q. So q = Y + A = 7 + 18 = 2.\nDefine each X2's WWW as z. So z = q + V = 2 + 13 = 15.\nDefine each Y0's X2 as A. So A = (A + u + i + S) = (18 + 4 + 7 + 4) = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 583, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y3 equals each Z9's YYY. The number of each Z9's Y8 equals each Z1's YYY. The number of each Z1's Y8 equals 14 more than each Z0's Y8. The number of each Z9's Y3 equals 21 times each Z1's YYY. The number of each Z1's Y3 equals 19 times the difference of each Z0's Y6 and each Z0's Y8. The number of each Z0's Y6 equals 0 times each Z0's Y8. The number of each Z1's Y6 equals 14. The number of each Z9's Y6 equals the sum of each Z0's Y6 and each Z1's YYY. The number of each Z0's Y8 equals 7. How many Y3 does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["7. So 7.\nDefine each Z0's Y8 as u. So u = 7.\nDefine each Z0's Y6 as S. So S = 0 * u = 0 * 7 = 0.\nDefine each Z1's Y3 as A. So A = 19 * S - u = 19 * 0 - 7 = 16.\nDefine each Z1's Y6 as i. So i = 14.\nDefine each Z1's Y8 as Y. So Y = 14 * u = 14 * 7 = 6.\nDefine each Z1's YYY as F. So F = Y + A + i = 6 + 16 + 14 = 13.\nDefine each Z9's Y3 as r. So r = 21 * F = 21 * 13 = 20.\nDefine each Z9's Y6 as l. So l = S + F = 0 + 13 = 13.\nDefine each Z9's Y8 as V. So V = F = 13.\nDefine each Z9's YYY as q. So q = V + l + r = 13 + 13 + 20 = 0.\nDefine each Z0's Y3 as z. So z = q = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 584, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y1 equals 11 times each Z9's XXX. The number of each Z9's Y4 equals 3. The number of each Y4's X9 equals 6. The number of each Y3's X7 equals the sum of each Z9's XXX and each Z1's XXX. The number of each Y1's X8 equals 19 more than the difference of each Y4's X9 and each Y4's XXX. How many X7 does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["Y4's X9 as u. So u = 6.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as S. So S = u = 6.\nDefine each Z9's Y4 as A. So A = 3.\nDefine each Z9's XXX as i. So i = A * S = 3 * 6 = 18.\nDefine each Z1's Y1 as Y. So Y = 11 * i = 11 * 18 = 14.\nDefine each Y1's X8 as F. So F = 19 * u - S = 19 * 6 - 6 = 16.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as r. So r = F = 16.\nDefine each Z1's XXX as l. So l = Y * r = 14 * 16 = 17.\nDefine each Y3's X7 as V. So V = i + l = 18 + 17 = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 585, "question": "The number of each X8's W2 equals 8. The number of each X2's W4 equals 19 times the sum of each X6's W4, each Y7's X6 and each X8's W2. The number of each X6's W4 equals 22 more than each X8's W2. The number of each Y7's X6 equals 3 more than each X6's W4. The number of each X6's W2 equals 3 times the sum of each X8's W2, each X2's WWW and each X6's W4. How many W2 does each X6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["X8's W2 = 8. X6's W4 = 22 * u = 22 * 8 = 15.\nDefine each Y7's X6 as u. So u = 3 * X6's W4 = 3 * 15 = 22.\nDefine each X2's W4 as S. So S = 19 * (6 + u + X8's W2) = 19 * (15 + 22 + 8) = 19.\nDefine each X2's WWW as A. So A = S = 19.\nDefine each X6's W2 as i. So i = 3 * (u + A + X6's W4) = 3 * (22 + 19 + 15) = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 586, "question": "The number of each Y5's X4 equals 21 times each Y5's X5. The number of each Z9's Y5 equals each Y5's X4. The number of each X5's W3 equals each Z9's XXX. The number of each Z4's Y5 equals 12 more than each X4's WWW. The number of each X4's W8 equals the difference of each Z9's XXX and each X5's W3. The number of each Y5's X5 equals 3. The number of each X4's W3 equals 10 times each Z9's Y5. How many Y5 does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["Y5's X5 as u. So u = 3.\nDefine each Y5's X4 as S. So S = 21 * u = 21 * 3 = 17.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 17 + 3 = 20.\nDefine each Z9's Y5 as i. So i = S = 17.\nDefine each Z9's XXX as Y. So Y = i * A = 17 * 20 = 18.\nDefine each X5's W3 as F. So F = Y = 18.\nDefine each X4's W8 as r. So r = Y - F = 18 - 18 = 0.\nDefine each X4's W3 as l. So l = 10 * i = 10 * 17 = 9.\nDefine each X4's WWW as V. So V = l + r = 9 + 0 = 9.\nDefine each Z4's Y5 as q. So q = 12 * V = 12 * 9 = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 587, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y9 equals 7. The number of each Z6's Y3 equals 12 more than each Z9's Y9. The number of each Z9's Y0 equals 18 times each Z6's Y3. How many Y0 does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Z9's Y9 as u. So u = 7.\nDefine each Z6's Y3 as S. So S = 12 * u = 12 * 7 = 15.\nDefine each Z9's Y0 as A. So A = 18 * S = 18 * 15 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 588, "question": "The number of each X3's W5 equals 18. The number of each X4's W7 equals each X3's W5. The number of each X1's W5 equals each X4's W7. The number of each X1's W7 equals each X1's W3. The number of each X1's W3 equals 14 times each X1's W5. How many W7 does each X1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["X3's W5 = 18. X4's W7 = X3's W5 = 18.\nDefine each X1's W5 as u. So u = r = 18.\nDefine each X1's W3 as S. So S = 14 * u = 14 * 18 = 22.\nDefine each X1's W7 as A. So A = S = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 589, "question": "The number of each Y4's X4 equals 15. How many X4 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Y4's X4 = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 590, "question": "The number of each Y4's X9 equals 18 more than each Z8's WWW. The number of each X9's W6 equals 4 more than each Z3's Y4. The number of each Y4's X7 equals 13 more than each Y4's X9. The number of each Z8's Y9 equals 12 more than the sum of each Y7's X9 and each X9's W6. The number of each Y9's X9 equals 22 times each X9's W6. The number of each Z3's Y4 equals 10. The number of each Y7's X9 equals each Y9's X9. How many X7 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Z3's Y4 = 10. X9's W6 = 4 * Z3's Y4 = 4 * 10 = 17.\nDefine each Y9's X9 as u. So u = 22 * S = 22 * 17 = 6.\nDefine each Y7's X9 as S. So S = u = 6.\nDefine each Z8's Y9 as A. So A = 12 * S + u = 12 * 6 + 17 = 10.\nDefine each X9's WWW as i. So i = X9's W6 = 17.\nDefine each Y9's WWW as Y. So Y = u * i = 6 * 17 = 10.\nDefine each Z8's WWW as F. So F = A * Y = 10 * 10 = 8.\nDefine each Y4's X9 as r. So r = 18 + F = 18 + 8 = 3.\nDefine each Y4's X7 as l. So l = 13 + r = 13 + 3 = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 591, "question": "The number of each Y7's X7 equals the sum of each Y6's XXX and each Y9's X5. The number of each Y0's X0 equals 14 times each Y9's X5. The number of each Y9's X5 equals 21. The number of each Y6's X7 equals the difference of each Y0's X0 and each Y9's X5. How many X7 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["Y9's X5 = 21. Y0's X0 = 14 * Y9's X5 = 14.\nDefine each Y6's X7 as u. So u = A - Y9's X5 = 12 - 21 = 14.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as S. So S = u = 14.\nDefine each Y7's X7 as A. So A = S + Y9's X5 = 14 + 21 = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 592, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y3 equals 4. The number of each Y2's X4 equals 13 times each Z6's Y7. The number of each Y2's X2 equals 13 more than each Z9's Y3. The number of each Z9's Y7 equals 14. The number of each Z6's Y7 equals 13 times each Z9's YYY. The number of each Z8's Y2 equals each Y2's X2. The number of each Y2's X1 equals 7. The number of each Z9's Y2 equals 14 more than each Z9's Y7. How many XXX does each Z8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["Z9's Y7 as u. So u = 14.\nDefine each Z9's Y2 as S. So S = 14 * u = 14 * 14 = 12.\nDefine each Z9's Y3 as A. So A = 4.\nDefine each Z9's YYY as i. So i = S + A + u = 12 + 4 + 14 = 7.\nDefine each Z6's Y7 as Y. So Y = 13 * i = 13 * 7 = 22.\nDefine each Y2's X4 as F. So F = 13 * Y = 13 * 22 = 10.\nDefine each Y2's X2 as r. So r = 13 * A = 13 * 4 = 6.\nDefine each Z8's Y2 as l. So l = r = 6.\nDefine each Y2's X1 as V. So V = 7.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as q. So q = r + V + F = 6 + 7 + 10 = 0.\nDefine each Z8's XXX as z. So z = l * q = 6 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 593, "question": "The number of each Z2's Y4 equals the difference of each X6's W4 and each X6's WWW. The number of each X6's W4 equals 0 more than the difference of each X0's WWW and each X0's W4. The number of each Y4's X0 equals 13. The number of each X0's W4 equals 1 more than each Y4's X0. How many Y4 does each Z2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y4's X0 = 13. X0's W4 as u. So u = 1 * Y4's X0 = 13 * 13 = 8.\nDefine each X0's WWW as S. So S = u = 8.\nDefine each Y4's WWW as A. So A = Y4's X0 * S = 13 * 8 = 12.\nDefine each X6's W4 as i. So i = 0 * S - u = 0 * 8 - 8 = 15.\nDefine each X6's WWW as Y. So Y = i = 15.\nDefine each Z2's Y4 as F. So F = i - Y = 15 - 15 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 594, "question": "The number of each Y6's X2 equals 10. The number of each X2's W7 equals 9 more than each Z1's XXX. The number of each Z1's Y6 equals 5. How many W7 does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["Y6's X2 as u. So u = 10.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as S. So S = u = 10.\nDefine each Z1's Y6 as A. So A = 5.\nDefine each Z1's XXX as i. So i = A * S = 5 * 10 = 4.\nDefine each X2's W7 as Y. So Y = 9 * i = 9 * 4 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 595, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y3 equals 0. The number of each Z5's Y3 equals 15 more than each Z1's YYY. How many YYY does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Z1's Y3 = 0. Z1's YYY = 0. Z5's Y3 = 15 * Z1's Y0 = 15 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z1's YYY as u. So u = Z1's Y3 = 0.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as S. So S = Z5's Y3 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 596, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y4 equals 8 more than the difference of each X4's WWW and each X4's W5. The number of each Y2's X8 equals the difference of each Z3's WWW and each Y4's WWW. The number of each X4's W6 equals 17 more than each Y4's XXX. The number of each X4's W5 equals 9 more than the difference of each Y4's X4 and each Y4's XXX. The number of each Y4's X4 equals 22. How many X8 does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y4's X4 as u. So u = 22.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as S. So S = u = 22.\nDefine each X4's W6 as A. So A = 17 * S = 17 * 22 = 6.\nDefine each X4's W5 as i. So i = 9 * u - S = 9 * 22 - 22 = 15.\nDefine each X4's WWW as Y. So Y = A + i = 6 + 15 = 21.\nDefine each Y4's WWW as F. So F = u * Y = 22 * 21 = 2.\nDefine each Z3's Y4 as r. So r = 8 + Y - i = 8 + 21 - 15 = 14.\nDefine each Z3's WWW as l. So l = r * F = 14 * 2 = 5.\nDefine each Y2's X8 as V. So V = l - F = 5 - 2 = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 597, "question": "The number of each X3's W8 equals the sum of each X8's WWW, each Y3's X8, each Y4's X8 and each Y3's WWW. The number of each Y9's X8 equals the sum of each Y3's WWW, each Y4's WWW and each X8's WWW. The number of each X8's W7 equals 17. The number of each Y4's X8 equals the difference of each X8's WWW and each Y3's WWW. The number of each Y1's X3 equals 16 times each Y9's WWW. The number of each Y3's X8 equals each X8's WWW. How many WWW does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["X8's W7 as u. So u = 17.\nDefine each X8's WWW as S. So S = u = 17.\nDefine each Y3's X8 as A. So A = S = 17.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as i. So i = A * S = 17 * 17 = 13.\nDefine each Y4's X8 as Y. So Y = S - i = 17 - 13 = 4.\nDefine each Y4's WWW as F. So F = Y * S = 4 * 17 = 22.\nDefine each Y9's X8 as r. So r = (i + F + S) = (13 + 22 + 17) = 6.\nDefine each Y9's WWW as l. So l = r * S = 6 * 17 = 10.\nDefine each Y1's X3 as V. So V = 16 * l = 16 * 10 = 22.\nDefine each X3's W8 as q. So q = (S + A + Y + i) = (17 + 17 + 4 + 13) = 5.\nDefine each X3's WWW as z. So z = q = 5.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as A. So A = V * Z = 22 * 5 = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 598, "question": "The number of each Y0's X8 equals 17. The number of each X0's W2 equals 21 times each Y0's X8. The number of each Y6's X0 equals 4 more than each Y0's X8. How many WWW does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["Y0's X8 = 17. Y6's X0 = 4 * Y0's X8 = 4 * 17 = 22.\nDefine each X0's W2 as u. So u = 21 * Y0's X8 = 21 * 17 = 12.\nDefine each X0's WWW as S. So S = u = 12.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as A. So A = Y6's X0 * S = 22 * 12 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 599, "question": "The number of each Y8's X5 equals 4. How many XXX does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["Y8's X5 = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX = 4. Y8's XXX as u. So u = 4. Y8's XXX as S. So S = 4. Y8's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 4 + 4 = 8. Y8's XXX as i. So i = S + A + u = 8 + 8 + 4 = 20. Y8's XXX as Y. So Y = S + A + u = 20 + 8 + 20 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 600, "question": "The number of each Y4's X8 equals 8. The number of each Y0's X8 equals 19 more than each Y4's X8. How many X8 does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["Y4's X8 = 8. Y0's X8 = 19 * Y4's X8 = 19 * 8 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 601, "question": "The number of each X4's W2 equals 12. The number of each Z4's Y6 equals 16 times each X2's W3. The number of each X2's W3 equals 15 times each X2's W2. The number of each Y6's X2 equals 19 times each X2's W3. The number of each X2's W2 equals each X4's W2. How many WWW does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["X4's W2 = 12. X2's W2 = X4's W2 = 12.\nDefine each X2's W3 as u. So u = 15 * u = 15 * 12 = 19.\nDefine each X2's WWW as S. So S = u = 19.\nDefine each Y6's X2 as A. So A = 19 * u = 19 * 19 = 16.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as i. So i = A * S = 16 * 19 = 5.\nDefine each Z4's Y6 as Y. So Y = 16 * u = 16 * 19 = 5.\nDefine each Z4's WWW as F. So F = Y * i = 5 * 5 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 602, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y0 equals 4. The number of each X0's W4 equals 8 times the sum of each Y8's XXX, each Y8's X2 and each Z3's Y0. The number of each Y8's X2 equals each Z3's Y0. How many W4 does each X0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["Z3's Y0 = 4. Y8's X2 = Z3's Y0 = 4.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as u. So u = Y8 = 8.\nDefine each X0's W4 as S. So S = 8 * (u + Y8's X2 + Z3's Y0) = 8 * (8 + 8 + 4) = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 603, "question": "The number of each X8's W6 equals 18. The number of each X5's W6 equals 9 more than each X8's WWW. The number of each X8's W3 equals each X8's W6. The number of each Y5's X5 equals 6 more than the sum of each X5's W6 and each X8's W3. How many WWW does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y5's X5 as u. So u = 6 * X5's W6 + X8's W6 = 6 * 9 + 18 = 19.\nDefine each X8's W6 as S. So S = 18.\nDefine each X8's W3 as A. So A = S = 18.\nDefine each X8's WWW as i. So i = S + A = 18 + 18 = 13.\nDefine each X5's W6 as Y. So Y = 9 + i = 9 + 13 = 22.\nDefine each X5's WWW as F. So F = Y = 22.\nDefine each Y5's WWW as r. So r = u * F = 19 * 22 = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 604, "question": "The number of each Y2's X2 equals 14 more than each X4's W5. The number of each X9's W5 equals 5 more than each Y7's X9. The number of each X4's W5 equals 2 more than each Y7's WWW. The number of each Y7's X9 equals each X9's W9. The number of each X9's W9 equals 22. How many X2 does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["X9's W9 as u. So u = 22.\nDefine each Y7's X9 as S. So S = u = 22.\nDefine each X9's W5 as A. So A = 5 * S = 5 * 22 = 18.\nDefine each X9's WWW as i. So i = A + u = 18 + 22 = 17.\nDefine each Y7's WWW as Y. So Y = S * i = 22 * 17 = 6.\nDefine each X4's W5 as F. So F = 2 * Y = 2 * 6 = 12.\nDefine each Y2's X2 as r. So r = 14 * F = 14 * 12 = 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 605, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y0 equals the difference of each Y0's XXX and each Y0's X7. The number of each Y0's X4 equals each Y2's X4. The number of each Y2's X6 equals 20. The number of each Y0's X7 equals 9 times the sum of each Y2's X6 and each Y0's X4. The number of each Y0's X6 equals 12 times each Y0's X7. The number of each Y2's X4 equals 8 more than each Y2's X6. How many Y0 does each Z3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Y2's X6 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each Y2's X4 as S. So S = 8 * u = 8 * 20 = 22.\nDefine each Y0's X4 as A. So A = S = 22.\nDefine each Y0's X7 as i. So i = 9 * u + A = 9 * 20 + 22 = 18.\nDefine each Y0's X6 as Y. So Y = 12 * i = 12 * 18 = 9.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as F. So F = Y + i + A = 9 + 18 + 22 = 3.\nDefine each Z3's Y0 as r. So r = F - i = 3 - 18 = 8.\nThus, the answer is 8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 606, "question": "The number of each X5's W6 equals 19. The number of each X9's W3 equals 17 times the difference of each X5's WWW and each X5's W6. How many W3 does each X9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["X5's W6 = 19. X5's WWW = 19. X9's W3 = 17 * X5's W6 - u = 17 * 19 - 23 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 607, "question": "The number of each Y9's X9 equals 2 more than each Y5's X4. The number of each Y5's X4 equals 0 more than each Y9's X0. The number of each Y6's X4 equals 2. The number of each Y2's X9 equals 16 times each Y6's X4. The number of each Y5's X3 equals 5 times each Y9's X9. The number of each Y9's X0 equals each Y2's X9. How many X3 does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["Y6's X4 = 2. Y2's X9 = 16 * Y6's X4 = 16 * 2 = 9.\nDefine each Y9's X0 as u. So u = S = 9.\nDefine each Y5's X4 as S. So S = 0 * u = 0 * 9 = 0.\nDefine each Y9's X9 as A. So A = 2 * S = 2 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y5's X3 as i. So i = 5 * A = 5 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 608, "question": "The number of each Y5's X3 equals 14. The number of each Y5's X6 equals each Z7's YYY. The number of each Z7's Y5 equals 13 more than each Y5's X3. The number of each Z7's Y3 equals 20 more than each Z7's Y5. How many X6 does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Y5's X3 as u. So u = 14.\nDefine each Z7's Y5 as S. So S = 13 * u = 13 * 14 = 21.\nDefine each Z7's Y3 as A. So A = 20 * S = 20 * 21 = 6.\nDefine each Z7's YYY as i. So i = S + A = 21 + 6 = 4.\nDefine each Y5's X6 as Y. So Y = i = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 609, "question": "The number of each X0's W0 equals 13 more than each X9's WWW. The number of each X9's W2 equals 12. How many WWW does each X0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["X9's W2 as u. So u = 12.\nDefine each X9's WWW as S. So S = u = 12.\nDefine each X0's W0 as A. So A = 13 * S = 13 * 12 = 18.\nDefine each X0's WWW as i. So i = A = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 610, "question": "The number of each Z2's Y8 equals 7. How many Y8 does each Z2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["Z2's Y8 = 7. So 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 611, "question": "The number of each X8's W3 equals the difference of each X8's W6 and each X9's W6. The number of each X2's W3 equals the sum of each X8's W6, each X8's WWW and each X8's W3. The number of each X9's W6 equals 4. The number of each X8's W8 equals 11 times the sum of each X8's W3 and each X8's W6. The number of each X8's W6 equals 9 more than each X9's W6. How many W3 does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["X9's W6 = 4. X8's W6 as u. So u = 9 * S = 9 * 4 = 13.\nDefine each X8's W3 as S. So S = u - u = 13 - 13 = 0.\nDefine each X8's W8 as A. So A = 11 * S + u = 11 * 0 + 13 = 13.\nDefine each X8's WWW as i. So i = S + A + u = 0 + 13 + 13 = 3.\nDefine each X2's W3 as Y. So Y = (u + i + S) = (13 + 3 + 0) = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 612, "question": "The number of each Y4's X7 equals 18 times each Y8's XXX. The number of each Y8's X6 equals 2. The number of each Y8's X7 equals 4. How many X7 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Y8's X7 as u. So u = 4.\nDefine each Y8's X6 as S. So S = 2.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as A. So A = S + u + u = 2 + 4 + 4 = 10.\nDefine each Y4's X7 as i. So i = 18 * A = 18 * 10 = 19.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as Y. So Y = i = 19.\nDefine each X3's XXX as F. So F = i = 19.\nDefine each X2's XXX as r. So r = S + F = 2 + 19 = 21.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as l. So l = S + u + u = 2 + 4 + 4 = 10.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as V. So V = i = 19.\nDefine each X2's XXX as q. So q = r = 21.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as z. So z = i = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 613, "question": "The number of each X5's W8 equals 18. How many W8 does each X5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["X5's W8 = 18.\nDefine each X5's WWW as u. So u = X8.\nDefine each Y1's l0 as S. So S = 20.\nDefine each Y1's l0 as A. So A = 20.\nDefine each Y1's lWW as i. So i = S * u + A * u = 20 * 20 + 20 * 8 = 19.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's lWW as l. So l = S * i + A * u = 20 * 19 + 20 * 8 = 17.\nDefine each X8. So X8 = 8.\nDefine each X5's W8 as V. So V = 18.\nDefine each X5's WWW as q. So q = V = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 614, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y2 equals 0 more than each Z7's Y7. The number of each Z7's Y7 equals 17. How many YYY does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["Z7's Y7 as u. So u = 17.\nDefine each Z7's Y2 as S. So S = 0 * u = 0 * 17 = 0.\nDefine each Z7's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 0 + 17 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 615, "question": "The number of each Y9's X7 equals 11 times each Z7's Y9. The number of each Z7's Y9 equals 5. How many X7 does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["Z7's Y9 = 5. Y9's X7 = 11 * Z7's Y9 = 11 * 5 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 616, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y7 equals 10 times each Z7's Y5. The number of each Z7's Y8 equals 5 more than each Z1's Y7. The number of each Z8's Y7 equals the difference of each Z1's Y7 and each Z7's Y8. The number of each Z7's Y5 equals 1 times the difference of each Z7's Y8 and each Z8's Y7. The number of each Z1's Y7 equals 20. How many Y7 does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Z1's Y7 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each Z7's Y8 as S. So S = 5 * u = 5 * 20 = 8.\nDefine each Z8's Y7 as A. So A = u - S = 20 - 8 = 12.\nDefine each Z7's Y5 as i. So i = 1 * S - A = 1 * 8 - 12 = 19.\nDefine each Z7's Y7 as Y. So Y = 10 * i = 10 * 19 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 617, "question": "The number of each Y7's X9 equals 2. How many X9 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Y7's X9 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 618, "question": "The number of each X6's W0 equals each Z3's Y2. The number of each Z6's Y9 equals 18 times the sum of each X0's WWW, each Z4's WWW and each Z4's Y2. The number of each Z3's Y2 equals 11 more than each Z4's WWW. The number of each Y9's X6 equals 21 more than each X0's WWW. The number of each Z4's Y2 equals 2 times the sum of each Y2's X0 and each X0's W4. The number of each X0's W4 equals 21. The number of each Y2's X0 equals 18 times each X0's W4. How many WWW does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Z4's Y2 as u. So u = 2 * Y2's X0 + X0's W4 = 21.\nDefine each X0's W4 as S. So S = 21.\nDefine each X0's WWW as A. So A = S = 21.\nDefine each Y2's X0 as i. So i = 18 * S = 18 * 21 = 10.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as Y. So Y = i * A = 10 * 21 = 3.\nDefine each Z4's WWW as F. So F = u * Y = 21 * 3 = 17.\nDefine each Z3's Y2 as r. So r = 11 * F = 11 * 17 = 3.\nDefine each X6's W0 as l. So l = r = 3.\nDefine each X6's WWW as V. So V = l = 3.\nDefine each Y9's X6 as q. So q = 21 * A = 21 * 21 = 4.\nDefine each Y9's WWW as z. So z = q * V = 4 * 3 = 12.\nDefine each Z6's Y9 as A. So A = 18 + (A + F + u) = 18 + (12 + 17 + 3) = 4.\nDefine each Z6's WWW as i. So i = A * Z = 4 * 12 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 619, "question": "The number of each X8's W2 equals each X9's W5. The number of each X8's W5 equals each X8's W2. The number of each X9's W7 equals 5 more than each X9's W5. The number of each X8's W7 equals 2 times each X9's WWW. The number of each X9's W5 equals 21. How many WWW does each X8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["X9's W5 as u. So u = 21.\nDefine each X9's W7 as S. So S = 5 * u = 5 * 21 = 13.\nDefine each X9's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 13 + 21 = 11.\nDefine each X8's W7 as i. So i = 2 * A = 2 * 11 = 22.\nDefine each X8's W2 as Y. So Y = u = 21.\nDefine each X8's W5 as F. So F = Y = 21.\nDefine each X8's WWW as r. So r = Y + F + i = 21 + 21 + 22 = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 620, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y3 equals each Y3's X0. The number of each Y3's X0 equals 19. How many XXX does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Y3's X0 = 19. Z0's Y3 = i = 19.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as Y. So Y = X0 = 19.\nDefine each Z0's XXX as F. So F = Z0's XXX as r. So r = Z0's XXX as l. So l = Z0's XXX as V. So V = Z0's XXX as q. So q = Z0's XXX as q. So q = V = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 621, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y2 equals 10 more than the difference of each Z3's Y9 and each Z0's Y9. The number of each Z3's Y9 equals 7. The number of each Z0's Y9 equals 14. How many YYY does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["Z3's Y9 as u. So u = 7.\nDefine each Z0's Y9 as S. So S = 14.\nDefine each Z0's Y2 as A. So A = 10 * u - S = 10 * 7 - 14 = 11.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as i. So i = S + A + A = 14 + 11 + 11 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 622, "question": "The number of each Y1's X7 equals 14 times each X7's W6. The number of each X7's W6 equals 0 times each Y8's X9. The number of each Y6's X7 equals 2 times each Y1's WWW. The number of each Y8's X9 equals 21. The number of each Z9's Y1 equals the sum of each Y6's X7 and each X7's W6. The number of each Z9's Y6 equals 10 times each Z9's Y1. How many WWW does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y8's X9 as u. So u = 21.\nDefine each X7's W6 as S. So S = 0 * u = 0 * 21 = 0.\nDefine each X7's WWW as A. So A = S = 0.\nDefine each Y1's X7 as i. So i = 14 * S = 14 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as Y. So Y = i * A = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y6's X7 as F. So F = 2 * Y = 2 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z9's Y1 as r. So r = F + S = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z9's Y6 as l. So l = 10 * r = 10 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as V. So V = F * A = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z9's WWW as q. So q = l * V + r * Y = 0 * 0 + 0 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 623, "question": "The number of each Y0's X5 equals 11 more than the difference of each X5's W3 and each Y0's X6. The number of each X5's W3 equals the sum of each Y0's X6, each Y5's X4 and each X6's W3. The number of each Y1's X4 equals each Y0's WWW. The number of each Y0's X6 equals 20 more than the sum of each Y5's X4 and each X6's W3. The number of each Y5's X4 equals 3. The number of each X5's W6 equals 6. The number of each X6's W3 equals each Y5's X4. How many X4 does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["Y5's X4 = 3. X6's W3 = Y5's X4 = 3.\nDefine each Y0's X6 as u. So u = 20 * Y5's X4 + u = 20 * 3 + 20 = 11.\nDefine each X5's W6 as S. So S = 6.\nDefine each X5's W3 as A. So A = (u + Y5's X4 + u) = (11 + 3 + 11) = 2.\nDefine each X6's WWW as i. So i = u = 11.\nDefine each Y0's X5 as Y. So Y = 11 * A - u = 11 * 2 - 11 = 11.\nDefine each X5's WWW as F. So F = S + A = 6 + 2 = 8.\nDefine each Y0's WWW as r. So r = Y * F + u * i = 11 * 8 + 11 * 11 = 18.\nDefine each Y1's X4 as l. So l = r = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 624, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y9 equals 12. The number of each Z4's Y1 equals 7 more than each Z8's Y9. How many Y1 does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Z8's Y9 = 12. Z4's Y1 = 7 * Z8's Y9 = 7 * 12 = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 625, "question": "The number of each Y3's X9 equals 22 more than the sum of each Z5's Y3 and each Y9's X6. The number of each Y3's X6 equals 11 more than each Y3's X9. The number of each Y4's X3 equals each Y3's X6. The number of each Y9's X6 equals 13. The number of each Z5's Y3 equals 22 more than each Y9's X6. How many X3 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["Y9's X6 as u. So u = 13.\nDefine each Z5's Y3 as S. So S = 22 * u = 22 * 13 = 10.\nDefine each Y3's X9 as A. So A = 22 * S + u = 22 * 10 + 13 = 1.\nDefine each Y3's X6 as i. So i = 11 + A = 11 + 1 = 12.\nDefine each Y4's X3 as Y. So Y = i = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 626, "question": "The number of each Y6's X6 equals 3 times the sum of each Y0's WWW, each Y0's X6 and each Z5's WWW. The number of each Y0's X6 equals 4. The number of each Z1's Y9 equals 1 more than the sum of each Y6's X6, each X6's W7 and each Y3's WWW. The number of each Y3's X6 equals 14 more than the sum of each Y0's X6, each Y6's X6 and each X6's W7. The number of each Z5's Y0 equals each Y0's X6. The number of each X6's W7 equals 14 more than the sum of each Z5's Y0 and each Y0's X6. How many Y9 does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Y0's X6 as u. So u = 4.\nDefine each Z5's Y0 as S. So S = u = 4.\nDefine each X6's W7 as A. So A = 14 * S + u = 14 * 4 + 4 = 14.\nDefine each X6's WWW as i. So i = A = 14.\nDefine each Y0's WWW as Y. So Y = u * i = 4 * 14 = 10.\nDefine each Z5's WWW as F. So F = S * Y = 4 * 10 = 17.\nDefine each Y6's X6 as r. So r = 3 * (Y + u + F) = 3 * (10 + 4 + 17) = 19.\nDefine each Y3's X6 as l. So l = 14 + (u + r + A) = 14 + (4 + 19 + 14) = 5.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as V. So V = l * i = 5 * 14 = 1.\nDefine each Z1's Y9 as q. So q = 1 * (r + A + V) = 1 * (19 + 14 + 1) = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 627, "question": "The number of each X0's W8 equals 2. The number of each Y7's X5 equals 3 more than the sum of each X0's W8 and each X0's WWW. How many X5 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["X0's W8 as u. So u = 2.\nDefine each X0's WWW as S. So S = u = 2.\nDefine each Y7's X5 as A. So A = 3 * u + S = 3 * 2 + 2 = 8.\nThus, the answer is 8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 628, "question": "The number of each X8's W3 equals 17 more than each Y9's X5. The number of each Y3's X7 equals each X7's WWW. The number of each Z5's Y9 equals the difference of each Y9's X5 and each X8's W3. The number of each Y7's X7 equals each Z5's Y9. The number of each X7's W3 equals the sum of each Y9's X5 and each Y7's X7. The number of each X1's W2 equals the sum of each X7's W3 and each Y3's WWW. The number of each Y9's X5 equals 15. How many W2 does each X1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Y9's X5 as u. So u = 15.\nDefine each X8's W3 as S. So S = 17 * u = 17 * 15 = 2.\nDefine each Z5's Y9 as A. So A = u - S = 15 - 2 = 13.\nDefine each Y7's X7 as i. So i = A = 13.\nDefine each X7's W3 as Y. So Y = u + i = 15 + 13 = 5.\nDefine each X7's WWW as F. So F = Y = 5.\nDefine each Y3's X7 as r. So r = F = 5.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as l. So l = r * F = 5 * 5 = 2.\nDefine each X1's W2 as V. So V = Y + l = 5 + 2 = 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 629, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y6 equals 19 times each Y6's X9. The number of each Y3's X5 equals 3 more than each X5's W4. The number of each Y6's X9 equals 15 more than the difference of each Y3's X5 and each Z1's Y7. The number of each X5's W4 equals 2. The number of each Z4's Y5 equals 7 more than the difference of each Y3's X5 and each X5's W4. The number of each X9's W8 equals 9 more than each Z1's Y7. The number of each Z1's Y7 equals each Z4's YYY. How many WWW does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["X5's W4 = 2.\nDefine each Y3's X5 as u. So u = 3 * X5 = 3 * 2 = 6.\nDefine each Z4's Y5 as S. So S = 7 * u - X5 = 7 * 6 - 2 = 19.\nDefine each Z4's YYY as A. So A = S = 19.\nDefine each Z1's Y7 as i. So i = A = 19.\nDefine each X9's W8 as Y. So Y = 9 * i = 9 * 19 = 10.\nDefine each X9's WWW as F. So F = Y = 10.\nDefine each Y6's X9 as r. So r = 15 * u - i = 15 * 6 - 19 = 15.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as l. So l = r * F = 15 * 10 = 12.\nDefine each Z7's Y6 as V. So V = 19 * r = 19 * 15 = 9.\nDefine each Z7's WWW as q. So q = V * l = 9 * 12 = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 630, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y9 equals 9. How many Y9 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["Z5's Y9 = 9. So 9 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 631, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y5 equals 22. The number of each Z9's Y5 equals the difference of each Y5's X5 and each Y5's XXX. The number of each Y5's X5 equals 14 more than each Z8's Y5. How many XXX does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Z8's Y5 = 22. Y5's X5 as u. So u = 14 * Z8's Y5 = 14 * 22 = 9.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as S. So S = u = 9.\nDefine each Z9's Y5 as A. So A = u - S = 9 - 9 = 0.\nDefine each Z9's XXX as i. So i = A * S = 0 * 9 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 632, "question": "The number of each X6's W5 equals 12 more than each X4's W2. The number of each X0's W2 equals 2 more than the sum of each Z0's YYY, each X4's W2 and each Z9's Y5. The number of each Z4's Y8 equals 2 times each Y2's X4. The number of each Y8's X0 equals 1 more than each X6's W5. The number of each X4's W2 equals 19. The number of each Z9's Y5 equals each Z0's YYY. The number of each Y2's X4 equals 5 more than the difference of each X4's W2 and each Z0's WWW. The number of each Z0's Y8 equals 8 times each X6's W5. How many WWW does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["X4's W2 as u. So u = 19.\nDefine each X6's W5 as S. So S = 12 * u = 12 * 19 = 21.\nDefine each Z0's Y8 as A. So A = 8 * S = 8 * 21 = 7.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as i. So i = A = 7.\nDefine each Z9's Y5 as Y. So Y = i = 7.\nDefine each X0's W2 as F. So F = 2 * (i + u + Y) = 2 * (7 + 19 + 7) = 19.\nDefine each X0's WWW as r. So r = F = 19.\nDefine each Y8's X0 as l. So l = 1 * S = 1 * 21 = 21.\nDefine each Y8's WWW as V. So V = l * r = 21 * 19 = 8.\nDefine each Z0's WWW as q. So q = A * V = 7 * 8 = 10.\nDefine each Y2's X4 as z. So z = 5 * u - q = 5 * 19 - 10 = 11.\nDefine each Z4's Y8 as A. So A = 2 * S = 2 * 21 = 19.\nDefine each Z4's WWW as i. So i = A * V = 19 * 8 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 633, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y3 equals each Y8's X0. The number of each Y7's X3 equals the sum of each Z0's YYY and each Z0's Y7. The number of each Y3's X3 equals 8 times each Z9's Y8. The number of each Y8's X0 equals 3 times each Y5's X0. The number of each Z0's Y7 equals 13 times each Z0's Y3. The number of each Z9's Y8 equals each Z0's Y7. The number of each Z0's Y3 equals 1. The number of each Y7's X9 equals 4 times each Y7's X3. The number of each Y5's X0 equals each Y7's X9. How many XXX does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["Z0's Y3 as u. So u = 1.\nDefine each Z0's Y7 as S. So S = 13 * u = 13 * 1 = 13.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 13 + 1 = 14.\nDefine each Y7's X3 as i. So i = A + S = 14 + 13 = 4.\nDefine each Y7's X9 as Y. So Y = 4 * i = 4 * 4 = 16.\nDefine each Y5's X0 as F. So F = Y = 16.\nDefine each Y8's X0 as r. So r = 3 * F = 3 * 16 = 2.\nDefine each Z9's Y3 as l. So l = r = 2.\nDefine each Z9's Y8 as V. So V = S = 13.\nDefine each Y3's X3 as q. So q = 8 * V = 8 * 13 = 12.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as z. So z = q = 12.\nDefine each Z9's XXX as A. So A = V * V + l * z = 13 * 13 + 2 * 12 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 634, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y7 equals 17. How many YYY does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["Z9's Y7 = 17. Z9's YYY = Z9's YYY = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 635, "question": "The number of each Y8's X8 equals 6. The number of each X7's W2 equals each Y8's X8. How many W2 does each X7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Y8's X8 = 6. X7's W2 = Y8's X8 = 6.\nDefine each X7's WWW as u. So u = X7 = 6.\nDefine each Y8's WWW as S. So S = Y8's X8 * u = 6 * 6 = 13.\nDefine each X3's WWW as A. So A = X3 = 3.\nDefine each Y8's WWW as i. So i = S = 13.\nDefine each X3's WWW as Y. So Y = A = 3.\nDefine each Y8's WWW as F. So F = S + i = 13 + 13 = 3.\nDefine each X8's WWW as r. So r = X8's WWW = 18.\nDefine each Y8's X8 as l. So l = 6.\nDefine each X7's W2 as V. So V = l = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 636, "question": "The number of each Y3's X9 equals 4. The number of each Y3's X5 equals 16 times the difference of each Y3's X2 and each Y3's X9. The number of each Y3's X2 equals 15 more than each Y3's X9. How many XXX does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Y3's X9 as u. So u = 4.\nDefine each Y3's X2 as S. So S = 15 * u = 15 * 4 = 14.\nDefine each Y3's X5 as A. So A = 16 * S - u = 16 * 14 - 4 = 12.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as i. So i = S + A + u = 14 + 12 + 4 = 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 637, "question": "The number of each X5's W2 equals 12 times each X6's W9. The number of each X0's W2 equals each X6's WWW. The number of each X0's W0 equals the sum of each X0's W9 and each X5's W2. The number of each X0's W9 equals 4. The number of each X6's W9 equals 17 more than the sum of each X0's W9 and each X5's W9. The number of each X6's W0 equals the sum of each X0's W0, each X5's W2 and each X0's W9. The number of each X5's W9 equals 10 times each X0's W9. How many W2 does each X0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["X0's W9 as u. So u = 4.\nDefine each X5's W9 as S. So S = 10 * u = 10 * 4 = 17.\nDefine each X6's W9 as A. So A = 17 * u + S = 17 * 4 + 17 = 16.\nDefine each X5's W2 as i. So i = 12 * A = 12 * 16 = 8.\nDefine each X0's W0 as Y. So Y = u + i = 4 + 8 = 12.\nDefine each X6's W0 as F. So F = (Y + i + u) = (12 + 8 + 4) = 1.\nDefine each X6's WWW as r. So r = A + F = 16 + 1 = 17.\nDefine each X0's W2 as l. So l = r = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 638, "question": "The number of each X8's W3 equals 1 times the sum of each Z8's YYY and each Z8's Y2. The number of each X8's W0 equals 17 more than each X8's W3. The number of each Z8's Y2 equals 0. How many WWW does each X8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["Z8's Y2 as u. So u = 0.\nDefine each Z8's YYY as S. So S = u = 0.\nDefine each X8's W3 as A. So A = 1 * S + u = 1 * 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each X8's W0 as i. So i = 17 + A = 17 + 0 = 17.\nDefine each X8's WWW as Y. So Y = A + i = 0 + 17 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 639, "question": "The number of each Y8's X5 equals 8. How many X5 does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["Y8's X5 = 8.\nThus, the answer is 8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 640, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y6 equals 16. The number of each Z9's Y7 equals 5 more than each Z5's Y6. How many Y7 does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["Z5's Y6 = 16. Z9's Y7 = 5 * Z5's Y6 = 5 * 16 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 641, "question": "The number of each Y8's X4 equals 21 times each Y3's X7. The number of each Y3's X7 equals 16. How many X4 does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Y3's X7 = 16. Y8's X4 = 21 * Y3's X7 = 21 * 16 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 642, "question": "The number of each X3's W4 equals 22. The number of each Y0's X3 equals the difference of each Y4's X3 and each Y4's XXX. The number of each Y4's X3 equals 17. The number of each Z1's Y0 equals the difference of each Y4's X3 and each X3's W4. How many WWW does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y4's X3 as u. So u = 17.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as S. So S = u = 17.\nDefine each Y0's X3 as A. So A = u - S = 17 - 17 = 0.\nDefine each X3's W4 as i. So i = 22.\nDefine each X3's WWW as Y. So Y = i = 22.\nDefine each Y0's WWW as F. So F = A * Y = 0 * 22 = 0.\nDefine each Z1's Y0 as r. So r = u - i = 17 - 22 = 18.\nDefine each Z1's WWW as l. So l = r * F = 18 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 643, "question": "The number of each Z4's Y5 equals 19 times the sum of each Z0's Y4 and each Z9's Y4. The number of each Z9's Y4 equals 0. The number of each Z0's Y4 equals 15 more than each Z9's Y4. The number of each Z9's Y7 equals 7 more than the sum of each Z9's Y4, each Z0's Y4 and each Z4's Y5. How many Y7 does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["Z9's Y4 as u. So u = 0.\nDefine each Z0's Y4 as S. So S = 15 * u = 15 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z4's Y5 as A. So A = 19 * S + u = 19 * 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z9's Y7 as i. So i = 7 * (u + S + A) = 7 * (0 + 0 + 0) = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 644, "question": "The number of each Z2's Y4 equals 8. How many Y4 does each Z2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["Z2's Y4 as u. So u = 8.\nThus, the answer is 8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 645, "question": "The number of each Y1's X7 equals 15 more than each Y1's X9. The number of each Y1's X9 equals 3. The number of each Y1's X6 equals 15 times each Z6's Y1. The number of each Z6's Y1 equals 4. How many XXX does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Z6's Y1 as u. So u = 4.\nDefine each Y1's X6 as S. So S = 15 * u = 15 * 4 = 14.\nDefine each Y1's X9 as A. So A = 3.\nDefine each Y1's X7 as i. So i = 15 * A = 15 * 3 = 22.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as Y. So Y = S + i + A = 14 + 22 + 3 = 16.\nDefine each Z6's XXX as F. So F = u * Y = 4 * 16 = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 646, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y0 equals 9. The number of each Z4's Y0 equals each Z7's Y9. The number of each Z7's Y9 equals 10 times each Z7's Y0. How many Y0 does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["Z7's Y0 as u. So u = 9.\nDefine each Z7's Y9 as S. So S = 10 * u = 10 * 9 = 21.\nDefine each Z4's Y0 as A. So A = S = 21.\nThus, the answer is 21."], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 647, "question": "The number of each X4's W4 equals each X1's W8. The number of each X1's W6 equals 19 times each X4's W4. The number of each X6's W4 equals each X1's W6. The number of each X1's W8 equals 3. How many W4 does each X6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["X1's W8 as u. So u = 3.\nDefine each X4's W4 as S. So S = u = 3.\nDefine each X1's W6 as A. So A = 19 * S = 19 * 3 = 11.\nDefine each X6's W4 as i. So i = A = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 648, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y5 equals 2 times each Z3's Y3. The number of each Y1's X8 equals 14. The number of each Z9's Y1 equals 14 times each Z3's XXX. The number of each Z3's Y3 equals 1 times each Z8's XXX. The number of each Y3's X7 equals 20 more than each Y3's X8. The number of each Z8's Y3 equals 22 times each Y3's X8. The number of each Y5's X8 equals 13 more than each Y3's X7. The number of each Z3's Y1 equals 11. The number of each Y3's X8 equals 11. How many Y1 does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["Y3's X8 as u. So u = 11.\nDefine each Y3's X7 as S. So S = 20 * u = 20 * 11 = 13.\nDefine each Y5's X8 as A. So A = 13 * S = 13 * 13 = 8.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as i. So i = A = 8.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as Y. So Y = S + u = 13 + 11 = 1.\nDefine each Z8's Y3 as F. So F = 22 * u = 22 * 11 = 12.\nDefine each Z8's XXX as r. So r = F * Y = 12 * 1 = 12.\nDefine each Z3's Y3 as l. So l = 1 * r = 1 * 12 = 12.\nDefine each Z3's Y5 as V. So V = 2 * l = 2 * 12 = 1.\nDefine each Z3's Y1 as q. So q = 11.\nDefine each Z3's XXX as z. So z = q * i + l * Y = 11 * 8 + 12 * 1 = 1.\nDefine each Z9's Y1 as A. So A = 14 * Z3's XXX = 14 * 1 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 649, "question": "The number of each X0's W3 equals 1. The number of each X0's W5 equals 14 more than each Y9's WWW. The number of each Y9's X5 equals 16 more than each X0's W3. The number of each X5's W3 equals each X0's W3. The number of each Y1's X2 equals the difference of each X5's WWW and each X2's WWW. The number of each Y4's X2 equals 21 more than each X0's W5. The number of each X8's W7 equals each Y4's WWW. The number of each X2's W5 equals 17. The number of each Y1's X8 equals the sum of each X0's W5, each X8's W7 and each Y4's WWW. How many WWW does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["X0's W3 = 1. X5's W3 = X0's W3 = 1.\nDefine each X5's WWW as u. So u = X0's W3 = 1.\nDefine each Y9's X5 as S. So S = 16 * X0's W3 = 16 * 1 = 16.\nDefine each Y9's WWW as A. So A = S * u = 16 * 1 = 16.\nDefine each X0's W5 as i. So i = 14 * A = 14 * 16 = 17.\nDefine each Y4's X2 as Y. So Y = 21 * i = 21 * 17 = 12.\nDefine each X2's W5 as F. So F = 17.\nDefine each X2's WWW as r. So r = F = 17.\nDefine each Y4's WWW as l. So l = Y * r = 12 * 17 = 20.\nDefine each X8's W7 as V. So V = l = 20.\nDefine each Y1's X8 as q. So q = (i + V + l) = (17 + 20 + 20) = 11.\nDefine each Y1's X2 as z. So z = u - r = 1 - 17 = 7.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as A. So A = q * A + z * r = 11 * 16 + 7 * 17 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 650, "question": "The number of each Y2's X1 equals 6 more than each Z1's Y4. The number of each X1's W6 equals the sum of each Y8's XXX and each X1's W4. The number of each Y8's X2 equals 15 more than each Y2's XXX. The number of each Y2's X2 equals 17 times each Y2's X0. The number of each X0's W4 equals 21. The number of each Y4's X1 equals 11 times each X1's WWW. The number of each Y2's X0 equals 13 more than each Y2's X1. The number of each X1's W4 equals 18 times each Y2's X0. The number of each Z1's Y4 equals each X0's W4. How many X1 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["X0's W4 = 21. Z1's Y4 = X0's W4 = 21.\nDefine each Y2's X1 as u. So u = 6 * Z1's Y4 = 6 * 21 = 11.\nDefine each Y2's X0 as S. So S = 13 * u = 13 * 11 = 5.\nDefine each Y2's X2 as A. So A = 17 * S = 17 * 5 = 16.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as i. So i = S + A + u = 5 + 16 + 11 = 9.\nDefine each Y8's X2 as Y. So Y = 15 * i = 15 * 9 = 20.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as F. So F = Y = 20.\nDefine each X1's W4 as r. So r = 18 * S = 18 * 5 = 21.\nDefine each X1's W6 as l. So l = F + r = 20 + 21 = 18.\nDefine each X1's WWW as V. So V = l + r = 18 + 21 = 16.\nDefine each Y4's X1 as q. So q = 11 * V = 11 * 16 = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 651, "question": "The number of each Y5's X8 equals the sum of each Y9's X1 and each Y2's X8. The number of each Y2's X8 equals the sum of each Y9's XXX and each X8's W2. The number of each Y9's X8 equals the difference of each Y9's X0 and each X1's W2. The number of each X8's W1 equals the difference of each X1's W3 and each X1's W0. The number of each Y9's X0 equals the sum of each X8's W3, each X1's W2 and each X0's W0. The number of each X8's W2 equals 0 times each X8's W1. The number of each Y2's X0 equals 20 more than each X0's WWW. The number of each X1's W3 equals 19. The number of each X0's W0 equals 14 times each Y5's X6. The number of each Y9's X1 equals the difference of each Y2's X0 and each X1's W2. The number of each X8's W3 equals each X8's W2. The number of each X1's W2 equals 3 times the sum of each Y2's X0 and each X1's W3. The number of each X1's W0 equals each X1's W3. The number of each Y5's X6 equals 8 more than each X8's W3. How many X8 does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["X8's W1 as u. So u = 13 - 10 = 3.\nDefine each X8's W2 as S. So S = 0 * u = 0 * 3 = 0.\nDefine each X8's W3 as A. So A = S = 0.\nDefine each Y5's X6 as i. So i = 8 * A = 8 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X0's W0 as Y. So Y = 14 * i = 14 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X1's W3 as F. So F = 19.\nDefine each X1's W0 as r. So r = F = 19.\nDefine each X0's WWW as l. So l = Y = 0.\nDefine each Y2's X0 as V. So V = 20 * l = 20 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X1's W2 as q. So q = 3 * V + F = 3 * 0 + 19 = 19.\nDefine each Y9's X0 as z. So z = (A + q + Y) = (0 + 19 + 0) = 19.\nDefine each Y9's X8 as A. So A = S - q = 0 - 19 = 4.\nDefine each Y9's X1 as i. So i = V - q = 0 - 19 = 4.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as Y. So Y = i + A + Z = 4 + 4 + 19 = 4.\nDefine each Y2's X8 as F. So F = Y + S = 4 + 0 = 4.\nDefine each Y5's X8 as r. So r = i + F = 4 + 4 = 8.\nThus, the answer is 8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 652, "question": "The number of each X8's W2 equals 1. The number of each Y6's X8 equals each X8's WWW. How many WWW does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["X8's W2 = 1. X8's WWW = 1. X8's WWW = 1. X8's WWW = 1. X8's WWW = 1. X8's WWW = 1. X8's WWW = 1. X8's WWW = 1. X8's WWW = 1. X8's WWW = 1. X8's WWW = 1. X8's WWW = 1. X8's WWW = 1. X8's WWW = 1. X8's WWW = 1. X8's WWW = 1. X8's WWW = 1. X8's WWW = 1. X8's W2 as u. So u = 1. X8's W2 as S. So S = 1. X8's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 1 + 1 = 2.\nDefine each Y6's X8 as i. So i = A = 2.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as Y. So Y = i * A = 2 * 2 = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 653, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y7 equals the sum of each Y7's X0 and each Y7's X4. The number of each Y7's X0 equals each Y7's X4. The number of each Y7's X4 equals 0. How many XXX does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y7's X4 as u. So u = 0.\nDefine each Y7's X0 as S. So S = u = 0.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z9's Y7 as i. So i = S + u = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z9's XXX as Y. So Y = i * A = 0 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 654, "question": "The number of each Y8's X7 equals 19. The number of each Y2's X6 equals 20 more than the difference of each Y8's XXX and each Y8's X7. How many X6 does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Y8's X7 = 19. Y8's XXX as u. So u = Y8's XXX = 19.\nDefine each Y2's X6 as S. So S = 20 * u - Y8's X7 = 20 * 19 - 19 = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 655, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y0 equals 5. The number of each Z7's Y4 equals each Z7's Y0. How many Y4 does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Z7's Y0 = 5.\nDefine each Z7's Y4 as u. So u = Z7's Y0 = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 656, "question": "The number of each Y9's X6 equals 12 times the sum of each Z0's Y9, each Y3's X6 and each Z0's YYY. The number of each Z7's Y0 equals 8 times the sum of each Y9's X6, each Y3's X6 and each Z0's Y9. The number of each Z0's Y9 equals 0 times each Y3's X6. The number of each Y3's X6 equals 15. How many Y0 does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Y3's X6 = 15. Z0's Y9 = 0 * Y3 = 0 * 15 = 0.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as u. So u = u = 0.\nDefine each Y9's X6 as S. So S = 12 * (S + Y3's X6 + u) = 12 * (12 + 15 + 0) = 19.\nDefine each Z7's Y0 as A. So A = 8 + (S + Y3's X6 + u) = 8 + (19 + 15 + 0) = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 657, "question": "The number of each Y4's X8 equals 14. The number of each Y2's X8 equals 22 times each Y4's XXX. The number of each Y4's X0 equals 3. The number of each Y2's X4 equals 5 more than each Y4's XXX. The number of each Y2's X0 equals 11 more than each Y4's X0. The number of each Y4's X4 equals 22. How many XXX does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Y4's X4 as u. So u = 22.\nDefine each Y4's X0 as S. So S = 3.\nDefine each Y4's X8 as A. So A = 14.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as i. So i = S + A + u = 3 + 14 + 22 = 16.\nDefine each Y2's X8 as Y. So Y = 22 * i = 22 * 16 = 7.\nDefine each Y2's X4 as F. So F = 5 * i = 5 * 16 = 11.\nDefine each Y2's X0 as r. So r = 11 * S = 11 * 3 = 10.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as l. So l = r + Y + F = 10 + 7 + 11 = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 658, "question": "The number of each Y4's X0 equals 7. The number of each Z0's Y4 equals 16 times each Y4's X0. The number of each Z0's Y1 equals 7 times the difference of each Y4's X0 and each Z0's Y4. How many YYY does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["Y4's X0 as u. So u = 7.\nDefine each Z0's Y4 as S. So S = 16 * u = 16 * 7 = 20.\nDefine each Z0's Y1 as A. So A = 7 * u - S = 7 * 7 - 20 = 19.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as i. So i = S + A = 20 + 19 = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 659, "question": "The number of each Y9's X9 equals 14. How many X9 does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Y9's X9 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 660, "question": "The number of each Z4's Y4 equals 7 more than each Z4's Y2. The number of each Z4's Y2 equals 22. The number of each Z2's Y4 equals 12 more than each Z4's Y4. The number of each Z2's Y2 equals 22 times each Z2's Y4. How many Y2 does each Z2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Z4's Y2 as u. So u = 22.\nDefine each Z4's Y4 as S. So S = 7 * u = 7 * 22 = 16.\nDefine each Z2's Y4 as A. So A = 12 * S = 12 * 16 = 8.\nDefine each Z2's Y2 as i. So i = 22 * A = 22 * 8 = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 661, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y6 equals 0 more than each Z9's Y7. The number of each Y6's X6 equals 1 times each Z9's Y6. The number of each Y6's X8 equals 0 times the sum of each Z9's Y6 and each Y6's X6. The number of each Z9's Y7 equals 1. How many XXX does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Z9's Y7 as u. So u = 1.\nDefine each Z9's Y6 as S. So S = 0 * u = 0 * 1 = 0.\nDefine each Y6's X6 as A. So A = 1 * S = 1 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y6's X8 as i. So i = 0 * S + A = 0 * 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as Y. So Y = A + i = 0 + 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 662, "question": "The number of each X9's W1 equals 10 more than each Z0's Y4. The number of each Z3's Y5 equals 22 more than each Z7's XXX. The number of each Z6's Y5 equals 22 more than each X9's W1. The number of each Y4's X8 equals 22 more than each Z6's Y5. The number of each Z7's Y4 equals 14 more than each Y4's X8. The number of each X8's W6 equals 20. The number of each Z0's Y4 equals each X8's W6. How many Y5 does each Z3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["X8's W6 = 20. Z0's Y4 = X8's W6 = 20.\nDefine each X9's W1 as u. So u = 10 * Z0's Y4 = 10 * 20 = 16.\nDefine each Z6's Y5 as S. So S = 22 * u = 22 * 16 = 7.\nDefine each Y4's X8 as A. So A = 22 * S = 22 * 7 = 16.\nDefine each Z7's Y4 as i. So i = 14 * A = 14 * 16 = 17.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as Y. So Y = A = 16.\nDefine each Z7's XXX as F. So F = i * Y = 17 * 16 = 19.\nDefine each Z3's Y5 as r. So r = 22 * F = 22 * 19 = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 663, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y9 equals each Z2's Y0. The number of each Z2's Y4 equals 19 times each Y0's X2. The number of each Y4's X2 equals each Z5's XXX. The number of each Z5's Y9 equals each Z0's Y9. The number of each Y9's X4 equals 19 times each Z5's YYY. The number of each Z2's Y0 equals 3 times each Y0's X4. The number of each Y0's X4 equals 9 more than each Y0's X6. The number of each Y0's X2 equals the sum of each Y9's XXX and each Y4's X2. The number of each Y0's X6 equals 5. How many Y4 does each Z2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["Y0's X6 = 5. Y0's X6 = 5. Y0's X4 = 9 * Y0's X6 = 9 * 5 = 22.\nDefine each Z2's Y0 as u. So u = 3 * Y0's X4 = 3 * 22 = 20.\nDefine each Z0's Y9 as S. So S = u = 20.\nDefine each Z5's Y9 as A. So A = S = 20.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as i. So i = A = 20.\nDefine each Y9's X4 as Y. So Y = 19 * i = 19 * 20 = 12.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as F. So F = Y = 12.\nDefine each Z5's XXX as r. So r = A * F = 20 * 12 = 10.\nDefine each Y4's X2 as l. So l = r = 10.\nDefine each Y0's X2 as V. So V = F + l = 12 + 10 = 22.\nDefine each Z2's Y4 as q. So q = 19 * V = 19 * 22 = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 664, "question": "The number of each Y5's X3 equals 3 more than each Y6's X0. The number of each Y6's X0 equals 22. The number of each Y6's X3 equals each Y5's X3. How many X3 does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Y6's X0 = 22. Y5's X3 = 3 * Y6's X0 = 3 * 22 = 20.\nDefine each Y6's X3 as u. So u = Y5's X3 = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 665, "question": "The number of each Y6's X4 equals 8 times each Y6's X3. The number of each Y7's X4 equals 10 times each Z8's Y6. The number of each Z8's Y6 equals 17 times each Z8's Y7. The number of each Y6's X3 equals 14. The number of each Z8's Y7 equals 22. The number of each Y7's X3 equals 12 times each Y6's XXX. How many XXX does each Z8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["Z8's Y7 as u. So u = 22.\nDefine each Z8's Y6 as S. So S = 17 * u = 17 * 22 = 6.\nDefine each Y6's X3 as A. So A = 14.\nDefine each Y6's X4 as i. So i = 8 * A = 8 * 14 = 20.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as Y. So Y = A + i = 14 + 20 = 11.\nDefine each Y7's X3 as F. So F = 12 * Y = 12 * 11 = 17.\nDefine each Y7's X4 as r. So r = 10 * S = 10 * 6 = 14.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as l. So l = r + F = 14 + 17 = 8.\nDefine each Z8's XXX as V. So V = S * Y + u * l = 6 * 11 + 22 * 8 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 666, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y5 equals 18 times each Y7's XXX. The number of each Y5's X5 equals 5. The number of each Y7's X5 equals each Y5's X5. How many Y5 does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["Y5's X5 as u. So u = 5.\nDefine each Y7's X5 as S. So S = u = 5.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as A. So A = S = 5.\nDefine each Z9's Y5 as i. So i = 18 * A = 18 * 5 = 21.\nThus, the answer is 21."], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 667, "question": "The number of each Y0's X9 equals 7 more than the difference of each Y1's X1 and each Y1's XXX. The number of each X1's W6 equals the sum of each X9's WWW, each X9's W6, each Y1's X1 and each Y0's WWW. The number of each Y1's X1 equals 22. The number of each X9's W6 equals 7 times the difference of each Y0's XXX and each Y1's XXX. The number of each X2's W8 equals the sum of each Y1's WWW, each Y0's XXX, each X1's WWW and each Y0's WWW. How many WWW does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["X2's W8 as u. So u = (Y1's WWW + each Y0's X9 + each Y1's X1) = 21.\nDefine each Y1's X1 as S. So S = 22.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as A. So A = S = 22.\nDefine each Y0's X9 as i. So i = 7 * S - A = 7 * 22 - 22 = 17.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as Y. So Y = i = 17.\nDefine each X9's W6 as F. So F = 7 * Y - A = 7 * 17 - 22 = 19.\nDefine each X9's WWW as r. So r = F = 19.\nDefine each Y0's WWW as l. So l = i * r = 17 * 19 = 1.\nDefine each X1's W6 as V. So V = (r + F + S + l) = (19 + 19 + 22 + 1) = 15.\nDefine each X1's WWW as q. So q = V = 15.\nDefine each X2's W8 as z. So z = (Y + Y + q + l) = (17 + 17 + 15 + 1) = 4.\nDefine each X2's WWW as A. So A = Z = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 668, "question": "The number of each X2's W1 equals the sum of each Y4's XXX and each Y5's XXX. The number of each Y5's X6 equals 21. The number of each X6's W7 equals 21 times each Y4's WWW. The number of each Y4's X2 equals 2 times each Y5's XXX. How many WWW does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["Y5's X6 = 21. Y5's XXX = 21. Y4's X2 as u. So u = 2 * Y5 = 2 * 21 = 19.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as S. So S = u = 19.\nDefine each X2's W1 as A. So A = S + Y5 = 19 + 21 = 17.\nDefine each X2's WWW as i. So i = A = 17.\nDefine each Y4's WWW as Y. So Y = u * i = 19 * 17 = 1.\nDefine each X6's W7 as F. So F = 21 * Y = 21 * 1 = 21.\nDefine each X6's WWW as r. So r = F = 21.\nDefine each Y5's WWW as l. So l = Y + r = 1 + 21 = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 669, "question": "The number of each X5's W9 equals 17. The number of each X0's W7 equals 22 more than each X5's WWW. How many W7 does each X0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["X5's W9 = 17. X5's WWW = 17. X0's W7 as u. So u = 22 * X5's W9 = 22 * 17 = 6.\nDefine each X0's WWW as S. So S = u = 6.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as A. So A = Y1's S = 6.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as i. So i = A = 6.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each X5's WWW as Y. So Y = X5's W9 + X5's WWW = 17 + 17 = 11.\nDefine each X0's W7 as F. So F = 22 * Y = 22 * 11 = 12.\nDefine each X0's WWW as r. So r = F + u = 12 + 12 = 1.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as l. So l = i = 6.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 670, "question": "The number of each Y8's X1 equals the sum of each Y9's X8, each Y9's X1 and each Y9's XXX. The number of each Y9's X8 equals 0. The number of each Y8's X8 equals the difference of each Y9's XXX and each Y8's X1. The number of each Y9's X1 equals 9 more than each Y9's X8. How many XXX does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["Y9's X8 as u. So u = 0.\nDefine each Y9's X1 as S. So S = 9 * u = 9 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y8's X1 as i. So i = (u + S + A) = (0 + 0 + 0) = 0.\nDefine each Y8's X8 as Y. So Y = A - i = 0 - 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as F. So F = Y + i = 0 + 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 671, "question": "The number of each Y8's X1 equals 22. The number of each Y6's X9 equals 13 more than each Y1's X9. The number of each Y3's X9 equals 20 more than the sum of each Y8's X1, each Y1's X1 and each Y3's X1. The number of each Y1's X9 equals the difference of each Y3's XXX and each Y3's X1. The number of each Y1's X1 equals each Y8's XXX. The number of each Y3's X1 equals 14 more than the sum of each Y8's XXX, each Y1's X1 and each Y8's X1. How many XXX does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Y8's X1 as u. So u = 22.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as S. So S = u = 22.\nDefine each Y1's X1 as A. So A = S = 22.\nDefine each Y3's X1 as i. So i = 14 * (S + A + u) = 14 * (22 + 22 + 22) = 19.\nDefine each Y3's X9 as Y. So Y = 20 * (u + A + i) = 20 * (22 + 22 + 19) = 19.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as F. So F = Y + i = 19 + 19 = 15.\nDefine each Y1's X9 as r. So r = F - i = 15 - 19 = 19.\nDefine each Y6's X9 as l. So l = 13 + r = 13 + 19 = 9.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as V. So V = l = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 672, "question": "The number of each X8's W7 equals 9 times each Y0's X1. The number of each X1's W7 equals the sum of each X1's W8 and each Y8's X8. The number of each X8's W8 equals 2 times the sum of each Y8's X8 and each Y8's X1. The number of each Y0's X8 equals 0 times each Y8's X8. The number of each Y8's X1 equals 6 times each Y0's X8. The number of each X1's W8 equals 3 times each X8's WWW. The number of each Y8's X8 equals 21. The number of each Y0's X1 equals 11 times each Y8's X1. How many WWW does each X1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Y8's X8 = 21. Y0's X8 = 0 * u = 0 * 21 = 0.\nDefine each Y8's X1 as u. So u = 6 * Y0's X8 = 6 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y0's X1 as S. So S = 11 * u = 11 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X8's W7 as A. So A = 9 * S = 9 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X8's W8 as i. So i = 2 * u + u = 2 * 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each X8's WWW as Y. So Y = A + i = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each X1's W8 as F. So F = 3 * Y = 3 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y8's X8 as r. So r = 21.\nDefine each X1's W7 as l. So l = F + r = 0 + 21 = 21.\nDefine each X1's WWW as V. So V = l + F = 21 + 0 = 21.\nThus, the answer is 21."], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 673, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y1 equals 20 times the sum of each Z2's Y1, each Z7's Y7 and each Z3's Y1. The number of each Z3's Y1 equals 12 times the difference of each Z5's Y7 and each Z2's Y1. The number of each Z7's Y7 equals 19. The number of each Z2's Y1 equals 3 times each Z5's Y7. The number of each Z5's Y7 equals 21 times each Z7's Y7. How many Y1 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["21 * Z7's Y7 = 21 * 19 = 8.\nDefine each Z5's Y7 as u. So u = 21 * S = 21 * 8 = 7.\nDefine each Z2's Y1 as S. So S = 3 * u = 3 * 7 = 21.\nDefine each Z3's Y1 as A. So A = 12 * u - S = 12 * 7 - 21 = 15.\nDefine each Z5's Y1 as i. So i = 20 * (S + u + A) = 20 * (21 + 7 + 15) = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 674, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y5 equals 6. The number of each Z1's Y0 equals 2 more than each Z1's Y5. How many Y0 does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["Z1's Y5 as u. So u = 6.\nDefine each Z1's Y0 as S. So S = 2 * u = 2 * 6 = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 675, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y0 equals 17. How many Y0 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["Z5's Y0 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 676, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y5 equals each Z0's Y1. The number of each X0's W7 equals the difference of each Y0's XXX and each Z0's YYY. The number of each Z0's Y1 equals each Y0's XXX. The number of each Y0's X0 equals 13. How many W7 does each X0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Y0's X0 = 13. Y0's XXX = 13. Y1's X0 = 13. Y1's X0 = 13. Y1's XXX = 13. Z0's Y1 as u. So u = Y0's XXX = 13.\nDefine each Z0's Y5 as S. So S = u = 13.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as A. So A = S + u + u = 13 + 13 + 13 = 16.\nDefine each X0's W7 as i. So i = Y0's XXX - A = 13 - 16 = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 677, "question": "The number of each Y9's X5 equals 19 more than each Y2's XXX. The number of each Y9's X3 equals 2 more than each Z7's Y9. The number of each Y2's X5 equals 21. The number of each Z7's Y9 equals each Y2's X5. The number of each Y4's X6 equals the sum of each Y9's XXX and each Z7's XXX. The number of each Z7's Y2 equals the difference of each Y9's X5 and each Y2's X5. The number of each Z4's Y9 equals 10 more than each Y4's XXX. How many XXX does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["Y2's X5 as u. So u = 21.\nDefine each Z7's Y9 as S. So S = u = 21.\nDefine each Y9's X3 as A. So A = 2 * S = 2 * 21 = 19.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as i. So i = u = 21.\nDefine each Y9's X5 as Y. So Y = 19 * i = 19 * 21 = 8.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as F. So F = Y + A = 8 + 19 = 4.\nDefine each Z7's Y2 as r. So r = Y - u = 8 - 21 = 10.\nDefine each Z7's XXX as l. So l = S * F + r * i = 21 * 4 + 10 * 21 = 19.\nDefine each Y4's X6 as V. So V = F + l = 4 + 19 = 0.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as q. So q = V = 0.\nDefine each Z4's Y9 as z. So z = 10 * q = 10 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z4's XXX as A. So A = z * F = 0 * 4 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 678, "question": "The number of each Y7's X5 equals 13. The number of each Y8's X5 equals the sum of each Y7's X5 and each Y8's X6. The number of each Y8's X6 equals 10 more than each Y7's X5. How many XXX does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["Y7's X5 as u. So u = 13.\nDefine each Y8's X6 as S. So S = 10 * u = 10 * 13 = 15.\nDefine each Y8's X5 as A. So A = u + S = 13 + 15 = 5.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as i. So i = S + A + S = 15 + 5 + 15 = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 679, "question": "The number of each Y8's X4 equals 3 times each Y8's X2. The number of each X2's W3 equals 7. The number of each Y8's X2 equals 2 more than each X2's W3. The number of each Z6's Y8 equals 22 times the sum of each Y8's XXX and each X2's W3. How many Y8 does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["X2's W3 = 7. Y8's X2 as u. So u = 2 * X2's W3 = 2 * 7 = 14.\nDefine each Y8's X4 as S. So S = 3 * u = 3 * 14 = 19.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 19 + 14 = 10.\nDefine each Z6's Y8 as i. So i = 22 * A + X2's W3 = 22 * 10 + 7 = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 680, "question": "The number of each X9's W4 equals 18 more than the difference of each Z5's YYY and each Z3's Y0. The number of each Z3's Y9 equals 19. The number of each Y0's X9 equals the sum of each Z3's YYY, each X9's W4 and each X9's WWW. The number of each Z5's Y9 equals the sum of each Z3's Y0, each Z3's Y9 and each Z3's YYY. The number of each Z3's Y0 equals 18 more than each Z3's Y9. The number of each Y9's X2 equals each Z3's YYY. The number of each Z5's Y0 equals the difference of each Y9's X2 and each Z3's Y9. How many X9 does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["Z3's Y9 as u. So u = 19.\nDefine each Z3's Y0 as S. So S = 18 * u = 18 * 19 = 20.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 20 + 19 = 16.\nDefine each Y9's X2 as i. So i = A = 16.\nDefine each Z5's Y0 as Y. So Y = i - u = 16 - 19 = 20.\nDefine each Z5's Y9 as F. So F = (S + u + A) = (20 + 19 + 16) = 9.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as r. So r = Y + F = 20 + 9 = 6.\nDefine each X9's W4 as l. So l = 18 * r - S = 18 * 6 - 20 = 16.\nDefine each X9's WWW as V. So V = l = 16.\nDefine each Y0's X9 as q. So q = (A + l + V) = (16 + 16 + 16) = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 681, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y2 equals 7. The number of each Z5's Y4 equals 8 more than the difference of each Z3's Y6 and each Z7's XXX. The number of each Y6's X7 equals 1 more than each Z5's XXX. The number of each Z3's Y6 equals 21 more than each Z7's XXX. The number of each Y2's X4 equals 16 times each Z7's Y2. The number of each Y4's X7 equals each Z5's Y4. How many XXX does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Z7's Y2 as u. So u = 7.\nDefine each Y2's X4 as S. So S = 16 * u = 16 * 7 = 20.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as A. So A = S = 20.\nDefine each Z7's XXX as i. So i = u * A = 7 * 20 = 2.\nDefine each Z3's Y6 as Y. So Y = 21 * i = 21 * 2 = 19.\nDefine each Z5's Y4 as F. So F = 8 + Y - i = 8 + 19 - 2 = 2.\nDefine each Y4's X7 as r. So r = F = 2.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as l. So l = r = 2.\nDefine each Z5's XXX as V. So V = F * l = 2 * 2 = 4.\nDefine each Y6's X7 as q. So q = 1 * V = 1 * 4 = 4.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as z. So z = q = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 682, "question": "The number of each X0's W4 equals 6 times each Y6's X0. The number of each Y7's X2 equals 16. The number of each Y6's X0 equals 22 times each Y7's XXX. How many W4 does each X0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Y7's X2 = 16. Y7's XXX = 16. Y6's X0 = 22 * Y7's X2 = 22 * 16 = 7.\nDefine each X0's W4 as u. So u = 6 * Y6's X0 = 6 * 7 = 19.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as S. So S = Y7's X2 = 16.\nDefine each Y6's X0 as A. So A = 22 * S = 22 * 16 = 7.\nDefine each X0's WWW as i. So i = u = 19.\nDefine each Y7's WWW as Y. So Y = Y = 16.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as F. So F = A * i = 7 * 19 = 18.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as r. So r = A * i = 7 * 19 = 18.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y7's X2 as l. So l = 16.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as V. So V = l = 16.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as q. So q = A = 7.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 683, "question": "The number of each X8's W7 equals 21 more than each X9's W4. The number of each X9's W4 equals 0. The number of each X9's W6 equals each X8's W6. The number of each X8's W6 equals 21 more than each X8's W7. How many W6 does each X9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["X9's W4 as u. So u = 0.\nDefine each X8's W7 as S. So S = 21 * u = 21 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X8's W6 as A. So A = 21 * S = 21 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X9's W6 as i. So i = A = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 684, "question": "The number of each Y7's X0 equals 1. The number of each Y8's X9 equals 19 times each Y7's X0. How many X9 does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Y7's X0 = 1. Y8's X9 = 19 * Y7's X0 = 19 * 1 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 685, "question": "The number of each Y7's X3 equals 0. The number of each Y7's X9 equals 15 times each Y7's X3. How many XXX does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y7's X3 as u. So u = 0.\nDefine each Y7's X9 as S. So S = 15 * u = 15 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 0 + 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 686, "question": "The number of each X8's W8 equals 21 more than each X9's W2. The number of each X9's W2 equals 16. The number of each X9's W8 equals each X8's W8. How many W8 does each X9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["X9's W2 as u. So u = 16.\nDefine each X8's W8 as S. So S = 21 * u = 21 * 16 = 14.\nDefine each X9's W8 as A. So A = S = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 687, "question": "The number of each Z4's Y5 equals 7. The number of each Z0's Y5 equals 12 times each Z4's Y5. How many Y5 does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Z4's Y5 = 7. Z0's Y5 = 12 * Z4's Y5 = 12 * 7 = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 688, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y6 equals 20. The number of each Z3's Y2 equals 7 more than each Z6's Y6. The number of each Z6's Y2 equals 13 times each Z3's Y2. How many Y2 does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Z6's Y6 = 20. Z3's Y2 = 7 * Z6's Y6 = 7 * 20 = 2.\nDefine each Z6's Y2 as u. So u = 13 * Z3's Y2 = 13 * 2 = 3.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as S. So S = Z3's Y2 = 2.\nDefine each Z6's Y6 as A. So A = 20.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as i. So i = S = 2.\nDefine each Z6's Y6 as Y. So Y = 20.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as F. So F = S + i = 2 + 2 = 4.\nDefine each Z6's Y6 as r. So r = 20.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as l. So l = S + i = 2 + 2 = 4.\nDefine each Z6's Y2 as V. So V = 13 + Z3's Y2 = 13 + 2 = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 689, "question": "The number of each Y4's X5 equals 14 more than each Y4's X7. The number of each Y3's X7 equals the sum of each Y4's X7 and each Y4's X5. The number of each Y4's X7 equals 3. How many XXX does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Y4's X7 as u. So u = 3.\nDefine each Y4's X5 as S. So S = 14 * u = 14 * 3 = 19.\nDefine each Y3's X7 as A. So A = u + S = 3 + 19 = 22.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as i. So i = A = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 690, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y1 equals 3. How many Y1 does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["Z1's Y1 as u. So u = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 691, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y4 equals 17. The number of each X6's W4 equals 7 times each X6's W6. The number of each Y7's X6 equals 22 times each X6's WWW. The number of each X6's W6 equals 13. The number of each Z7's Y7 equals each Y7's WWW. The number of each Z6's Y7 equals 17 more than each Z7's XXX. How many YYY does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["X6's W6 as u. So u = 13.\nDefine each X6's W4 as S. So S = 7 * u = 7 * 13 = 22.\nDefine each X6's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 22 + 13 = 12.\nDefine each Y7's X6 as i. So i = 22 * A = 22 * 12 = 11.\nDefine each Y7's WWW as Y. So Y = i * A = 11 * 12 = 17.\nDefine each Z7's Y7 as F. So F = Y = 17.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as r. So r = i = 11.\nDefine each Z7's XXX as l. So l = F * r = 17 * 11 = 3.\nDefine each Z6's Y7 as V. So V = 17 * l = 17 * 3 = 5.\nDefine each Z6's Y4 as q. So q = 17.\nDefine each Z6's YYY as z. So z = q + V = 17 + 5 = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 692, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y4 equals 15. How many Y4 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Z5's Y4 = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 693, "question": "The number of each Y2's X0 equals the sum of each X0's W7, each Y7's X0 and each X0's WWW. The number of each Y2's X6 equals 17 times each X6's W4. The number of each X6's W4 equals 3 more than the sum of each X0's W4 and each Y7's XXX. The number of each Y7's X0 equals 13. The number of each X0's W7 equals 14 more than each Y7's XXX. The number of each X0's W4 equals 7 times the sum of each Y7's X0 and each X0's W7. How many WWW does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["Y7's X0 = 13. Y7's XXX = 13. X0's W7 as u. So u = 14 * Y7's XXX = 14 * 13 = 21.\nDefine each X0's W4 as S. So S = 7 * Y7 + u = 7 * 13 + 21 = 19.\nDefine each X0's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 19 + 21 = 17.\nDefine each X6's W4 as i. So i = 3 * S + Y7's XXX = 3 * 19 + 13 = 18.\nDefine each Y2's X6 as Y. So Y = 17 + i = 17 + 18 = 12.\nDefine each Y2's X0 as F. So F = (u + Y + A) = (21 + 12 + 17) = 4.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as r. So r = F * A + Y * i = 4 * 17 + 12 * 18 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 694, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y1 equals 21 times each Y1's X5. The number of each Y1's X5 equals 19. The number of each Z6's Y2 equals 16 times the difference of each Y1's X5 and each Z6's Y1. How many YYY does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y1's X5 as u. So u = 19.\nDefine each Z6's Y1 as S. So S = 21 * u = 21 * 19 = 8.\nDefine each Z6's Y2 as A. So A = 16 * u - S = 16 * 19 - 8 = 19.\nDefine each Z6's YYY as i. So i = S + A = 8 + 19 = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 695, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y6 equals the sum of each Y3's X3 and each Z7's Y9. The number of each Y3's X3 equals 17 more than each Z7's Y9. The number of each Z7's Y3 equals 12. The number of each Z5's Y9 equals the difference of each Z7's Y6 and each X3's W9. The number of each Y6's X6 equals 20 times each Z5's Y9. The number of each X6's W2 equals 16 more than the difference of each Y3's X3 and each Z7's Y6. The number of each X3's W9 equals 0 more than each Z2's XXX. The number of each Z2's Y9 equals each Y9's XXX. The number of each Z7's Y9 equals 22 more than each Z7's Y3. The number of each Y9's X0 equals the sum of each X6's W2, each Z7's Y3 and each Z7's Y9. The number of each Y9's X6 equals each X6's W2. How many X6 does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["20. Z7's Y3 as u. So u = 12.\nDefine each Z7's Y9 as S. So S = 22 * u = 22 * 12 = 11.\nDefine each Y3's X3 as A. So A = 17 * S = 17 * 11 = 3.\nDefine each Z7's Y6 as i. So i = A + S = 3 + 11 = 14.\nDefine each X6's W2 as Y. So Y = 16 * A - i = 16 * 3 - 14 = 18.\nDefine each Y9's X6 as F. So F = Y = 18.\nDefine each Y9's X0 as r. So r = (Y + u + S) = (18 + 12 + 11) = 18.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as l. So l = r + F = 18 + 18 = 13.\nDefine each Z2's Y9 as V. So V = l = 13.\nDefine each Z2's XXX as q. So q = V * l = 13 * 13 = 8.\nDefine each X3's W9 as z. So z = 0 * q = 0 * 8 = 0.\nDefine each Z5's Y9 as A. So A = i - S = 14 - 11 = 3.\nDefine each Y6's X6 as i. So i = 20 * A = 20 * 3 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 696, "question": "The number of each X9's W0 equals 9 more than each Y5's X3. The number of each Y5's X3 equals 2. The number of each X9's W5 equals 15 more than each Y5's X3. How many WWW does each X9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Y5's X3 = 2. X9's W5 as u. So u = 15 * Y5's X3 = 15 * 2 = 7.\nDefine each X9's W0 as S. So S = 9 * Y5's X3 = 9 * 2 = 18.\nDefine each X9's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 18 + 7 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 697, "question": "The number of each X8's W5 equals the difference of each X4's W7 and each X4's W5. The number of each X4's W7 equals each X5's WWW. The number of each X5's W5 equals 21. The number of each X6's W7 equals 3 times each X4's WWW. The number of each X8's W7 equals each X6's WWW. The number of each X4's W5 equals each X5's W5. How many WWW does each X8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["X5's W5 as u. So u = 21.\nDefine each X5's WWW as S. So S = u = 21.\nDefine each X4's W7 as A. So A = S = 21.\nDefine each X4's W5 as i. So i = u = 21.\nDefine each X4's WWW as Y. So Y = A + i = 21 + 21 = 19.\nDefine each X6's W7 as F. So F = 3 * Y = 3 * 19 = 11.\nDefine each X6's WWW as r. So r = F = 11.\nDefine each X8's W7 as l. So l = r = 11.\nDefine each X8's W5 as V. So V = A - i = 21 - 21 = 0.\nDefine each X8's WWW as q. So q = V + l = 0 + 11 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 698, "question": "The number of each Z4's Y7 equals 16. How many Y7 does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Z4's Y7 = 16. So 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 699, "question": "The number of each Y0's X8 equals 0 times the sum of each X8's W4, each Y1's WWW and each Y1's X8. The number of each Y1's X8 equals 2 times the difference of each X8's W4 and each X8's WWW. The number of each X8's W4 equals 13. How many X8 does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["X8's W4 as u. So u = 13.\nDefine each X8's WWW as S. So S = u = 13.\nDefine each Y1's X8 as A. So A = 2 * u - S = 2 * 13 - 13 = 13.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as i. So i = A * S = 13 * 13 = 8.\nDefine each Y0's X8 as Y. So Y = 0 * (u + i + A) = 0 * (13 + 8 + 13) = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 700, "question": "The number of each X0's W6 equals 6 times each Y9's X0. The number of each Y9's X0 equals 1. How many WWW does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Y9's X0 = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9's WWW = 1. Y9"], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 701, "question": "The number of each Y9's X3 equals 1 more than the sum of each Z7's Y2, each Z7's YYY and each Y8's X2. The number of each Y9's X2 equals each Z5's YYY. The number of each Z7's Y2 equals each Y2's X8. The number of each Y2's X8 equals 9. The number of each Z5's Y9 equals 3 more than the difference of each X0's W4 and each Z7's YYY. The number of each Y8's X2 equals 4 more than each Y9's X2. The number of each X0's W4 equals 15 more than the difference of each Y2's X8 and each Z7's YYY. How many X3 does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 702, "question": "The number of each Y3's X4 equals 2 times the sum of each Y0's X2 and each Z9's Y0. The number of each Z9's Y0 equals 18. The number of each Y0's X4 equals 20. The number of each Y0's X2 equals each Z9's Y0. The number of each Z1's Y3 equals 8 times each Y0's X2. The number of each Z1's Y0 equals 8 more than each Y3's X4. The number of each Y3's X2 equals each Y3's X4. How many XXX does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["Z9's Y0 = 18. Y0's X2 as u. So u = Z9's Y0 = 18.\nDefine each Y3's X4 as S. So S = 2 * u + Z9's Y0 = 2 * 18 + 18 = 8.\nDefine each Y3's X2 as A. So A = S = 8.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as i. So i = S + A = 8 + 8 = 16.\nDefine each Z1's Y3 as Y. So Y = 8 + u = 8 + 18 = 3.\nDefine each Y0's X4 as F. So F = 20.\nDefine each Z1's Y0 as r. So r = 8 + S = 8 + 8 = 16.\nDefine each Y0's X2 as l. So l = Z9's Y0 = 18.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as V. So V = l + F + u = 18 + 20 + 18 = 10.\nDefine each Z1's XXX as q. So q = r * V + Y * i = 16 * 10 + 3 * 16 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 703, "question": "The number of each Y6's X0 equals 8 times each Z2's Y6. The number of each Y0's X5 equals 0. The number of each Z6's Y9 equals 18 times each Y0's X5. The number of each Z2's Y6 equals 21 more than each Z6's Y9. The number of each Z0's Y6 equals each Y6's X0. How many YYY does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["Y0's X5 as u. So u = 0.\nDefine each Z6's Y9 as S. So S = 18 * u = 18 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z2's Y6 as A. So A = 21 * S = 21 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y6's X0 as i. So i = 8 * A = 8 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z0's Y6 as Y. So Y = i = 0.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as F. So F = Y = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 704, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y6 equals 6. The number of each X4's W3 equals 14 more than each Y6's XXX. The number of each Y6's X5 equals 8 times each Y8's X5. The number of each Y8's X5 equals 7 times the sum of each Z8's Y6 and each Z8's YYY. The number of each Z8's Y8 equals 1. How many W3 does each X4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Z8's Y8 as u. So u = 1.\nDefine each Z8's Y6 as S. So S = 6.\nDefine each Z8's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 6 + 1 = 7.\nDefine each Y8's X5 as i. So i = 7 * S + A = 7 * 6 + 7 = 3.\nDefine each Y6's X5 as Y. So Y = 8 + i = 8 + 3 = 11.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as F. So F = Y = 11.\nDefine each X4's W3 as r. So r = 14 * F = 14 * 11 = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 705, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y7 equals 3 more than each X5's WWW. The number of each Z8's Y3 equals 6 more than each Z8's Y7. The number of each X5's W4 equals 16 times each X5's W8. The number of each X5's W8 equals 22. How many YYY does each Z8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["X5's W8 as u. So u = 22.\nDefine each X5's W4 as S. So S = 16 * u = 16 * 22 = 7.\nDefine each X5's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 7 + 22 = 6.\nDefine each Z8's Y7 as i. So i = 3 * A = 3 * 6 = 18.\nDefine each Z8's Y3 as Y. So Y = 6 * i = 6 * 18 = 16.\nDefine each Z8's YYY as F. So F = Y + i = 16 + 18 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 706, "question": "The number of each X4's W9 equals 1. The number of each X4's W8 equals 21. How many WWW does each X4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["X4's W8 as u. So u = 21.\nDefine each X4's W9 as S. So S = 1.\nDefine each X4's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 1 + 21 = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 707, "question": "The number of each Y3's X9 equals 11 times the sum of each Y7's XXX, each Y3's X4 and each Y7's X9. The number of each Y7's X9 equals 18. The number of each Y7's X4 equals each Y7's X9. The number of each Y3's X4 equals each Y7's X4. How many XXX does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Y7's X9 as u. So u = 18.\nDefine each Y7's X4 as S. So S = u = 18.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 18 + 18 = 13.\nDefine each Y3's X4 as i. So i = S = 18.\nDefine each Y3's X9 as Y. So Y = 11 * (A + i + u) = 11 * (13 + 18 + 18) = 19.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as F. So F = Y + i = 19 + 18 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 708, "question": "The number of each Y6's X4 equals 6 more than each Y1's X3. The number of each Y4's X5 equals 2 more than the sum of each Y6's X4, each Y1's X3 and each Y1's X7. The number of each Y1's X3 equals each Y1's X7. The number of each Y1's X7 equals 18. How many X5 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Y1's X7 as u. So u = 18.\nDefine each Y1's X3 as S. So S = u = 18.\nDefine each Y6's X4 as A. So A = 6 * S = 6 * 18 = 16.\nDefine each Y4's X5 as i. So i = 2 * (A + S + u) = 2 * (16 + 18 + 18) = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 709, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y7 equals the sum of each Y7's X4 and each Y6's X7. The number of each Z4's Y6 equals 10. The number of each Y7's X4 equals 2. The number of each Y6's X7 equals 12 times the difference of each Y7's X4 and each Z4's Y6. The number of each X4's W6 equals each Y6's X7. The number of each Y9's X4 equals each Z1's WWW. How many X4 does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Z4's Y6 = 10. Y7's X4 as u. So u = 2.\nDefine each Y6's X7 as S. So S = 12 * u - Z4's Y6 = 12 * 2 - 10 = 14.\nDefine each X4's W6 as A. So A = S = 14.\nDefine each X4's WWW as i. So i = A = 14.\nDefine each Y7's WWW as Y. So Y = u * i = 2 * 14 = 5.\nDefine each Z1's Y7 as F. So F = u + S = 2 + 14 = 16.\nDefine each Z1's WWW as r. So r = F * Y = 16 * 5 = 11.\nDefine each Y9's X4 as l. So l = r = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 710, "question": "The number of each X1's W9 equals the difference of each X4's W9 and each X4's W7. The number of each X1's W7 equals 10 more than each X1's W1. The number of each X4's W9 equals 17. The number of each X1's W1 equals 21 times each X4's W7. The number of each X4's W7 equals 5 times each X4's W9. How many WWW does each X1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["X4's W9 as u. So u = 17.\nDefine each X4's W7 as S. So S = 5 * u = 5 * 17 = 16.\nDefine each X1's W1 as A. So A = 21 * S = 21 * 16 = 14.\nDefine each X1's W7 as i. So i = 10 * A = 10 * 14 = 2.\nDefine each X1's W9 as Y. So Y = u - S = 17 - 16 = 1.\nDefine each X1's WWW as F. So F = Y + A + i = 1 + 14 + 2 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 711, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y6 equals 6. The number of each Z1's Y1 equals 19 times the difference of each Y8's X1 and each Z5's Y6. The number of each Y1's X1 equals 15 times the sum of each Z5's Y6 and each Z1's Y1. The number of each Y8's X1 equals each Z5's Y6. The number of each Z4's Y1 equals the sum of each Y1's X1, each Y8's X1 and each Z1's XXX. How many XXX does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Z5's Y6 = 6. Y8's X1 = Z5's Y6 = 6. Z1's Y1 as u. So u = 19 * Y8's X1 - Z5's Y6 = 19 * 6 - 6 = 16.\nDefine each Y1's X1 as S. So S = 15 * Z5's Y6 + u = 15 * 6 + 16 = 14.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as A. So A = S = 14.\nDefine each Z1's XXX as i. So i = u * A = 16 * 14 = 17.\nDefine each Z4's Y1 as Y. So Y = (S + Y + i) = (14 + 14 + 17) = 22.\nDefine each Z4's XXX as F. So F = Y * A = 22 * 14 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 712, "question": "The number of each X6's W9 equals 13. The number of each X7's W9 equals 2 times each X6's W9. The number of each X4's W9 equals 20 times the sum of each X7's W9, each X6's WWW and each X7's WWW. The number of each X7's W3 equals the sum of each X6's W9 and each X6's WWW. How many W9 does each X4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["X6's W9 as u. So u = 13.\nDefine each X6's WWW as S. So S = u = 13.\nDefine each X7's W3 as A. So A = u + S = 13 + 13 = 3.\nDefine each X7's W9 as i. So i = 2 * u = 2 * 13 = 3.\nDefine each X7's WWW as Y. So Y = A + i = 3 + 3 = 6.\nDefine each X4's W9 as F. So F = 20 * (i + S + Y) = 20 * (3 + 13 + 6) = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 713, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y4 equals 20 times each Y4's XXX. The number of each Y4's X8 equals 12. The number of each X8's W7 equals 19 more than each Z8's XXX. The number of each Y1's X9 equals each Z8's WWW. How many XXX does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Y4's X8 as u. So u = 12.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as S. So S = u = 12.\nDefine each Z8's Y4 as A. So A = 20 * S = 20 * 12 = 10.\nDefine each Z8's XXX as i. So i = A * S = 10 * 12 = 5.\nDefine each X8's W7 as Y. So Y = 19 * i = 19 * 5 = 3.\nDefine each X8's WWW as F. So F = Y = 3.\nDefine each Y4's WWW as r. So r = u * F = 12 * 3 = 13.\nDefine each Z8's WWW as l. So l = A * r = 10 * 13 = 15.\nDefine each Y1's X9 as V. So V = l = 15.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as q. So q = V = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 714, "question": "The number of each X5's W8 equals 3 more than the difference of each X0's W7 and each X5's W0. The number of each X0's W7 equals 2. The number of each X5's W0 equals 7 times each X0's W7. How many W8 does each X5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["X0's W7 as u. So u = 2.\nDefine each X5's W0 as S. So S = 7 * u = 7 * 2 = 14.\nDefine each X5's W8 as A. So A = 3 * u - S = 3 * 2 - 14 = 15.\nDefine each X5's WWW as i. So i = S + A = 14 + 15 = 6.\nDefine each Y1's l0 as Y. So Y = 20.\nDefine each Y1's l0 as F. So F = 20.\nDefine each Y1's lWW as r. So r = Y * F = 20 * 20 = 9.\nDefine each X3's W3 as l. So l = 3.\nDefine each X3's WWW as V. So V = l = 3.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as q. So q = Y * r + F * i = 20 * 9 + 20 * 6 = 11.\nDefine each X5's WWW as z. So z = S + A = 14 + 15 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 715, "question": "The number of each X0's W5 equals 3. The number of each X8's W5 equals each X0's WWW. How many WWW does each X8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["X0's W5 as u. So u = 3.\nDefine each X0's WWW as S. So S = u = 3.\nDefine each X8's W5 as A. So A = S = 3.\nDefine each X8's WWW as i. So i = A = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 716, "question": "The number of each Y6's X0 equals 7. The number of each Z5's Y8 equals each Z0's XXX. The number of each Z0's Y8 equals 9 times each Y6's X0. The number of each X0's W8 equals 1 times each Z5's YYY. The number of each Z0's Y6 equals 12. The number of each Y8's X4 equals 10. The number of each Y8's X8 equals 21. How many WWW does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["Y6's X0 as u. So u = 7.\nDefine each Z0's Y8 as S. So S = 9 * u = 9 * 7 = 17.\nDefine each Y8's X8 as A. So A = 21.\nDefine each Y8's X4 as i. So i = 10.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as Y. So Y = A + i = 21 + 10 = 8.\nDefine each Z0's Y6 as F. So F = 12.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as r. So r = u = 7.\nDefine each Z0's XXX as l. So l = S * Y + F * r = 17 * 8 + 12 * 7 = 19.\nDefine each Z5's Y8 as V. So V = l = 19.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as q. So q = V = 19.\nDefine each X0's W8 as z. So z = 1 * q = 1 * 19 = 19.\nDefine each X0's WWW as A. So A = z = 19.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as i. So i = u * A = 7 * 19 = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 717, "question": "The number of each Y0's X4 equals 16 more than the sum of each X4's W6 and each X4's WWW. The number of each X4's W6 equals 6 more than the sum of each Y6's X4 and each X2's W8. The number of each Y6's X4 equals 1. The number of each X2's W8 equals 6 more than each Y6's X4. How many X4 does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["Y6's X4 = 1.\nDefine each X2's W8 as u. So u = 6 * Y6's X4 = 6 * 1 = 6.\nDefine each X4's W6 as S. So S = 6 * u + u = 6 * 6 + 6 = 19.\nDefine each X4's WWW as A. So A = S = 19.\nDefine each Y0's X4 as i. So i = 16 * S + A = 16 * 19 + 19 = 1.\nDefine each Y6's X4 as Y. So Y = 1.\nDefine each X2's WWW as F. So F = u = 6.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as r. So r = Y * A = 1 * 19 = 19.\nDefine each Y0's WWW as l. So l = i * A = 1 * 19 = 19.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 718, "question": "The number of each Y7's X5 equals 22. How many X5 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["Y7's X5 = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 719, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y9 equals 7 times the sum of each Z5's Y6 and each Z9's Y6. The number of each Z5's Y6 equals 7 times each Z9's Y6. The number of each Z9's Y6 equals 15. How many YYY does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Z9's Y6 as u. So u = 15.\nDefine each Z5's Y6 as S. So S = 7 * u = 7 * 15 = 13.\nDefine each Z5's Y9 as A. So A = 7 * S + u = 7 * 13 + 15 = 19.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as i. So i = S + A + A = 13 + 19 + 19 = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 720, "question": "The number of each X4's W5 equals each Y4's WWW. The number of each Y3's X4 equals 4 more than each X4's WWW. The number of each Y0's X7 equals 19 more than each Y7's WWW. The number of each X5's W1 equals 10. The number of each X1's W6 equals the sum of each Y3's WWW and each Y4's WWW. The number of each Y4's X5 equals 3 more than each X5's W1. The number of each Y7's X1 equals 3. How many X7 does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["3. Y7's X1 = 3. X1's W6 = Y3's WWW + Y4's WWW = 3. Y7's WWW = 3. Y4's X5 as u. So u = 3 * X5's W1 = 3 * 10 = 7.\nDefine each X5's W1 as S. So S = 10.\nDefine each X5's WWW as A. So A = S = 10.\nDefine each Y4's WWW as i. So i = u * A = 7 * 10 = 1.\nDefine each X4's W5 as Y. So Y = i = 1.\nDefine each X4's WWW as F. So F = Y = 1.\nDefine each Y3's X4 as r. So r = 4 * F = 4 * 1 = 4.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as l. So l = r * F = 4 * 1 = 4.\nDefine each X1's W6 as V. So V = l + i = 4 + 1 = 5.\nDefine each Y7's X1 as q. So q = 3.\nDefine each X1's WWW as z. So z = V = 5.\nDefine each Y7's WWW as A. So A = q * Z = 3 * 5 = 15.\nDefine each Y0's X7 as i. So i = 19 * A = 19 * 15 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 721, "question": "The number of each X8's W4 equals 4 times each X8's W6. The number of each X8's W6 equals 9 times each X1's W6. The number of each X1's W4 equals 12. The number of each X1's W6 equals 20 more than each X1's W4. The number of each X2's W4 equals each X8's W4. How many W4 does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["X1's W4 as u. So u = 12.\nDefine each X1's W6 as S. So S = 20 * u = 20 * 12 = 10.\nDefine each X8's W6 as A. So A = 9 * S = 9 * 10 = 21.\nDefine each X8's W4 as i. So i = 4 * A = 4 * 21 = 15.\nDefine each X2's W4 as Y. So Y = i = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 722, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y8 equals the difference of each Y7's XXX and each Y8's XXX. The number of each Y8's X6 equals 22 times each Y7's XXX. The number of each Y7's X4 equals each Z5's Y7. The number of each Z5's Y7 equals 11. The number of each Z9's Y7 equals 17 more than each Y8's X6. The number of each Y8's X3 equals 0 more than the sum of each Y7's XXX and each Y7's X6. The number of each Y7's X6 equals 17 times each Y7's X4. How many YYY does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Y7's X4 as u. So u = Z5's Y7 = 11.\nDefine each Y7's X6 as S. So S = 17 * u = 17 * 11 = 3.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 3 + 11 = 14.\nDefine each Y8's X6 as i. So i = 22 * A = 22 * 14 = 9.\nDefine each Y8's X3 as Y. So Y = 0 * A + S = 0 * 14 + 3 = 3.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as F. So F = Y + i = 3 + 9 = 12.\nDefine each Z9's Y8 as r. So r = A - F = 14 - 12 = 2.\nDefine each Z9's Y7 as l. So l = 17 * i = 17 * 9 = 15.\nDefine each Z9's YYY as V. So V = l + r = 15 + 2 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 723, "question": "The number of each Y3's X3 equals 2 times each Z4's Y5. The number of each Z4's Y5 equals each Y5's X3. The number of each Z3's Y3 equals 7 times each Z4's Y5. The number of each Y3's X2 equals each Z4's WWW. The number of each X3's W7 equals the difference of each Z4's Y5 and each Z4's XXX. The number of each X2's W2 equals 21 times each X3's W7. The number of each Y5's X3 equals 17. How many WWW does each Z3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["Y5's X3 as u. So u = 17.\nDefine each Z4's Y5 as S. So S = u = 17.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as A. So A = u = 17.\nDefine each Z4's XXX as i. So i = S * A = 17 * 17 = 13.\nDefine each X3's W7 as Y. So Y = S - i = 17 - 13 = 4.\nDefine each X2's W2 as F. So F = 21 * Y = 21 * 4 = 15.\nDefine each X2's WWW as r. So r = F = 15.\nDefine each Y5's WWW as l. So l = u * r = 17 * 15 = 2.\nDefine each Z4's WWW as V. So V = S * l = 17 * 2 = 11.\nDefine each Y3's X2 as q. So q = V = 11.\nDefine each Z3's Y3 as z. So z = 7 * S = 7 * 17 = 4.\nDefine each Y3's X3 as A. So A = 2 * S = 2 * 17 = 11.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as i. So i = q + A = 11 + 11 = 22.\nDefine each Z3's XXX as Y. So Y = z * i = 4 * 22 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 724, "question": "The number of each X2's W7 equals 15 more than each Y8's WWW. The number of each Y0's X8 equals 8 more than each Y3's X2. The number of each Y1's X6 equals 15 times each X2's W7. The number of each Y1's X3 equals 14 more than each Y1's X6. The number of each Y8's X6 equals each X6's WWW. The number of each Y8's X3 equals the sum of each X6's WWW and each X6's W8. The number of each X6's W8 equals 20 more than each Y3's X6. The number of each Y3's X2 equals the sum of each Y1's XXX and each Y8's WWW. The number of each Y1's X2 equals each X3's W7. The number of each X3's W7 equals 15 more than each X6's W8. The number of each Y3's X6 equals 8. How many X8 does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Y3's X6 = 8. X6's W8 = 20 * Y3's X6 = 20 * 8 = 22.\nDefine each X3's W7 as u. So u = 15 * S = 15 * 22 = 8.\nDefine each Y1's X2 as S. So S = u = 8.\nDefine each X6's W8 as A. So A = 20 * Y3's X6 = 20 * 8 = 22.\nDefine each X6's WWW as i. So i = A = 22.\nDefine each Y8's X6 as Y. So Y = i = 22.\nDefine each Y8's X3 as F. So F = i + A = 22 + 22 = 21.\nDefine each Y1's X6 as r. So r = 15 * i = 15 * 22 = 8.\nDefine each Y1's X3 as l. So l = 14 * r = 14 * 8 = 20.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as V. So V = l + r + S = 20 + 8 + 8 = 13.\nDefine each Y3's X2 as q. So q = V + i = 13 + 22 = 12.\nDefine each Y0's X8 as z. So z = 8 * q = 8 * 12 = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 725, "question": "The number of each Y8's X4 equals 14 more than each Y1's X4. The number of each Y1's X4 equals 8. How many X4 does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["Y1's X4 as u. So u = 8.\nDefine each Y8's X4 as S. So S = 14 * u = 14 * 8 = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 726, "question": "The number of each Y0's X0 equals 14 times each Y0's X6. The number of each Y0's X6 equals 3 times each X5's WWW. The number of each X5's W8 equals 11 times each Y3's X5. The number of each Y3's X5 equals 0. How many XXX does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y3's X5 = 0.\nDefine each X5's W8 as u. So u = 11 * Y3's X5 = 11 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X5's WWW as S. So S = u = 0.\nDefine each Y0's X6 as A. So A = 3 * S = 3 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y0's X0 as i. So i = 14 * A = 14 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as Y. So Y = i + A = 0 + 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 727, "question": "The number of each X0's W4 equals 16 times the difference of each X0's W9 and each Y9's X0. The number of each Y9's X4 equals 20 times the difference of each X0's WWW and each Y3's X0. The number of each Y9's X0 equals 9. The number of each X0's W9 equals 16 more than each Y9's X0. The number of each Y3's X0 equals 15 times the sum of each Y9's X0, each X0's W9 and each X0's WWW. How many X4 does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Y9's X0 = 9. X0's W9 as u. So u = 16 * Y9's X0 = 16 * 9 = 6.\nDefine each X0's W4 as S. So S = 16 * u - Y9's X0 = 16 * 6 - 9 = 15.\nDefine each X0's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 15 + 6 = 21.\nDefine each Y3's X0 as i. So i = 15 * (Y9's X0 + u + A) = 15 * (9 + 6 + 21) = 19.\nDefine each Y9's X4 as Y. So Y = 20 * A - i = 20 * 21 - 19 = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 728, "question": "The number of each X7's W0 equals 2 more than each Y6's X7. The number of each Y6's X7 equals 16. How many W0 does each X7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["Y6's X7 = 16. X7's W0 = 2 * Y6's X7 = 2 * 16 = 9.\nDefine each Y6's X7 as u. So u = 16.\nDefine each X7's W0 as S. So S = 2 * u = 2 * 16 = 9.\nDefine each X7's WWW as A. So A = S = 9.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as i. So i = u * A = 16 * 9 = 6.\nDefine each X3's W0 as Y. So Y = 5 + i = 5 + 6 = 11.\nDefine each X3's WWW as F. So F = Y = 11.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as r. So r = u * A = 16 * 9 = 6.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as l. So l = u * A = 16 * 9 = 6.\nDefine each X7's W0 as V. So V = 2 * u = 2 * 16 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 729, "question": "The number of each X4's W8 equals 16. The number of each X6's W3 equals 1 times the sum of each X4's WWW, each X4's W8 and each X7's W8. The number of each X7's W8 equals 14 more than the difference of each X4's W8 and each X4's WWW. How many WWW does each X6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["X4's W8 as u. So u = 16.\nDefine each X4's WWW as S. So S = u = 16.\nDefine each X7's W8 as A. So A = 14 * u - S = 14 * 16 - 16 = 1.\nDefine each X6's W3 as i. So i = 1 * (S + u + A) = 1 * (16 + 16 + 1) = 10.\nDefine each X6's WWW as Y. So Y = i = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 730, "question": "The number of each X1's W0 equals 0. How many W0 does each X1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["X1's W0 = 0. So 0.\nDefine each X1's WWW as u. So u = X1.\nDefine each Y1's l0 as S. So S = 0.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as A. So A = S * u = 0 * 1 = 0.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as i. So i = S * A = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's l0 as Y. So Y = 0.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as F. So F = Y + S = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each X3's W0 as r. So r = 0.\nDefine each X3's WWW as l. So l = r = 0.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as V. So V = Y = 0.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 731, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y6 equals 5. How many YYY does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Z6's Y6 = 5. Z6's YYY = Z6's YYY = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 732, "question": "The number of each X0's W1 equals 5 more than each Z3's YYY. The number of each Z3's Y5 equals 0. How many W1 does each X0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Z3's Y5 as u. So u = 0.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as S. So S = u = 0.\nDefine each X0's W1 as A. So A = 5 * S = 5 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as i. So i = A = 0.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as Y. So Y = i = 0.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as F. So F = Y = 0.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as r. So r = F + Y + i = 0 + 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as l. So l = r + Y + F = 0 + 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z3's XXX as V. So V = u * l = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each l. So l = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 733, "question": "The number of each Z4's Y6 equals 18. How many Y6 does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["Z4's Y6 = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 734, "question": "The number of each Y1's X7 equals 2. The number of each Y5's X2 equals each Y1's X7. How many XXX does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Y1's X7 as u. So u = 2.\nDefine each Y5's X2 as S. So S = u = 2.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as A. So A = S = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 735, "question": "The number of each X6's W4 equals 21 times each X6's W2. The number of each Y0's X6 equals each X6's WWW. The number of each X6's W2 equals 8. The number of each X5's W4 equals 17. The number of each X5's W2 equals 7 times each Y0's X6. How many WWW does each X5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["X6's W2 as u. So u = 8.\nDefine each X6's W4 as S. So S = 21 * u = 21 * 8 = 7.\nDefine each X6's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 7 + 8 = 15.\nDefine each Y0's X6 as i. So i = A = 15.\nDefine each X5's W2 as Y. So Y = 7 * i = 7 * 15 = 13.\nDefine each X5's W4 as F. So F = 17.\nDefine each X5's WWW as r. So r = Y + F = 13 + 17 = 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 736, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y0 equals 1 times each Z0's Y6. The number of each Y6's X2 equals each X2's W4. The number of each X3's W4 equals 14 more than the difference of each Y0's X3 and each Y0's XXX. The number of each Y0's X3 equals the sum of each Y6's XXX, each Y6's X3 and each Z0's YYY. The number of each X2's W4 equals the sum of each Z0's YYY and each Z0's Y0. The number of each X3's W0 equals 5 times the sum of each X2's W4 and each Y6's XXX. The number of each Z0's Y6 equals 0. The number of each Y6's X3 equals 10 times each X2's W4. How many WWW does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Z0's Y6 as u. So u = 0.\nDefine each Z0's Y0 as S. So S = 1 * u = 1 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each X2's W4 as i. So i = A + S = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y6's X3 as Y. So Y = 10 * i = 10 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y6's X2 as F. So F = i = 0.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as r. So r = Y + F = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y0's X3 as l. So l = (r + Y + A) = (0 + 0 + 0) = 0.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as V. So V = l = 0.\nDefine each X3's W4 as q. So q = 14 * l - V = 14 * 0 - 0 = 0.\nDefine each X3's W0 as z. So z = 5 * i + r = 5 * 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each X3's WWW as A. So A = q + z = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y0's WWW as i. So i = l * A = 0 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 737, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y3 equals 2. How many Y3 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Z5's Y3 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 738, "question": "The number of each X9's W1 equals each Y3's X1. The number of each Y6's X8 equals 19 more than each Y3's X8. The number of each X1's W6 equals 14. The number of each Y3's X9 equals 9 times the difference of each X1's W1 and each X1's W6. The number of each Y3's X8 equals the difference of each X1's W3 and each X1's W6. The number of each X1's W1 equals 4 more than each X1's W6. The number of each X1's W3 equals 22 more than each X9's W1. The number of each Y3's X1 equals 3 times the sum of each X1's W1, each Y3's X9 and each X1's W6. How many X8 does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 739, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y6 equals 0 times each Z9's YYY. The number of each Z3's Y1 equals the difference of each Z2's XXX and each Z9's YYY. The number of each Z3's Y2 equals the sum of each Z9's XXX and each Z2's XXX. The number of each Y6's X2 equals 17 more than each Z9's Y6. The number of each Z9's Y6 equals 19 more than each Y1's X5. The number of each Z2's Y6 equals 2 times each Z9's XXX. The number of each Y2's X2 equals 8 times each Z3's YYY. The number of each Y1's X5 equals 4. The number of each Y6's X8 equals 16 times each Z9's Y6. How many X2 does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y1's X5 = 4. Z9's Y6 as u. So u = 19 * Y1's X5 = 19 * 4 = 7.\nDefine each Y6's X2 as S. So S = 17 * u = 17 * 7 = 4.\nDefine each Y6's X8 as A. So A = 16 * u = 16 * 7 = 20.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as i. So i = S + A = 4 + 20 = 1.\nDefine each Z9's XXX as Y. So Y = u * i = 7 * 1 = 7.\nDefine each Z2's Y6 as F. So F = 2 * Y = 2 * 7 = 14.\nDefine each Z2's XXX as r. So r = F * i = 14 * 1 = 14.\nDefine each Z3's Y1 as l. So l = r - Y = 14 - 7 = 7.\nDefine each Z3's Y2 as V. So V = Y + r = 7 + 14 = 21.\nDefine each Z3's Y6 as q. So q = 0 * Y = 0 * 7 = 0.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as z. So z = q + V + l = 0 + 21 + 7 = 5.\nDefine each Y2's X2 as A. So A = 8 * z = 8 * 5 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 740, "question": "The number of each Y2's X1 equals 4. The number of each Y2's X7 equals 17 times each Y2's X1. How many XXX does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["Y2's X1 as u. So u = 4.\nDefine each Y2's X7 as S. So S = 17 * u = 17 * 4 = 22.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 22 + 4 = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 741, "question": "The number of each Y9's X8 equals 14. The number of each Z1's Y9 equals 9. The number of each Z0's Y9 equals 3 times the sum of each Z1's Y9 and each Y9's XXX. The number of each Z7's Y9 equals 0 more than the difference of each Y9's XXX and each Z0's XXX. The number of each Y1's X8 equals 22 times each Z1's Y9. The number of each Z0's Y1 equals each Z0's Y9. How many Y9 does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Y9's X8 = 14. Y9's XXX as u. So u = u = 14.\nDefine each Z1's Y9 as S. So S = 9.\nDefine each Y1's X8 as A. So A = 22 * S = 22 * 9 = 14.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as i. So i = A = 14.\nDefine each Z0's Y9 as Y. So Y = 3 * S + u = 3 * 9 + 14 = 19.\nDefine each Z0's Y1 as F. So F = Y = 19.\nDefine each Z0's XXX as r. So r = Y * u + F * i = 19 * 14 + 19 * 14 = 17.\nDefine each Z7's Y9 as l. So l = 0 * u - r = 0 * 14 - 17 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 742, "question": "The number of each Z4's Y8 equals 10. How many Y8 does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Z4's Y8 = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 743, "question": "The number of each Y7's X6 equals 20. The number of each Z8's Y7 equals each Y7's X6. The number of each Z4's Y7 equals each Z8's Y7. The number of each Z4's Y6 equals 2 times each Z4's Y7. How many Y6 does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["Y7's X6 = 20. Y7's XXX as u. So u = Y7 = 20.\nDefine each Z8's Y7 as S. So S = u = 20.\nDefine each Z4's Y7 as A. So A = S = 20.\nDefine each Z4's Y6 as i. So i = 2 * A = 2 * 20 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 744, "question": "The number of each Y7's X0 equals 0. The number of each Y5's X0 equals 6 more than each Y7's X0. How many X0 does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Y7's X0 = 0. Y5's X0 = 6 * Y7's X0 = 6 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as u. So u = Y5's X0 = 0.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as S. So S = Y7's X0 = 0.\nDefine each X3's XXX as A. So A = i = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each X0's WWW as l. So l = V. So V = 1.\nDefine each Y7's WWW as q. So q = Y7's X0 * l = 0 * 1 = 0.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as A. So A = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 745, "question": "The number of each X2's W2 equals the sum of each Z3's WWW, each Y2's WWW, each Y3's X0 and each X8's W2. The number of each Z4's Y2 equals 22 more than each Y2's WWW. The number of each Y9's X8 equals 6 more than the difference of each X8's W2 and each X8's WWW. The number of each Y3's X0 equals the sum of each Y2's X0 and each Z4's Y2. The number of each Y2's X0 equals 14. The number of each X8's W2 equals 22 more than the difference of each Y3's X0 and each Y2's WWW. The number of each Z3's Y9 equals the sum of each Y2's WWW, each Y9's X8, each X8's WWW and each X0's WWW. The number of each X0's W5 equals 8. How many W2 does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["X0's W5 as u. So u = 8.\nDefine each X0's WWW as S. So S = u = 8.\nDefine each Y2's X0 as A. So A = 14.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as i. So i = A * S = 14 * 8 = 20.\nDefine each Z4's Y2 as Y. So Y = 22 * i = 22 * 20 = 3.\nDefine each Y3's X0 as F. So F = A + Y = 14 + 3 = 17.\nDefine each X8's W2 as r. So r = 22 * F - i = 22 * 17 - 20 = 9.\nDefine each X8's WWW as l. So l = r = 9.\nDefine each Y9's X8 as V. So V = 6 * r - l = 6 * 9 - 9 = 17.\nDefine each Z3's Y9 as q. So q = (i + V + l + S) = (20 + 17 + 9 + 8) = 8.\nDefine each Z3's WWW as z. So z = q * V = 8 * 17 = 21.\nDefine each X2's W2 as A. So A = (z + i + F + r) = (21 + 20 + 17 + 9) = 21.\nThus, the answer is 21."], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 746, "question": "The number of each Y1's X0 equals 20 more than each X0's W8. The number of each Z7's Y6 equals the sum of each X1's W8 and each Y0's XXX. The number of each Y6's X1 equals 5 times each X1's WWW. The number of each Y0's X0 equals 8 times each Z9's WWW. The number of each X1's W8 equals the difference of each Y1's X0 and each X0's W8. The number of each X0's W8 equals 2. The number of each Z9's Y6 equals 7 more than the difference of each X1's W8 and each Y1's X0. How many WWW does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["X0's W8 as u. So u = 2.\nDefine each Y1's X0 as S. So S = 20 * u = 20 * 2 = 17.\nDefine each X1's W8 as A. So A = S - u = 17 - 2 = 15.\nDefine each X1's WWW as i. So i = A = 15.\nDefine each Y6's X1 as Y. So Y = 5 * i = 5 * 15 = 6.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as F. So F = Y * i = 6 * 15 = 21.\nDefine each Z9's Y6 as r. So r = 7 * A - S = 7 * 15 - 17 = 19.\nDefine each Z9's WWW as l. So l = r * F = 19 * 21 = 8.\nDefine each Y0's X0 as V. So V = 8 * l = 8 * 8 = 18.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as q. So q = V = 18.\nDefine each Z7's Y6 as z. So z = A + q = 15 + 18 = 10.\nDefine each Z7's WWW as A. So A = z * F = 10 * 21 = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 747, "question": "The number of each X9's W7 equals the sum of each Y6's X5, each X4's W3 and each X4's W0. The number of each Y6's X5 equals 4 more than the sum of each X4's W3 and each X4's W0. The number of each X9's W0 equals each Y0's X4. The number of each Y6's X9 equals 7 times the sum of each X4's W3 and each X9's WWW. The number of each Y0's X4 equals 20 times each X4's W3. The number of each X4's W3 equals 22 more than each X4's W0. The number of each X9's W3 equals the sum of each X4's W0, each X4's W3 and each Y6's X5. The number of each X4's W0 equals 13. How many X9 does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["X4's W0 = 13.\nDefine each X4's W3 as u. So u = 22 * u = 22 * 13 = 10.\nDefine each Y6's X5 as S. So S = 4 * u + u = 4 * 10 + 10 = 17.\nDefine each X9's W3 as A. So A = (u + u + S) = (10 + 10 + 17) = 14.\nDefine each X9's W7 as i. So i = (S + u + u) = (17 + 10 + 10) = 14.\nDefine each Y0's X4 as Y. So Y = 20 * u = 20 * 10 = 16.\nDefine each X9's W0 as F. So F = Y = 16.\nDefine each X9's WWW as r. So r = A + F + i = 14 + 16 + 14 = 21.\nDefine each Y6's X9 as l. So l = 7 * u + r = 7 * 10 + 21 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 748, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y6 equals 0. The number of each X3's W5 equals 17 times each Z1's Y6. How many W5 does each X3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Z1's Y6 = 0. X3's W5 = 17 * Z1's Y6 = 17 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 749, "question": "The number of each Y7's X2 equals 22 times each Y6's X2. The number of each Y6's X2 equals 0. How many X2 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y6's X2 = 0. Y7's X2 = 22 * Y6's X2 = 22.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as u. So u = Y7's X2 = 22.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as S. So S = Y6's X2 = 0.\nDefine each X2's WWW as A. So A = i. So i = 22.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as l. So l = Y6's X2 = 0.\nDefine each X3's WWW as V. So V = i = 22.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as q. So q = Y6's X2 = 0.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as z. So z = Y7's X2 = 22.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as A. So A = Y7's X2 = 22.\nDefine each X3's WWW as i. So i = V = 22.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as Y. So Y = Y = 22.\nDefine each X2's WWW as F. So F = i = 22.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as r. So r = Y = 22.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as l. So l = Y = 22.\nDefine each X3's WWW as V. So V = i = 22.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as q. So q = Y = 22.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as z. So z = Y = 22.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as A. So A = Y = 22.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as i. So i = Y = 22.\nDefine each X2's WWW as Y. So Y = F = 22.\nDefine each Y7's X2 as F. So F = 22 * Y = 22 * 22 = 1.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as r. So r = Y + F = 22 + 1 = 0.\nDefine each X3's WWW as l. So l = i + V = 22 + 22 = 21.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as V. So V = Y = 22.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as q. So q = Y + F + i = 22 + 1 + 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 750, "question": "The number of each Y3's X4 equals 0 more than the sum of each X6's W9 and each Y6's XXX. The number of each X6's W9 equals 10. The number of each Z8's Y3 equals 12 times the difference of each Y6's WWW and each Y6's X6. The number of each Z8's Y6 equals the sum of each Y6's X6, each X6's WWW, each Y6's XXX and each X6's W9. The number of each X6's W1 equals 19 more than the sum of each X6's W9 and each Y6's X6. The number of each Y6's X6 equals each X6's W9. How many XXX does each Z8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["X6's W9 as u. So u = 10.\nDefine each Y6's X6 as S. So S = u = 10.\nDefine each X6's W1 as A. So A = 19 * u + S = 19 * 10 + 10 = 16.\nDefine each X6's WWW as i. So i = A + u = 16 + 10 = 3.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as Y. So Y = S * i = 10 * 3 = 7.\nDefine each Z8's Y3 as F. So F = 12 * Y - S = 12 * 7 - 10 = 15.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as r. So r = S = 10.\nDefine each Z8's Y6 as l. So l = (S + i + r + u) = (10 + 3 + 10 + 10) = 10.\nDefine each Y3's X4 as V. So V = 0 * u + r = 0 * 10 + 10 = 10.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as q. So q = V = 10.\nDefine each Z8's XXX as z. So z = l * r + F * q = 10 * 10 + 15 * 10 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 751, "question": "The number of each Y7's X5 equals 5 times each Y7's X0. The number of each Z9's Y7 equals 5 times each Z9's Y2. The number of each Z5's Y2 equals the difference of each Y7's XXX and each Y9's X0. The number of each Y7's X0 equals 22 more than each Z9's Y7. The number of each Y9's X0 equals 12 more than the sum of each Z5's Y9 and each Z5's Y7. The number of each Z5's Y7 equals each Y2's X2. The number of each Z5's Y9 equals 10. The number of each Y7's X2 equals 21 times the sum of each Y9's X0, each Y7's X5 and each Z9's Y2. The number of each Z9's Y2 equals 18 times each Y9's X0. The number of each Y2's X2 equals 1 times each Z5's Y9. How many Y2 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["18 + Y9's X0 = 12 + 10 = 9.\nDefine each Z9's Y2 as u. So u = 18 * Y9's X0 = 18 * 9 = 1.\nDefine each Z9's Y7 as S. So S = 5 * u = 5 * 1 = 5.\nDefine each Y7's X0 as A. So A = 22 * S = 22 * 5 = 18.\nDefine each Y7's X5 as i. So i = 5 * A = 5 * 18 = 21.\nDefine each Y2's X2 as Y. So Y = 1 * Z5's Y9 = 1 * 10 = 10.\nDefine each Z5's Y7 as F. So F = Y = 10.\nDefine each Y9's X0 as r. So r = 12 * 10 + F = 5 * 12 + 10 = 1.\nDefine each Z9's Y2 as l. So l = 18 + r = 18 + 1 = 19.\nDefine each Z5's Y9 as V. So V = 10.\nDefine each Y7's X2 as q. So q = 21 + (r + i + l) = 21 + (1 + 21 + 19) = 16.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as z. So z = A + q + i = 18 + 16 + 21 = 9.\nDefine each Z5's Y2 as A. So A = S - r = 5 - 1 = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 752, "question": "The number of each Y4's X0 equals 10. How many X0 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Y4's X0 = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 753, "question": "The number of each X9's W4 equals 16. The number of each X8's W6 equals 12 more than each X9's W4. How many W6 does each X8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["X9's W4 = 16. X8's W6 = 12 * X9's W4 = 12 * 16 = 8.\nThus, the answer is 8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 754, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y5 equals 16. How many Y5 does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Z1's Y5 = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 755, "question": "The number of each X3's W4 equals 16. The number of each X8's W4 equals 10 more than each X3's WWW. How many WWW does each X8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["X3's W4 as u. So u = 16.\nDefine each X3's WWW as S. So S = u = 16.\nDefine each X8's W4 as A. So A = 10 * S = 10 * 16 = 22.\nDefine each X8's WWW as i. So i = A = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 756, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y8 equals 1 times each Z6's WWW. The number of each Y5's X9 equals 19 more than each Z0's Y8. The number of each X9's W9 equals 12 more than each Z6's XXX. The number of each Z0's Y8 equals 10. The number of each Z6's Y5 equals 3 more than each Z0's Y8. How many Y8 does each Z8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Z0's Y8 = 10. Y5's X9 = 19 * Z0's Y8 = 19. Y5's XXX = 19. Z6's Y5 as u. So u = 3 * Z0's Y8 = 3 * 10 = 7.\nDefine each Z6's XXX as S. So S = u * Y5's X9 = 7 * 19 = 18.\nDefine each X9's W9 as A. So A = 12 * S = 12 * 18 = 9.\nDefine each X9's WWW as i. So i = A = 9.\nDefine each Y5's WWW as Y. So Y = 19.\nDefine each Z6's WWW as F. So F = u * Y = 7 * 19 = 18.\nDefine each Z8's Y8 as r. So r = 1 * F = 1 * 18 = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 757, "question": "The number of each X2's W5 equals 14 times each Y7's X9. The number of each Y7's X9 equals 5. How many W5 does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Y7's X9 = 5. X2's W5 = 14 * Y7's X9 = 14 * 5 = 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 758, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y0 equals 10. How many Y0 does each Z8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Z8's Y0 = 10. So 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 759, "question": "The number of each Z2's Y3 equals 11. The number of each Z2's Y7 equals 22 times each Z2's Y3. How many YYY does each Z2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Z2's Y3 as u. So u = 11.\nDefine each Z2's Y7 as S. So S = 22 * u = 22 * 11 = 12.\nDefine each Z2's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 12 + 11 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 760, "question": "The number of each X7's W7 equals 17. The number of each X9's W7 equals the sum of each Y7's WWW and each Z6's WWW. The number of each Y2's X9 equals the difference of each Y3's X7 and each Z8's Y2. The number of each Z6's Y7 equals each X5's WWW. The number of each Z3's Y2 equals the difference of each Z8's WWW and each Y2's WWW. The number of each Z8's Y2 equals each Z6's WWW. The number of each Y7's X5 equals 20 times each Y3's X9. The number of each X5's W4 equals the difference of each X7's W7 and each Y7's X5. The number of each Y2's X5 equals 1 more than each X9's WWW. The number of each Y3's X9 equals 4 more than each X7's W7. The number of each Y3's X7 equals 2 more than each X9's W7. How many WWW does each Z3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["X7's W7 = 17. Y3's X9 = 4 * X7 = 4 * 17 = 22.\nDefine each Y7's X5 as u. So u = 20 * Y3's X9 = 20 * 22 = 3.\nDefine each X5's W4 as S. So S = A - u = 17 - 3 = 14.\nDefine each X5's WWW as A. So A = S = 14.\nDefine each Y7's WWW as i. So i = u * A = 3 * 14 = 19.\nDefine each Z6's Y7 as Y. So Y = A = 14.\nDefine each Z6's WWW as F. So F = Y * i = 14 * 19 = 13.\nDefine each Z8's Y2 as r. So r = F = 13.\nDefine each X9's W7 as l. So l = i + F = 19 + 13 = 9.\nDefine each X9's WWW as V. So V = l = 9.\nDefine each Y2's X5 as q. So q = 1 * V = 1 * 9 = 9.\nDefine each Y3's X7 as z. So z = 2 * l = 2 * 9 = 18.\nDefine each Y2's X9 as A. So A = S - r = 14 - 13 = 1.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as i. So i = q * A + q * A = 9 * 1 + 1 * 9 = 18.\nDefine each Z8's WWW as Y. So Y = r * i = 13 * 18 = 4.\nDefine each Z3's Y2 as F. So F = Y - i = 4 - 18 = 9.\nDefine each Z3's WWW as r. So r = F * i = 9 * 18 = 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 761, "question": "The number of each Z2's Y7 equals 0 times each Z8's Y0. The number of each Z8's Y0 equals 1. How many Y7 does each Z2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Z8's Y0 = 1. Z2's Y7 = 0 * Y0 = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z2's Y7 as u. So u = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 762, "question": "The number of each X5's W1 equals 3 more than each X8's W1. The number of each Y2's X5 equals 16. The number of each X8's W1 equals each Y2's X5. How many W1 does each X5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Y2's X5 = 16. X8's W1 = Y2's X5. X5's W1 = 3 * X8's W1 = 3 * 8 = 1.\nDefine each X5's W1 as u. So u = 3 * X8's W1 = 3 * 8 = 1.\nDefine each X5's WWW as S. So S = u = 1.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as A. So A = Y2's X5 * S = 16 * 1 = 16.\nDefine each X8's W1 as i. So i = Y2's X5 = 16.\nDefine each X5's W1 as Y. So Y = 3 + i = 3 + 16 = 19.\nDefine each X5's WWW as F. So F = Y + u = 19 + 1 = 20.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as r. So r = Y * F = 19 * 20 = 12.\nDefine each X8's WWW as l. So l = i = 16.\nDefine each Y2's X5 as V. So V = 16.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as q. So q = V * S + r * l = 16 * 1 + 12 * 16 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 763, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y3 equals the sum of each X7's W5, each X7's WWW and each X6's W3. The number of each Z6's Y2 equals the difference of each Y2's WWW and each Z9's WWW. The number of each Y3's X6 equals 7 more than the sum of each X6's WWW and each Y3's X7. The number of each Z9's Y2 equals the sum of each Y2's WWW, each X6's WWW and each Y2's X6. The number of each X6's W3 equals 17 more than each Y2's X6. The number of each Y3's X7 equals 5 more than each Y2's WWW. The number of each Y2's X6 equals 17. The number of each X7's W5 equals each Y2's X6. How many Y2 does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Y2's X6 = 17. X6's W3 = 17 * Y2 = 17 * 17 = 13.\nDefine each X6's WWW as u. So u = u = 13.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as S. So S = Y2's X6 * u = 17 * 13 = 14.\nDefine each Y3's X7 as A. So A = 5 * S = 5 * 14 = 1.\nDefine each Y3's X6 as i. So i = 7 * u + A = 7 * 13 + 1 = 22.\nDefine each X7's W5 as Y. So Y = i = 22.\nDefine each X7's WWW as F. So F = Y = 22.\nDefine each Z9's Y3 as r. So r = (Y + F + u) = (22 + 22 + 13) = 11.\nDefine each Z9's Y2 as l. So l = (S + u + i) = (14 + 13 + 22) = 3.\nDefine each Z9's WWW as V. So V = l * S + r * i = 3 * 14 + 11 * 22 = 19.\nDefine each Z6's Y2 as q. So q = S - V = 14 - 19 = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 764, "question": "The number of each X6's W0 equals 0. How many WWW does each X6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's WWW = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's WWW = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's WWW = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6's WWW = X6's W0 = 0. X6'"], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 765, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y7 equals 0 more than each Z9's YYY. The number of each Z9's Y2 equals 19. How many Y7 does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Z9's Y2 as u. So u = 19.\nDefine each Z9's YYY as S. So S = u = 19.\nDefine each Z0's Y7 as A. So A = 0 * S = 0 * 19 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 766, "question": "The number of each Y3's X1 equals 17. The number of each Z2's Y9 equals the sum of each Y3's X1 and each Y3's XXX. How many Y9 does each Z2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["Y3's X1 = 17. Y3's XXX = 17. Y9's XXX as i. So i = Y9's X1 = 19.\nDefine each Z2's Y9 as Y. So Y = u + i = 17 + 19 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 767, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y4 equals 19 more than each Z0's YYY. The number of each Z4's Y4 equals 2. The number of each Z3's Y9 equals 9 more than each Z3's Y7. The number of each Z0's Y9 equals 3 times each Z4's Y4. The number of each Z3's Y7 equals the sum of each Z4's Y4 and each Z9's Y4. How many YYY does each Z3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["Z4's Y4 = 2.\nDefine each Z0's Y9 as u. So u = 3 * Z4's Y4 = 3 * 2 = 6.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as S. So S = u = 6.\nDefine each Z9's Y4 as A. So A = 19 * S = 19 * 6 = 22.\nDefine each Z3's Y7 as i. So i = Z4's Y4 + A = 2 + 22 = 1.\nDefine each Z3's Y9 as Y. So Y = 9 * i = 9 * 1 = 9.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as F. So F = Y + i = 9 + 1 = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 768, "question": "The number of each Y8's X3 equals 5 times each Y8's X9. The number of each Y6's X2 equals 19 times each Y8's X3. The number of each Y8's X9 equals 0. How many X2 does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y8's X9 as u. So u = 0.\nDefine each Y8's X3 as S. So S = 5 * u = 5 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y6's X2 as A. So A = 19 * S = 19 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 769, "question": "The number of each Y7's X5 equals 4. The number of each X8's W2 equals 13 times each Y7's XXX. How many W2 does each X8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Y7's X5 = 4. Y7's XXX = 4. Y7's XXX = 4. Y7's XXX = 4. Y7's XXX = 4. Y7's XXX = 4. Y7's XXX = 4. Y7's XXX = 4. Y7's XXX = 4. Y7's XXX = 4. Y7's XXX = 4. Y7's XXX = 4. Y7's XXX = 4. Y7's XXX = 4. Y7's XXX = 4. Y7's XXX = 4. Y7's XXX = 4. Y7's XXX = 4. Y7's XXX = 4. Y7's XXX = 4. Y7's XXX = 4. Y7's XXX = 4. Y7's XXX = 4. Y7's XXX as u. So u = Y7's X5 + Y7's XXX = 4 + 4 = 8.\nDefine each X8's W2 as S. So S = 13 * u = 13 * 8 = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 770, "question": "The number of each X9's W8 equals the sum of each X9's W9 and each Y2's X9. The number of each Z5's Y2 equals 18. The number of each Y7's X9 equals 20 times each Y2's XXX. The number of each X9's W9 equals 16 more than each Y2's XXX. The number of each Y2's X9 equals each Z5's Y2. How many WWW does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Z5's Y2 = 18. Y2's X9 = Z5's Y2 = 18.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as u. So u = Y2's XXX = 18.\nDefine each X9's W9 as S. So S = 16 * u = 16 * 18 = 12.\nDefine each X9's W8 as A. So A = S + u = 12 + 18 = 7.\nDefine each X9's WWW as i. So i = S + A = 12 + 7 = 19.\nDefine each Y7's X9 as Y. So Y = 20 * u = 20 * 18 = 15.\nDefine each Y7's WWW as F. So F = Y * i = 15 * 19 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 771, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y8 equals 11 times each X2's W6. The number of each Y1's X6 equals each Z6's YYY. The number of each Y1's X2 equals 21 times each Y1's X6. The number of each X2's W6 equals 9. How many XXX does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["X2's W6 = 9. Z6's Y8 = 11 * X2 = 11 * 9 = 7.\nDefine each Z6's YYY as u. So u = u = 7.\nDefine each Y1's X6 as S. So S = u = 7.\nDefine each Y1's X2 as A. So A = 21 * S = 21 * 7 = 9.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as i. So i = S + A = 7 + 9 = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 772, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y2 equals 13 times each Z3's XXX. The number of each X0's W1 equals 16 more than each Z3's Y2. The number of each Y2's X8 equals 21 more than each X0's W1. The number of each Y9's X0 equals 0. The number of each Y2's X0 equals the sum of each Y9's X0 and each Y2's X8. The number of each Z3's Y9 equals the difference of each X0's W1 and each Y9's XXX. The number of each Y9's X8 equals 19 times each Y9's X0. The number of each Z3's Y2 equals 13 more than each Y9's X0. How many Y2 does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["Y9's X0 as u. So u = 0.\nDefine each Z3's Y2 as S. So S = 13 * u = 13 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X0's W1 as A. So A = 16 * S = 16 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y2's X8 as i. So i = 21 * A = 21 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y2's X0 as Y. So Y = u + i = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as F. So F = Y + i = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y9's X8 as r. So r = 19 * u = 19 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as l. So l = r + u = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z3's Y9 as V. So V = A - l = 0 - 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z3's XXX as q. So q = V * l + S * F = 0 * 0 + 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z7's Y2 as z. So z = 13 * q = 13 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 773, "question": "The number of each Y9's X6 equals 3 more than each Z2's XXX. The number of each Y2's X6 equals each Z2's Y2. The number of each Z2's Y2 equals 20 more than each Y9's X1. The number of each Y9's X1 equals 14. The number of each Z4's Y2 equals the sum of each Z2's Y2 and each Y9's X6. The number of each Y2's X1 equals the difference of each Z2's Y2 and each Y9's X1. How many Y2 does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Y9's X1 as u. So u = 14.\nDefine each Z2's Y2 as S. So S = 20 * u = 20 * 14 = 4.\nDefine each Y2's X6 as A. So A = S = 4.\nDefine each Y2's X1 as i. So i = S - u = 4 - 14 = 13.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as Y. So Y = i + A = 13 + 4 = 17.\nDefine each Z2's XXX as F. So F = S * Y = 4 * 17 = 22.\nDefine each Y9's X6 as r. So r = 3 * F = 3 * 22 = 20.\nDefine each Z4's Y2 as l. So l = S + r = 4 + 20 = 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 774, "question": "The number of each X8's W5 equals 3 more than each Z6's Y7. The number of each Z6's Y7 equals 0. How many W5 does each X8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["Z6's Y7 = 0.\nDefine each X8's W5 as u. So u = 3 * Z6's Y7 = 3 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 775, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y8 equals each Y2's X1. The number of each X1's W8 equals 14. The number of each Y2's X1 equals each X1's W8. The number of each Y8's X6 equals 19. The number of each X6's W8 equals 15 times each Z1's Y8. How many WWW does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Y2's X1 = X1's W8 = 14.\nDefine each Z1's Y8 as u. So u = u = 14.\nDefine each X6's W8 as S. So S = 15 * u = 15 * 14 = 3.\nDefine each X6's WWW as A. So A = S = 3.\nDefine each X1's W8 as i. So i = 14.\nDefine each Y8's X6 as Y. So Y = 19.\nDefine each Y8's WWW as F. So F = Y * A = 19 * 3 = 11.\nDefine each Y2's X1 as r. So r = i = 14.\nDefine each Z1's WWW as l. So l = u * F = 14 * 11 = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 776, "question": "The number of each X7's W2 equals 18 times each X7's W0. The number of each X8's W0 equals 1 more than each X7's W6. The number of each X7's W0 equals 16 times each X3's W0. The number of each X8's W2 equals each X8's W6. The number of each X3's W2 equals each X8's W2. The number of each X3's W6 equals 20 more than each X8's W0. The number of each X3's W0 equals 12. The number of each X8's W6 equals the sum of each X7's W2 and each X3's W0. The number of each X7's W6 equals each X3's W2. How many W6 does each X3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["X3's W0 = 12. X7's W0 as u. So u = 16 * S = 16 * 12 = 8.\nDefine each X7's W2 as S. So S = 18 * u = 18 * 8 = 6.\nDefine each X8's W6 as A. So A = S + u = 6 + 8 = 14.\nDefine each X8's W2 as i. So i = A = 14.\nDefine each X3's W2 as Y. So Y = i = 14.\nDefine each X7's W6 as F. So F = Y = 14.\nDefine each X8's W0 as r. So r = 1 * F = 1 * 14 = 14.\nDefine each X3's W6 as l. So l = 20 * r = 20 * 14 = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 777, "question": "The number of each Y5's X6 equals 19. How many X6 does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Y5's X6 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 778, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y3 equals 16. The number of each Y8's X8 equals 22 times each Z1's Y8. The number of each Z9's Y8 equals 14 times each Z1's Y3. The number of each Z1's Y8 equals 14 more than each Z1's Y3. How many XXX does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Z1's Y3 as u. So u = 16.\nDefine each Z1's Y8 as S. So S = 14 * u = 14 * 16 = 17.\nDefine each Y8's X8 as A. So A = 22 * S = 22 * 17 = 6.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as i. So i = A = 6.\nDefine each Z9's Y8 as Y. So Y = 14 * u = 14 * 16 = 17.\nDefine each Z9's XXX as F. So F = Y * i = 17 * 6 = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 779, "question": "The number of each X1's W9 equals 10 more than each X1's W3. The number of each X1's W3 equals 18. How many W9 does each X1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["X1's W3 as u. So u = 18.\nDefine each X1's W9 as S. So S = 10 * u = 10 * 18 = 19.\nDefine each X1's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 19 + 18 = 14.\nDefine each Y1's l0 as i. So i = 20.\nDefine each Y1's l0 as Y. So Y = 20.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as F. So F = Y + i = 20 + 20 = 17.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as A. So A = Y + i = 20 + 20 = 17.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as i. So i = Y = 20.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as Y. So Y = i + Y = 20 + 20 = 17.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as F. So F = Y + i = 20 + 20 = 17.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as r. So r = Y + i + F = 20 + 20 + 17 = 11.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as l. So l = Y + i + r + F = 20 + 20 + 11 + 17 = 0.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 780, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y2 equals the sum of each Z2's Y9 and each Z5's Y8. The number of each Z2's Y9 equals 8 times each Z8's Y2. The number of each Z8's Y2 equals 6. The number of each Z5's Y8 equals 4 times the sum of each Z8's Y2 and each Z2's Y9. The number of each Z5's Y3 equals the sum of each Z5's Y2 and each Z8's Y2. How many Y3 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["Z8's Y2 as u. So u = 6.\nDefine each Z2's Y9 as S. So S = 8 * u = 8 * 6 = 2.\nDefine each Z5's Y8 as A. So A = 4 * u + S = 4 * 6 + 2 = 1.\nDefine each Z5's Y2 as i. So i = S + A = 2 + 1 = 3.\nDefine each Z5's Y3 as Y. So Y = i + u = 3 + 6 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 781, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y2 equals 9. How many Y2 does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["Z7's Y2 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 782, "question": "The number of each X3's W2 equals 10 times each Z5's WWW. The number of each Y3's X4 equals 4. The number of each X4's W2 equals 22 times each Z3's Y0. The number of each Z7's Y1 equals 9 times each Y0's X3. The number of each Z9's Y0 equals 6 times each Y0's X3. The number of each Z3's Y0 equals 11. The number of each Y0's X3 equals each X3's WWW. The number of each Y1's X3 equals 5 more than the difference of each X3's WWW and each Z9's WWW. The number of each Z5's Y3 equals 15 more than each X4's W2. How many WWW does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["X3's W2 as u. So u = 10 * Z5's WWW = 10 * 15 = 12.\nDefine each Z3's Y0 as S. So S = 11.\nDefine each X4's W2 as A. So A = 22 * S = 22 * 11 = 12.\nDefine each Z5's Y3 as i. So i = 15 * A = 15 * 12 = 19.\nDefine each Y3's X4 as Y. So Y = 4.\nDefine each X3's WWW as F. So F = u = 12.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as r. So r = Y * A = 4 * 12 = 2.\nDefine each Y0's X3 as l. So l = F = 12.\nDefine each Z9's Y0 as V. So V = 6 * l = 6 * 12 = 3.\nDefine each WWW as q. So q = V * l = 3 * 12 = 13.\nDefine each Z9's WWW as z. So z = V * q = 3 * 13 = 16.\nDefine each Y1's X3 as A. So A = 5 * F - Z = 5 * 12 - 16 = 19.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as i. So i = A * F = 19 * 12 = 21.\nDefine each Z7's Y1 as Y. So Y = 9 * l = 9 * 12 = 16.\nDefine each Z7's WWW as F. So F = Y * i = 16 * 21 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 783, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y0 equals 20 more than the difference of each Y0's XXX and each Y0's X1. The number of each Y0's X1 equals 18. The number of each Z3's Y5 equals 9 more than the sum of each Y0's XXX, each Z9's XXX and each Z9's Y0. How many YYY does each Z3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Y0's X1 as u. So u = 18.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as S. So S = u = 18.\nDefine each Z9's Y0 as A. So A = 20 * S - u = 20 * 18 - 18 = 20.\nDefine each Z9's XXX as i. So i = A * S = 20 * 18 = 15.\nDefine each Z3's Y5 as Y. So Y = 9 * (S + i + A) = 9 * (18 + 15 + 20) = 19.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as F. So F = Y = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 784, "question": "The number of each Y7's X8 equals 11. The number of each Y1's X5 equals the sum of each Y7's X8, each Y7's XXX and each Y7's X2. The number of each Y7's X2 equals 21 times each Y7's X8. The number of each Y7's X4 equals 9 times the difference of each Y7's X2 and each Y7's X8. The number of each Y3's X2 equals 12 more than each Y1's X5. How many X2 does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["12 * Y1's X5 = 12 * 15 = 19.\nDefine each Y7's X8 as u. So u = 11.\nDefine each Y7's X2 as S. So S = 21 * u = 21 * 11 = 1.\nDefine each Y7's X4 as A. So A = 9 * S - u = 9 * 1 - 11 = 21.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as i. So i = S + A + u = 1 + 21 + 11 = 10.\nDefine each Y1's X5 as Y. So Y = (u + i + S) = (11 + 10 + 1) = 22.\nDefine each Y3's X2 as F. So F = 12 * Y = 12 * 22 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 785, "question": "The number of each Y1's X2 equals 6. The number of each Y1's X9 equals 10. The number of each Y1's X6 equals each Y1's X2. How many XXX does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["Y1's X2 as u. So u = 6.\nDefine each Y1's X6 as S. So S = u = 6.\nDefine each Y1's X9 as A. So A = 10.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as i. So i = S + A + u = 6 + 10 + 6 = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 786, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y8 equals 0. The number of each Z7's Y8 equals the sum of each Z4's Y1, each Z9's Y8 and each Z7's Y9. The number of each Z7's Y1 equals 2 more than the sum of each Z4's Y8, each Z4's Y1 and each Z7's Y9. The number of each Z7's Y9 equals 15. The number of each Z4's Y8 equals 2 times each Z9's Y8. The number of each Z4's Y1 equals 17 times the difference of each Z9's Y8 and each Z4's Y8. The number of each Z9's Y1 equals the sum of each Z9's Y9, each Z4's Y1, each Z7's YYY and each Z7's Y8. The number of each Z9's Y9 equals each Z7's YYY. How many Y1 does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["9. Z9's Y8. Z4's Y8 = 2 * u = 2 * 9 = 18.\nDefine each Z4's Y1 as u. So u = 17 * u - A = 17 * 18 - 18 = 2.\nDefine each Z7's Y9 as S. So S = 15.\nDefine each Z7's Y8 as A. So A = (u + S + S) = (2 + 15 + 15) = 9.\nDefine each Z7's Y1 as i. So i = 2 * (4 + u + S) = 2 * (9 + 2 + 15) = 19.\nDefine each Z7's YYY as Y. So Y = S + A + i = 15 + 9 + 19 = 20.\nDefine each Z9's Y9 as F. So F = Y = 20.\nDefine each Z9's Y1 as r. So r = (F + u + Y + A) = (20 + 2 + 20 + 9) = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 787, "question": "The number of each Y7's X4 equals 12 more than each X4's W1. The number of each X2's W1 equals 11. The number of each X4's W1 equals 14. The number of each X2's W4 equals the difference of each X4's W1 and each Y7's X4. How many WWW does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["X4's W1 as u. So u = 14.\nDefine each Y7's X4 as S. So S = 12 * u = 12 * 14 = 7.\nDefine each X2's W4 as A. So A = u - S = 14 - 7 = 7.\nDefine each X2's W1 as i. So i = 11.\nDefine each X2's WWW as Y. So Y = i + A = 11 + 7 = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 788, "question": "The number of each Y3's X3 equals each Y7's X7. The number of each Y7's X3 equals each Y3's X3. The number of each Y7's X7 equals 10. How many X3 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Y7's X7 as u. So u = 10.\nDefine each Y3's X3 as S. So S = u = 10.\nDefine each Y7's X3 as A. So A = S = 10.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as i. So i = A + u = 10 + 10 = 20.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as Y. So Y = S = 10.\nDefine each X3's WWW as F. So F = Y = 10.\nDefine each X2's WWW as r. So r = F = 10.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as l. So l = S * F = 10 * 10 = 8.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as V. So V = S = 10.\nDefine each l = 8.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as q. So q = A + u = 10 + 10 = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 789, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y6 equals 4 times the difference of each Z8's Y1 and each Z8's YYY. The number of each Z8's Y1 equals 14 more than each Z8's Y6. The number of each Z8's Y6 equals 8. The number of each Z6's Y1 equals 7 times the difference of each Z8's YYY and each Z9's Y6. How many Y1 does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Z8's Y6 as u. So u = 8.\nDefine each Z8's Y1 as S. So S = 14 * u = 14 * 8 = 20.\nDefine each Z8's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 20 + 8 = 5.\nDefine each Z9's Y6 as i. So i = 4 * S - A = 4 * 20 - 5 = 16.\nDefine each Z6's Y1 as Y. So Y = 7 * A - i = 7 * 5 - 16 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 790, "question": "The number of each X3's W8 equals 21. The number of each Y4's X2 equals the sum of each X3's WWW and each X3's W8. How many X2 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["X3's W8 = 21. X3's WWW = 21. X2's W8 = 21. X2's WWW as i. So i = X2's W8 = 21.\nDefine each Y4's X2 as Y. So Y = X3's W8 + i = 21 + 21 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 791, "question": "The number of each Y3's X9 equals 9 more than each X0's W7. The number of each X0's W7 equals 7. How many XXX does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["X0's W7 as u. So u = 7.\nDefine each Y3's X9 as S. So S = 9 * u = 9 * 7 = 17.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as A. So A = S = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 792, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y4 equals each Y9's X3. The number of each Z5's Y8 equals each Y9's X0. The number of each Y9's X3 equals the sum of each Y9's X0 and each Y9's X9. The number of each Y9's X9 equals 19 more than each Z5's Y8. The number of each Y9's X0 equals 6. How many Y4 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["Y9's X0 as u. So u = 6.\nDefine each Z5's Y8 as S. So S = u = 6.\nDefine each Y9's X9 as A. So A = 19 * S = 19 * 6 = 22.\nDefine each Y9's X3 as i. So i = u + A = 6 + 22 = 5.\nDefine each Z5's Y4 as Y. So Y = i = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 793, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y5 equals 5 more than each Z9's Y8. The number of each Z9's Y8 equals 8. How many Y5 does each Z3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["Z9's Y8 as u. So u = 8.\nDefine each Z3's Y5 as S. So S = 5 * u = 5 * 8 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 794, "question": "The number of each Y5's X0 equals each Y2's WWW. The number of each Y5's X1 equals the sum of each Y5's X0, each Y2's XXX and each Y2's X0. The number of each Y2's X0 equals each X1's W7. The number of each X0's W7 equals each Y2's XXX. The number of each X1's W7 equals 10. The number of each X1's W3 equals 6 more than the sum of each Y5's X0, each X0's WWW and each Y5's XXX. How many W3 does each X1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["X1's W7 as u. So u = 10.\nDefine each Y2's X0 as S. So S = u = 10.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as A. So A = S = 10.\nDefine each X0's W7 as i. So i = A = 10.\nDefine each X0's WWW as Y. So Y = i = 10.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as F. So F = S * Y = 10 * 10 = 8.\nDefine each Y5's X0 as r. So r = F = 8.\nDefine each Y5's X1 as l. So l = (r + A + S) = (8 + 10 + 10) = 5.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as V. So V = l + r = 5 + 8 = 13.\nDefine each X1's W3 as q. So q = 6 * (r + Y + V) = 6 * (8 + 10 + 13) = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 795, "question": "The number of each X8's W1 equals 2. The number of each Z2's Y8 equals 9 times the sum of each X8's W1 and each Y8's X8. The number of each Z6's Y2 equals the difference of each Z2's Y8 and each X8's W1. The number of each Y8's X8 equals each X8's W1. How many Y2 does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["X8's W1 = 2.\nDefine each Y8's X8 as u. So u = X8's W1 = 2.\nDefine each Z2's Y8 as S. So S = 9 * X8's W1 + u = 9 * 2 + 2 = 20.\nDefine each Z6's Y2 as A. So A = S - X8's W1 = 20 - 2 = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 796, "question": "The number of each Y3's X1 equals 17. The number of each Y5's X2 equals 20 times each X1's W2. The number of each X2's W2 equals the difference of each Y3's X1 and each Y5's X2. The number of each X1's W2 equals 8 more than each Y3's X1. How many WWW does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y3's X1 = 17. X1's W2 = 8 * Y3's X1 = 8 * 17 = 21.\nDefine each Y5's X2 as u. So u = 20 * X1's W2 = 20 * 21 = 6.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as S. So S = Y3's X1 = 17.\nDefine each X2's W2 as A. So A = Y3's X1 - u = 17 - 6 = 11.\nDefine each X2's WWW as i. So i = A = 11.\nDefine each Y5's WWW as Y. So Y = u * i = 6 * 11 = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 797, "question": "The number of each Y0's X2 equals 15. The number of each Y0's X0 equals each Y0's X2. How many XXX does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["Y0's X2 as u. So u = 15.\nDefine each Y0's X0 as S. So S = u = 15.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 15 + 15 = 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 798, "question": "The number of each X8's W6 equals each X1's W1. The number of each X1's W8 equals the sum of each Y3's X0 and each Y2's X1. The number of each X1's W1 equals 1. The number of each X8's W8 equals each Y2's X1. The number of each X8's W1 equals each Y3's XXX. The number of each Y2's X1 equals 22. The number of each Y2's X0 equals 19 times each Y2's X1. The number of each Y3's X0 equals each Y2's XXX. The number of each Y3's X1 equals 14 more than the difference of each X1's WWW and each Y2's XXX. How many WWW does each X8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["Y2's X1 as u. So u = 22.\nDefine each Y2's X0 as S. So S = 19 * u = 19 * 22 = 4.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 4 + 22 = 3.\nDefine each Y3's X0 as i. So i = A = 3.\nDefine each X1's W8 as Y. So Y = i + u = 3 + 22 = 2.\nDefine each X1's W1 as F. So F = 1.\nDefine each X1's WWW as r. So r = Y + F = 2 + 1 = 3.\nDefine each Y3's X1 as l. So l = 14 * r - A = 14 * 3 - 3 = 15.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as V. So V = l + i = 15 + 3 = 18.\nDefine each X8's W1 as q. So q = V = 18.\nDefine each X8's W8 as z. So z = u = 22.\nDefine each X8's W6 as A. So A = F = 1.\nDefine each X8's WWW as i. So i = A + q + Z = 1 + 18 + 22 = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 799, "question": "The number of each Y3's X9 equals 8. The number of each X9's W4 equals 18 times each Y3's X9. How many WWW does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Y3's X9 as u. So u = 8.\nDefine each X9's W4 as S. So S = 18 * u = 18 * 8 = 6.\nDefine each X9's WWW as A. So A = S = 6.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as i. So i = u * A = 8 * 6 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 800, "question": "The number of each Y3's X4 equals 16. The number of each Z9's Y3 equals 1 times each Y3's X4. How many XXX does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["Y3's X4 as u. So u = 16.\nDefine each Z9's Y3 as S. So S = 1 * u = 1 * 16 = 16.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as A. So A = u = 16.\nDefine each Z9's XXX as i. So i = S * A = 16 * 16 = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 801, "question": "The number of each Y8's X1 equals 3. The number of each Y8's X7 equals 5 more than each Y8's X1. How many X7 does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["Y8's X1 as u. So u = 3.\nDefine each Y8's X7 as S. So S = 5 * u = 5 * 3 = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 802, "question": "The number of each X0's W8 equals 21. The number of each X1's W7 equals 21 times the difference of each X0's W6 and each X0's WWW. The number of each X0's W6 equals each X0's W8. The number of each X2's W3 equals 22. The number of each X0's W7 equals 20 more than each X2's W3. The number of each X1's W8 equals 1 more than each X0's WWW. How many WWW does each X1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["X2's W3 = 22. X0's W7 as u. So u = 20 * X2's W3 = 20 * 22 = 3.\nDefine each X0's W8 as S. So S = 21.\nDefine each X0's W6 as A. So A = S = 21.\nDefine each X0's WWW as i. So i = S + A + u = 21 + 21 + 3 = 22.\nDefine each X1's W8 as Y. So Y = 1 * i = 1 * 22 = 22.\nDefine each X1's W7 as F. So F = 21 * A - i = 21 * 21 - 22 = 1.\nDefine each X1's WWW as r. So r = Y + F = 22 + 1 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 803, "question": "The number of each X7's W3 equals 13. How many W3 does each X7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["X7's W3 = 13. So 13 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 804, "question": "The number of each Y3's X8 equals 1 times the sum of each Y7's X0, each Z3's WWW and each Y2's X8. The number of each Y7's X6 equals 7. The number of each Z3's Y2 equals each Y2's XXX. The number of each Y2's X8 equals 20 times the difference of each Y7's X6 and each Y7's XXX. The number of each X8's W8 equals the sum of each Z3's Y2, each Y7's X6, each Y2's X8 and each Z3's XXX. The number of each Y7's X0 equals 3. How many XXX does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Y7's X6 as u. So u = 7.\nDefine each Y7's X0 as S. So S = 3.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 3 + 7 = 10.\nDefine each Y2's X8 as i. So i = 20 * u - A = 20 * 7 - 10 = 15.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as Y. So Y = i = 15.\nDefine each Z3's Y2 as F. So F = Y = 15.\nDefine each Z3's XXX as r. So r = F * Y = 15 * 15 = 18.\nDefine each X8's W8 as l. So l = (F + u + i + r) = (15 + 7 + 15 + 18) = 9.\nDefine each X8's WWW as V. So V = l = 9.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as q. So q = i * V = 15 * 9 = 20.\nDefine each Z3's WWW as z. So z = F * q = 15 * 20 = 1.\nDefine each Y3's X8 as A. So A = 1 * (S + Z + i) = 1 * (3 + 1 + 15) = 19.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as i. So i = A = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 805, "question": "The number of each Y4's X7 equals the difference of each Y3's X7 and each Y3's XXX. The number of each Y3's X7 equals 3. The number of each Y4's X8 equals 18 more than each Y4's X7. The number of each X8's W6 equals each Y3's WWW. The number of each X7's W6 equals 7 more than each Y4's XXX. How many WWW does each X8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Y3's X7 as u. So u = 3.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as S. So S = u = 3.\nDefine each Y4's X7 as A. So A = u - S = 3 - 3 = 0.\nDefine each Y4's X8 as i. So i = 18 * A = 18 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as Y. So Y = i + A = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each X7's W6 as F. So F = 7 * Y = 7 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X7's WWW as r. So r = F = 0.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as l. So l = u * r = 3 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X8's W6 as V. So V = l = 0.\nDefine each X8's WWW as q. So q = V = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 806, "question": "The number of each Y6's X0 equals 2. The number of each Z7's Y6 equals each Z9's YYY. The number of each Z9's Y9 equals the sum of each Y6's X0 and each Y9's XXX. The number of each Z7's Y2 equals the difference of each Z9's XXX and each Y6's X0. The number of each Z2's Y6 equals 3 more than each Y6's XXX. The number of each Y9's X0 equals 20 times the difference of each Z2's Y6 and each Y6's X0. The number of each Y9's X9 equals 14 more than each Z2's XXX. The number of each Z7's Y9 equals the sum of each Z7's Y2, each Z9's XXX and each Z7's Y6. The number of each Z9's Y6 equals 20 times each Y6's XXX. The number of each Y6's X6 equals 20. How many YYY does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Y6's X6 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each Y6's X0 as S. So S = 2.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 2 + 20 = 22.\nDefine each Z2's Y6 as i. So i = 3 * A = 3 * 22 = 20.\nDefine each Z2's XXX as Y. So Y = i * A = 20 * 22 = 3.\nDefine each Y9's X9 as F. So F = 14 * Y = 14 * 3 = 19.\nDefine each Y9's X0 as r. So r = 20 * i - S = 20 * 20 - 2 = 1.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as l. So l = r + F = 1 + 19 = 20.\nDefine each Z9's Y9 as V. So V = S + l = 2 + 20 = 22.\nDefine each Z9's Y6 as q. So q = 20 * A = 20 * 22 = 3.\nDefine each Z9's YYY as z. So z = q + V = 3 + 22 = 2.\nDefine each Z7's Y6 as A. So A = S = 2.\nDefine each Z7's Y2 as i. So i = l - S = 20 - 2 = 18.\nDefine each Z7's Y9 as Y. So Y = (i + Z + A) = (18 + 2 + 2) = 22.\nDefine each Z7's YYY as F. So F = Y + A + i = 22 + 2 + 18 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 807, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y6 equals 14 more than each Z2's Y6. The number of each Z2's Y6 equals 19. The number of each Z5's Y4 equals 15 times each Z5's Y6. How many Y4 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["Z2's Y6 as u. So u = 19.\nDefine each Z5's Y6 as S. So S = 14 * u = 14 * 19 = 13.\nDefine each Z5's Y4 as A. So A = 15 * S = 15 * 13 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 808, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y5 equals 2 more than each Z1's YYY. The number of each Z1's Y6 equals 4. The number of each Z0's Y3 equals 18 times each Z0's Y5. The number of each Z0's Y6 equals the sum of each Z0's Y3, each Z1's Y6 and each Z0's Y5. The number of each Z1's Y5 equals 21 times each Z1's Y6. How many YYY does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Z1's Y6 as u. So u = 4.\nDefine each Z1's Y5 as S. So S = 21 * u = 21 * 4 = 15.\nDefine each Z1's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 15 + 4 = 19.\nDefine each Z0's Y5 as i. So i = 2 * A = 2 * 19 = 15.\nDefine each Z0's Y3 as Y. So Y = 18 * i = 18 * 15 = 17.\nDefine each Z0's Y6 as F. So F = (Y + u + i) = (17 + 4 + 15) = 13.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as r. So r = F + Y + i = 13 + 17 + 15 = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 809, "question": "The number of each Z4's Y3 equals the sum of each Y3's WWW and each Y2's WWW. The number of each Z5's Y5 equals the difference of each Z4's WWW and each Y2's X5. The number of each Y3's X0 equals 7 more than each X0's WWW. The number of each X0's W8 equals each Y2's WWW. The number of each Y2's X5 equals 20 more than each X5's WWW. The number of each X5's W3 equals 17. How many Y5 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["X5's W3 = 17. X5's WWW = 17. X0's W8 as u. So u = Y2's X5 = 20.\nDefine each Y2's X5 as S. So S = 20 * X5's W3 = 20 * 17 = 18.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as A. So A = S * X5's WWW = 18 * 17 = 7.\nDefine each X0's W8 as i. So i = A = 7.\nDefine each X0's WWW as Y. So Y = i = 7.\nDefine each Y3's X0 as F. So F = 7 * Y = 7 * 7 = 3.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as r. So r = F * Y = 3 * 7 = 21.\nDefine each Z4's Y3 as l. So l = r + A = 21 + 7 = 5.\nDefine each Z4's WWW as V. So V = l * r = 5 * 21 = 13.\nDefine each Z5's Y5 as q. So q = V - S = 13 - 18 = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 810, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y5 equals 18 times the sum of each X0's W7, each X8's W7 and each Y7's X2. The number of each Y7's X2 equals each Z2's WWW. The number of each Y5's X0 equals 5. The number of each Z2's Y3 equals 16 more than the difference of each Y3's WWW and each Y5's X0. The number of each X8's W7 equals 22 times the sum of each X0's W7, each Y5's X0 and each X2's W4. The number of each X2's W4 equals 19 more than each Y5's X0. The number of each X0's W7 equals 2 times the sum of each Y5's X0 and each X2's W4. The number of each Y3's X0 equals 7 more than the difference of each X2's W4 and each X8's W7. How many Y5 does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 811, "question": "The number of each Y6's X4 equals 20 more than each X4's W5. The number of each Y7's X9 equals 5 more than the difference of each X4's W5 and each Y6's X4. The number of each X9's W5 equals 20 more than each Y7's X9. The number of each X4's W5 equals 21. The number of each Z2's Y0 equals the sum of each X4's W5, each X9's WWW and each X9's W5. The number of each X7's W1 equals the sum of each Z6's WWW and each Z2's WWW. The number of each Y0's X9 equals each X9's WWW. The number of each Z8's Y0 equals the difference of each Y0's X9 and each Z2's WWW. The number of each Z6's Y0 equals 0 times the difference of each Y6's X4 and each Z8's WWW. How many W1 does each X7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["X4's W5 as u. So u = 21.\nDefine each Y6's X4 as S. So S = 20 * u = 20 * 21 = 6.\nDefine each Y7's X9 as A. So A = 5 * u - S = 5 * 21 - 6 = 11.\nDefine each X9's W5 as i. So i = 20 * A = 20 * 11 = 13.\nDefine each X9's WWW as Y. So Y = i = 13.\nDefine each Y0's X9 as F. So F = Y = 13.\nDefine each Y0's WWW as r. So r = F * Y = 13 * 13 = 8.\nDefine each Z2's Y0 as l. So l = (u + Y + i) = (21 + 13 + 13) = 1.\nDefine each Z2's WWW as V. So V = l * r = 1 * 8 = 8.\nDefine each Z8's Y0 as q. So q = F - V = 13 - 8 = 5.\nDefine each Z8's WWW as z. So z = q * r = 5 * 8 = 17.\nDefine each Z6's Y0 as A. So A = 0 * S - Z = 0 * 6 - 17 = 6.\nDefine each Z6's WWW as i. So i = A * r = 6 * 8 = 2.\nDefine each X7's W1 as Y. So Y = i + V = 2 + 8 = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 812, "question": "The number of each X4's W0 equals 8 more than the difference of each X3's W3 and each X9's W4. The number of each X3's W4 equals the sum of each X4's W0 and each X3's W3. The number of each X3's W3 equals 12. The number of each X9's W4 equals 18 times each X3's W3. How many W4 does each X3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["X3's W3 as u. So u = 12.\nDefine each X9's W4 as S. So S = 18 * u = 18 * 12 = 9.\nDefine each X4's W0 as A. So A = 8 * u - S = 8 * 12 - 9 = 19.\nDefine each X3's W4 as i. So i = A + u = 19 + 12 = 8.\nThus, the answer is 8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 813, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y2 equals 2 more than the sum of each Y2's X7, each X7's W0 and each X5's W1. The number of each Z2's Y2 equals the sum of each Z8's XXX and each Y2's XXX. The number of each Y9's X5 equals 16 times the sum of each Z2's Y2 and each Y2's XXX. The number of each X5's W1 equals 8 more than each X7's W0. The number of each X7's W0 equals 14. The number of each Y2's X7 equals 21 times the sum of each X5's W1 and each X7's W0. How many X5 does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["X7's W0 = 14. X5's W1 = 8 * r = 8 * 14 = 20.\nDefine each X7's W0 as u. So u = 14.\nDefine each X5's W1 as S. So S = 8 * u = 8 * 14 = 20.\nDefine each Y2's X7 as A. So A = 21 * S + u = 21 * 20 + 14 = 18.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as i. So i = A = 18.\nDefine each Z8's Y2 as Y. So Y = 2 * (A + u + S) = 2 * (18 + 14 + 20) = 19.\nDefine each Z8's XXX as F. So F = Y * i = 19 * 18 = 20.\nDefine each Z2's Y2 as r. So r = F + i = 20 + 18 = 15.\nDefine each Y9's X5 as l. So l = 16 * r + i = 16 * 15 + 18 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 814, "question": "The number of each Y1's X7 equals 4. The number of each Y7's X7 equals 11 times each Y1's XXX. The number of each Y7's X1 equals 1 times each Y1's XXX. The number of each Y1's X1 equals 20 more than each Y1's X7. How many XXX does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Y1's X7 as u. So u = 4.\nDefine each Y1's X1 as S. So S = 20 * u = 20 * 4 = 11.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 11 + 4 = 15.\nDefine each Y7's X1 as i. So i = 1 * A = 1 * 15 = 15.\nDefine each Y7's X7 as Y. So Y = 11 * A = 11 * 15 = 4.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as F. So F = Y + i = 4 + 15 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 815, "question": "The number of each Y8's X0 equals 8. The number of each Y6's X0 equals each Z3's XXX. The number of each Z3's Y8 equals 12 more than each Y8's XXX. How many X0 does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["Y8's X0 = 8. Y8's XXX = 8. Y8's XXX = 8. Y6's XXX = 3. Z3's Y8 = 12 * Y8's X0 = 12 * 8 = 4.\nDefine each Z3's XXX as u. So u = Z3's XXX Y8 * Y8's XXX = 4 * 8 = 9.\nDefine each Y6's X0 as S. So S = u = 9.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as A. So A = S = 9.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as i. So i = Y8's X0 = 8.\nDefine each Z3's XXX as Y. So Y = Z3's XXX Y8 * i = 4 * 8 = 9.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as F. So F = S = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 816, "question": "The number of each X9's W1 equals 16 times the difference of each X9's W3 and each X9's W0. The number of each X9's W3 equals 8. The number of each X9's W0 equals each X9's W3. How many WWW does each X9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["X9's W3 as u. So u = 8.\nDefine each X9's W0 as S. So S = u = 8.\nDefine each X9's W1 as A. So A = 16 * u - S = 16 * 8 - 8 = 13.\nDefine each X9's WWW as i. So i = S + A + u = 8 + 13 + 8 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 817, "question": "The number of each Y1's X2 equals 2. The number of each Z4's Y1 equals 14 times each Y8's X2. The number of each Y1's X0 equals 15 more than each Z9's Y8. The number of each Y8's X2 equals 0 times each Y1's X0. The number of each Z9's Y8 equals 9 times each Y1's X2. How many Y1 does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y1's X2 as u. So u = 2.\nDefine each Z9's Y8 as S. So S = 9 * u = 9 * 2 = 18.\nDefine each Y1's X0 as A. So A = 15 * S = 15 * 18 = 17.\nDefine each Y8's X2 as i. So i = 0 * A = 0 * 17 = 0.\nDefine each Z4's Y1 as Y. So Y = 14 + i = 14 + 0 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 818, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y7 equals 17 more than each Z6's YYY. The number of each Z6's Y7 equals 16 times each Z7's Y7. The number of each Z7's Y5 equals 7. The number of each Z7's Y7 equals 17 times each Z7's Y5. The number of each Z9's Y9 equals 14 times each Z5's Y7. How many Y9 does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["Z7's Y5 = 7. Z7's Y7 = 17 * Z7's Y5 = 17.\nDefine each Z6's Y7 as u. So u = 16 * Z7's Y7 = 16 * 17 = 19.\nDefine each Z6's YYY as S. So S = u = 19.\nDefine each Z5's Y7 as A. So A = 17 * S = 17 * 19 = 1.\nDefine each Z9's Y9 as i. So i = 14 * A = 14 * 1 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 819, "question": "The number of each X0's W9 equals 11 times each X6's W3. The number of each X0's W3 equals 1 times each X8's W9. The number of each X8's W7 equals 1 times each X6's W7. The number of each X6's W3 equals the sum of each X8's W3 and each X6's W9. The number of each X0's W7 equals the difference of each X0's W9 and each X6's W9. The number of each X6's W7 equals 7. The number of each X8's W3 equals 13 times the sum of each X0's W3 and each X8's W9. The number of each X6's W9 equals the sum of each X8's W3, each X0's W3 and each X8's W9. The number of each X8's W9 equals 12 times each X8's W7. How many W7 does each X0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 820, "question": "The number of each Y7's X8 equals each Y1's X4. The number of each Y1's X4 equals 5. How many X8 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Y1's X4 as u. So u = 5.\nDefine each Y7's X8 as S. So S = u = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 821, "question": "The number of each X0's W2 equals 4 more than the difference of each Z2's WWW and each Y3's WWW. The number of each Z8's Y8 equals 0. The number of each X7's W2 equals 5 more than each Z8's Y8. The number of each Z0's Y3 equals 7 times each X0's W2. The number of each Z2's Y3 equals the difference of each Z8's Y8 and each X7's W2. The number of each Y3's X7 equals the sum of each Z2's Y3, each X7's W2 and each X7's WWW. The number of each Z7's Y3 equals 17 times the difference of each Y8's X7 and each Z8's Y8. The number of each Y8's X7 equals 1 times each Z0's Y3. How many WWW does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["8. Z8's Y8 = 0. X7's W2 as u. So u = 5 * Z8's Y8 = 5 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z2's Y3 as S. So S = u - u = 0 - 0 = 0.\nDefine each X7's WWW as A. So A = u = 0.\nDefine each Y3's X7 as i. So i = (S + u + A) = (0 + 0 + 0) = 0.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as Y. So Y = i * A = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z2's WWW as F. So F = S * Y = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X0's W2 as r. So r = 4 * F - Y = 4 * 0 - 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z0's Y3 as l. So l = 7 * r = 7 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y8's X7 as V. So V = 1 * l = 1 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z7's Y3 as q. So q = 17 * V - u = 17 * 0 - 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z7's WWW as z. So z = q * Y = 0 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 822, "question": "The number of each Y5's X6 equals 4. The number of each X6's W1 equals 2 more than each Y5's X6. How many W1 does each X6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Y5's X6 = 4. X6's W1 = 2 * Y5's X6 = 2 * 4 = 8.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as u. So u = Y5's X6 = 4.\nDefine each X6's WWW as S. So S = X6's W1 = 8.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as A. So A = Y5's X6 = 4.\nDefine each X3's WWW as i. So i = X3's WWW = 3.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as Y. So Y = u = 4.\nDefine each X3's WWW as F. So F = i = 3.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as r. So r = Y + u + A = 4 + 4 + 4 = 12.\nDefine each X6's WWW as l. So l = S = 8.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as V. So V = Y + u + A = 12 + 4 + 4 = 20.\nDefine each X3's WWW as q. So q = i = 3.\nDefine each Y5's X6 as z. So z = 4.\nDefine each X6's W1 as A. So A = 2 * S = 2 * 8 = 16.\nDefine each X6's WWW as i. So i = A = 16.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as Y. So Y = Y + u + A = 20 + 4 + 16 = 17.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as F. So F = Y + u + A = 17 + 4 + 16 = 14.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as r. So r = Y + u + F = 17 + 4 + 14 = 12.\nDefine each X3's WWW as l. So l = i = 13.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as V. So V = Y + u + A = 17 + 4 + 16 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 823, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y4 equals 3 more than the sum of each Z9's Y5 and each X0's W1. The number of each X0's W4 equals the difference of each X7's WWW and each X7's W4. The number of each X7's W1 equals each X7's W4. The number of each X0's W1 equals each X7's W1. The number of each Z9's Y5 equals 17 more than each X0's WWW. The number of each X7's W4 equals 22. How many Y4 does each Z3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["X7's W4 as u. So u = 22.\nDefine each X7's W1 as S. So S = u = 22.\nDefine each X7's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 22 + 22 = 21.\nDefine each X0's W4 as i. So i = A - u = 21 - 22 = 22.\nDefine each X0's W1 as Y. So Y = S = 22.\nDefine each X0's WWW as F. So F = Y + i = 22 + 22 = 21.\nDefine each Z9's Y5 as r. So r = 17 * F = 17 * 21 = 12.\nDefine each Z3's Y4 as l. So l = 3 * r + Y = 3 * 12 + 22 = 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 824, "question": "The number of each X8's W3 equals 10. The number of each Y3's X2 equals 21 more than the difference of each X2's WWW and each X2's W0. The number of each X2's W0 equals 0 times each X8's W3. How many WWW does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["X8's W3 = 10. X2's W0 = 0 * X8's W3 = 0 * 10 = 0.\nDefine each X2's WWW as u. So u = X8's W3 = 10.\nDefine each Y3's X2 as S. So S = 21 * u - u = 21 * 10 - 10 = 16.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as A. So A = S * u = 16 * 10 = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 825, "question": "The number of each X8's W5 equals 9. The number of each Y2's X8 equals 21. The number of each X0's W2 equals 6 times each Y9's X9. The number of each Y9's X9 equals 22. The number of each Y0's X8 equals the difference of each Y2's WWW and each Y2's X8. The number of each X0's W5 equals each X8's W5. The number of each Z5's Y0 equals 4 times each Y2's X0. The number of each Y2's X0 equals each Y9's X9. How many WWW does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["Y9's X9 as u. So u = 22.\nDefine each X0's W2 as S. So S = 6 * u = 6 * 22 = 17.\nDefine each X8's W5 as A. So A = 9.\nDefine each X0's W5 as i. So i = A = 9.\nDefine each X0's WWW as Y. So Y = S + i = 17 + 9 = 3.\nDefine each Y2's X8 as F. So F = 21.\nDefine each Y2's X0 as r. So r = u = 22.\nDefine each X8's WWW as l. So l = A = 9.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as V. So V = r * Y + F * l = 22 * 3 + 21 * 9 = 19.\nDefine each Y0's X8 as q. So q = V - F = 19 - 21 = 21.\nDefine each Z5's Y0 as z. So z = 4 * r = 4 * 22 = 19.\nDefine each Y0's WWW as A. So A = q * l = 21 * 9 = 5.\nDefine each Z5's WWW as i. So i = z * A = 19 * 5 = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 826, "question": "The number of each X3's W1 equals 5 times the sum of each X3's W6, each X6's W4 and each X0's W1. The number of each X3's W6 equals 7 times the difference of each X6's W6 and each X0's W1. The number of each X6's W6 equals 19 more than each X0's W6. The number of each X6's W1 equals 13 more than the difference of each X0's W1 and each X3's W6. The number of each X0's W6 equals each X0's W1. The number of each X6's W4 equals 22 times the difference of each X0's W1 and each X6's W1. The number of each X0's W1 equals 15. The number of each X0's W4 equals 22 more than the sum of each X0's W1 and each X3's W1. How many W4 does each X0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["X0's W1. So the X0's W6 = u = 15.\nDefine each X6's W6 as S. So S = 19 * u = 19 * 15 = 9.\nDefine each X3's W6 as A. So A = 7 * S - u = 7 * 9 - 15 = 19.\nDefine each X6's W1 as i. So i = 13 + u - A = 13 + 15 - 19 = 9.\nDefine each X6's W4 as Y. So Y = 22 * u - i = 22 * 15 - 9 = 18.\nDefine each X3's W1 as F. So F = 5 * (A + Y + u) = 5 * (19 + 18 + 15) = 19.\nDefine each X0's W4 as r. So r = 22 * u + F = 22 * 15 + 19 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 827, "question": "The number of each X4's W2 equals 18. The number of each X2's W2 equals 2 times each X4's WWW. How many WWW does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["X4's W2 as u. So u = 18.\nDefine each X4's WWW as S. So S = u = 18.\nDefine each X2's W2 as A. So A = 2 * S = 2 * 18 = 13.\nDefine each X2's WWW as i. So i = A = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 828, "question": "The number of each Y4's X3 equals 9 times each X3's W2. The number of each Y1's X8 equals each Y4's X8. The number of each Y4's X8 equals 0. The number of each X3's W2 equals 21 times each Y1's X8. How many X3 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y4's X8 as u. So u = 0.\nDefine each Y1's X8 as S. So S = u = 0.\nDefine each X3's W2 as A. So A = 21 * S = 21 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y4's X3 as i. So i = 9 * A = 9 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as Y. So Y = u + i = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each X3's WWW as F. So F = A = 0.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as r. So r = u + i = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each X8's WWW as l. So l = S * l = 0 * 1 = 0.\nDefine each Y4's WWW as V. So V = u * l + i * F = 0 * 0 + 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y4's WWW as q. So q = u * V = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 0.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 829, "question": "The number of each Y2's X5 equals the difference of each Y8's X1 and each Y3's X2. The number of each Y7's X2 equals the sum of each Y2's X5 and each Y2's XXX. The number of each Y8's X5 equals each Y7's X2. The number of each Y3's X2 equals each Y8's X1. The number of each Y2's X2 equals 14 times each Y2's X1. The number of each Y2's X1 equals 3. The number of each Y8's X1 equals 21 times each Y3's X4. The number of each Y3's X4 equals 9. How many X5 does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["Y3's X4 as u. So u = 9.\nDefine each Y8's X1 as S. So S = 21 * u = 21 * 9 = 5.\nDefine each Y3's X2 as A. So A = S = 5.\nDefine each Y2's X5 as i. So i = S - A = 5 - 5 = 0.\nDefine each Y2's X1 as Y. So Y = 3.\nDefine each Y2's X2 as F. So F = 14 * Y = 14 * 3 = 19.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as r. So r = Y + F + i = 3 + 19 + 0 = 22.\nDefine each Y7's X2 as l. So l = i + r = 0 + 22 = 22.\nDefine each Y8's X5 as V. So V = l = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 830, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y6 equals 1 more than each Z4's Y8. The number of each Z3's Y8 equals 0 times each Z4's Y8. The number of each Z3's Y3 equals each Z4's Y8. The number of each Z4's Y8 equals 1 times each Z9's Y6. The number of each Z7's Y0 equals 18. The number of each Z7's Y3 equals the sum of each Z9's Y6 and each Z3's YYY. The number of each Z9's Y6 equals 8 more than each Z7's Y0. How many Y3 does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Z7's Y0 = 18.\nDefine each Z9's Y6 as u. So u = 8 * S7 = 8 * 18 = 6.\nDefine each Z4's Y8 as S. So S = 1 * u = 1 * 6 = 6.\nDefine each Z3's Y6 as A. So A = 1 * S = 1 * 6 = 6.\nDefine each Z3's Y3 as i. So i = S = 6.\nDefine each Z3's Y8 as Y. So Y = 0 * S = 0 * 6 = 0.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as F. So F = Y + i + A = 0 + 6 + 6 = 12.\nDefine each Z7's Y3 as r. So r = u + F = 6 + 12 = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 831, "question": "The number of each X3's W1 equals 7. How many W1 does each X3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["X3's W1 = 7. So 7.\nDefine each X3's WWW as u. So u = X3 = 7.\nDefine each Y1's l0 as S. So S = 21.\nDefine each Y1's lWW as A. So A = S * u = 21 * 7 = 9.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y1's l0 as i. So i = 21.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as Y. So Y = S + i = 21 + 21 = 19.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each X3's W1 as l. So l = 7.\nDefine each X3's WWW as V. So V = l + u = 7 + 7 = 14.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as q. So q = S * V + i * u = 21 * 14 + 21 * 7 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 832, "question": "The number of each Y2's X2 equals 12 times each Y2's X3. The number of each Y2's X3 equals 16. How many XXX does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Y2's X3 as u. So u = 16.\nDefine each Y2's X2 as S. So S = 12 * u = 12 * 16 = 8.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as A. So A = S + u + u = 8 + 16 + 16 = 17.\nDefine each X3's WWW as i. So i = u = 16.\nDefine each X3's WWW as Y. So Y = i = 16.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as F. So F = S + u + u = 8 + 16 + 16 = 17.\nDefine each X2's WWW as r. So r = S * Y = 8 * 16 = 13.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as l. So l = S * r + u * Y = 8 * 13 + 16 * 16 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 833, "question": "The number of each X7's W0 equals 16 more than the sum of each X3's WWW and each X3's W0. The number of each X7's W5 equals 14 more than the sum of each X7's W0 and each X3's W0. The number of each X3's W0 equals 21. The number of each X7's W2 equals 15 more than each X3's WWW. How many WWW does each X7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["X3's W0 as u. So u = 21.\nDefine each X3's WWW as S. So S = u = 21.\nDefine each X7's W2 as A. So A = 15 * S = 15 * 21 = 16.\nDefine each X7's W0 as i. So i = 16 * S + u = 16 * 21 + 21 = 12.\nDefine each X7's W5 as Y. So Y = 14 + i + u = 14 + 12 + 21 = 1.\nDefine each X7's WWW as F. So F = Y + A + i = 1 + 16 + 12 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 834, "question": "The number of each Y5's X0 equals the sum of each Y9's X5 and each Y5's X2. The number of each Y1's X5 equals the difference of each Y5's XXX and each Y1's X2. The number of each Y9's X2 equals each Y1's X5. The number of each Y1's X0 equals the sum of each Y5's X2, each Y9's X0, each Y5's X0 and each Y9's X2. The number of each Y1's X2 equals 1 times each Y9's X5. The number of each Y5's X2 equals each Y1's X2. The number of each Y5's X5 equals 4 more than the sum of each Y5's X2 and each Y1's X2. The number of each Y9's X0 equals 14 more than each Y9's X2. The number of each Y9's X5 equals 19. How many X0 does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["19. Y9's X5 as u. So u = 19.\nDefine each Y1's X2 as S. So S = 1 * u = 1 * 19 = 19.\nDefine each Y5's X2 as A. So A = S = 19.\nDefine each Y5's X5 as i. So i = 4 * A + S = 4 * 19 + 19 = 7.\nDefine each Y5's X0 as Y. So Y = u + A = 19 + 19 = 15.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as F. So F = Y + A + i = 15 + 19 + 7 = 18.\nDefine each Y1's X5 as r. So r = F - S = 18 - 19 = 22.\nDefine each Y9's X2 as l. So l = r = 22.\nDefine each Y9's X0 as V. So V = 14 * l = 14 * 22 = 9.\nDefine each Y1's X0 as q. So q = (A + V + Y + l) = (19 + 9 + 15 + 22) = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 835, "question": "The number of each X8's W7 equals 5 times each X6's W2. The number of each X6's W2 equals 7. How many W7 does each X8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["X6's W2 = 7. X8's W7 = 5 * X6's W2 = 5 * 7 = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 836, "question": "The number of each X4's W0 equals 15. The number of each X8's W0 equals 9 more than each X4's W5. The number of each X4's W5 equals 14 times each X4's W0. How many W0 does each X8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["X4's W0 = 15. X4's W5 = 14 * X4 = 14.\nDefine each X8's W0 as u. So u = 9 * X4's W5 = 9 * 14 = 11.\nDefine each X4's WWW as S. So S = X4's W0 + X4's W5 = 15 + 14 = 6.\nDefine each Y1's X0 as A. So A = 23.\nDefine each Y1's X0 as i. So i = 23.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as Y. So Y = i + A = 23 + 23 = 13.\nDefine each X3's W0 as F. So F = 2.\nDefine each X3's WWW as r. So r = F = 2.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as l. So l = i = 23.\nDefine each X8's WWW as V. So V = u = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 837, "question": "The number of each X8's W1 equals 2. The number of each Y3's X0 equals 20 times each X8's W1. The number of each Z4's Y3 equals the sum of each X8's W1, each X0's W0 and each X8's WWW. The number of each Y6's X8 equals 9 more than each Y3's XXX. The number of each X8's W0 equals each X8's W1. The number of each Y6's X1 equals the difference of each Z4's Y3 and each X0's W0. The number of each Y3's X1 equals each X8's W1. The number of each Y3's X8 equals 13 times each X8's W1. The number of each X0's W0 equals each X8's WWW. How many XXX does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["X8's W1 as u. So u = 2.\nDefine each X8's W0 as S. So S = u = 2.\nDefine each X8's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 2 + 2 = 4.\nDefine each X0's W0 as i. So i = A = 4.\nDefine each Z4's Y3 as Y. So Y = (u + i + A) = (2 + 4 + 4) = 10.\nDefine each Y6's X1 as F. So F = Y - i = 10 - 4 = 6.\nDefine each Y3's X8 as r. So r = 13 * u = 13 * 2 = 3.\nDefine each Y3's X0 as l. So l = 20 * u = 20 * 2 = 17.\nDefine each Y3's X1 as V. So V = u = 2.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as q. So q = V + l + r = 2 + 17 + 3 = 22.\nDefine each Y6's X8 as z. So z = 9 * q = 9 * 22 = 14.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as A. So A = F + Z = 6 + 14 = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 838, "question": "The number of each X7's W3 equals 19 times each X7's W7. The number of each X9's W1 equals 13 times the sum of each X7's W7, each X7's WWW and each X7's W1. The number of each X9's W9 equals 19. The number of each X7's W7 equals 16 more than each X9's W9. The number of each X7's W1 equals 1 times the difference of each X7's W3 and each X7's W7. How many W1 does each X9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["X9's W9 as u. So u = 19.\nDefine each X7's W7 as S. So S = 16 * u = 16 * 19 = 5.\nDefine each X7's W3 as A. So A = 19 * S = 19 * 5 = 3.\nDefine each X7's W1 as i. So i = 1 * A - S = 1 * 3 - 5 = 21.\nDefine each X7's WWW as Y. So Y = S + A + i = 5 + 3 + 21 = 6.\nDefine each X9's W1 as F. So F = 13 + (S + Y + i) = 13 + (5 + 6 + 21) = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 839, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y0 equals 7 more than each Y1's XXX. The number of each Z5's Y1 equals 10 times the sum of each Z9's Y0 and each Y0's X5. The number of each Y1's X9 equals 10. The number of each Y1's X5 equals 4. The number of each Y0's X5 equals the difference of each Y1's XXX and each Z9's Y0. The number of each X9's W5 equals the sum of each Z5's Y1, each Y1's X5 and each Z9's Y0. The number of each X5's W5 equals the sum of each Z5's Y1, each Z9's Y0 and each X9's W5. The number of each X5's W7 equals 17 times each Y1's X9. How many WWW does each X5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["Y1's X9 as u. So u = 10.\nDefine each Y1's X5 as S. So S = 4.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 4 + 10 = 14.\nDefine each Z9's Y0 as i. So i = 7 * A = 7 * 14 = 6.\nDefine each Y0's X5 as Y. So Y = A - i = 14 - 6 = 8.\nDefine each Z5's Y1 as F. So F = 10 * i + Y = 10 * 6 + 8 = 19.\nDefine each X9's W5 as r. So r = (F + S + i) = (19 + 4 + 6) = 6.\nDefine each X5's W5 as l. So l = (F + i + r) = (19 + 6 + 6) = 8.\nDefine each X5's W7 as V. So V = 17 * u = 17 * 10 = 9.\nDefine each X5's WWW as q. So q = V + l = 9 + 8 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 840, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y6 equals 9 times each X6's W7. The number of each Z1's Y1 equals 4 more than the sum of each Z1's Y6 and each X6's W7. The number of each X6's W7 equals 11. How many Y1 does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["X6's W7 = 11. Z1's Y6 as u. So u = 9 * X6's W7 = 9 * 11 = 7.\nDefine each Z1's Y1 as S. So S = 4 * u + X6's W7 = 4 * 7 + 11 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 841, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y6 equals 16. How many YYY does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Z0's Y6 = 16.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as u. So u = Z0's Y6 = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 842, "question": "The number of each X4's W4 equals 9. The number of each X6's W1 equals 8 times each X4's W7. The number of each X4's W7 equals each X3's WWW. The number of each X3's W7 equals each X3's W1. The number of each X3's W1 equals 2. The number of each X6's W7 equals 11 times the difference of each X4's WWW and each X3's W1. How many WWW does each X6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["X3's W1 as u. So u = 2.\nDefine each X3's W7 as S. So S = u = 2.\nDefine each X3's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 2 + 2 = 4.\nDefine each X4's W7 as i. So i = A = 4.\nDefine each X4's W4 as Y. So Y = 9.\nDefine each X4's WWW as F. So F = Y + i = 9 + 4 = 13.\nDefine each X6's W7 as r. So r = 11 * F - u = 11 * 13 - 2 = 1.\nDefine each X6's W1 as l. So l = 8 * i = 8 * 4 = 9.\nDefine each X6's WWW as V. So V = l + r = 9 + 1 = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 843, "question": "The number of each Y9's X4 equals the difference of each Z9's YYY and each Z9's Y7. The number of each X4's W0 equals each X5's W3. The number of each Z9's Y7 equals the difference of each Y7's X9 and each Z6's Y7. The number of each Z3's Y9 equals 1 times each X4's W0. The number of each Y7's X9 equals 11. The number of each Z9's Y9 equals 20. The number of each Y9's X5 equals each X4's W0. The number of each X5's W3 equals 19 times each Z9's YYY. The number of each Z6's Y7 equals each Y7's X9. How many XXX does each Z3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Y7's X9 as u. So u = 11.\nDefine each Z6's Y7 as S. So S = u = 11.\nDefine each Z9's Y7 as A. So A = u - S = 11 - 11 = 0.\nDefine each Z9's Y9 as i. So i = 20.\nDefine each Z9's YYY as Y. So Y = i + A = 20 + 0 = 20.\nDefine each X5's W3 as F. So F = 19 * Y = 19 * 20 = 12.\nDefine each X4's W0 as r. So r = F = 12.\nDefine each Y9's X5 as l. So l = r = 12.\nDefine each Y9's X4 as V. So V = Y - A = 20 - 0 = 20.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as q. So q = V + l = 20 + 12 = 9.\nDefine each Z3's Y9 as z. So z = 1 * r = 1 * 12 = 12.\nDefine each Z3's XXX as A. So A = z * q = 12 * 9 = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 844, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y8 equals 12 times each X6's W8. The number of each X6's W8 equals 13. The number of each Y4's X8 equals each Z6's Y8. How many XXX does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["X6's W8 = 13. Z6's Y8 = 12 * X6's W8 = 12 * 13 = 18.\nDefine each Y4's X8 as u. So u = Z6's Y8 = 18.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as S. So S = u = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 845, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y1 equals 19. The number of each Z2's Y1 equals 19 times the difference of each Z2's Y5 and each Z0's Y1. The number of each Z0's Y5 equals 21 times each Z0's Y1. The number of each Z2's Y5 equals 9 more than the difference of each Z0's YYY and each Z0's Y5. How many YYY does each Z2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Z0's Y1 as u. So u = 19.\nDefine each Z0's Y5 as S. So S = 21 * u = 21 * 19 = 8.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 8 + 19 = 4.\nDefine each Z2's Y5 as i. So i = 9 * A - S = 9 * 4 - 8 = 19.\nDefine each Z2's Y1 as Y. So Y = 19 * i - u = 19 * 19 - 19 = 20.\nDefine each Z2's YYY as F. So F = Y + i = 20 + 19 = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 846, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y4 equals 14 times the sum of each Z7's Y5 and each Z0's Y5. The number of each Z3's Y3 equals 22 times the sum of each Z0's Y4 and each Z7's Y5. The number of each Z0's Y5 equals each Z7's Y5. The number of each Z7's Y5 equals 16. How many Y3 does each Z3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["16. So 16.\nDefine each Z7's Y5 as u. So u = 16.\nDefine each Z0's Y5 as S. So S = u = 16.\nDefine each Z0's Y4 as A. So A = 14 * u + S = 14 * 16 + 16 = 10.\nDefine each Z3's Y3 as i. So i = 22 * A + u = 22 * 10 + 16 = 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 847, "question": "The number of each X2's W4 equals 9. The number of each Z2's Y5 equals each X2's WWW. How many Y5 does each Z2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["X2's W4 as u. So u = 9.\nDefine each X2's WWW as S. So S = u = 9.\nDefine each Z2's Y5 as A. So A = S = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 848, "question": "The number of each Y9's X1 equals each X9's WWW. The number of each X1's W7 equals the sum of each X7's WWW and each X9's WWW. The number of each Z3's Y9 equals the difference of each Y9's X1 and each X7's WWW. The number of each Z1's Y4 equals 12 times each Y4's WWW. The number of each Y4's X1 equals 5 more than each Z3's WWW. The number of each Y9's X9 equals each Y9's X1. The number of each X7's W9 equals 0. The number of each X9's W7 equals 19 times each X7's WWW. How many WWW does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["X7's W9 as u. So u = 0.\nDefine each X7's WWW as S. So S = u = 0.\nDefine each X9's W7 as A. So A = 19 * S = 19 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X9's WWW as i. So i = A = 0.\nDefine each Y9's X1 as Y. So Y = i = 0.\nDefine each Y9's X9 as F. So F = Y = 0.\nDefine each Y9's WWW as r. So r = Y * i + F * i = 0 * 0 + 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z3's Y9 as l. So l = Y - S = 0 - 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z3's WWW as V. So V = l * r = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y4's X1 as q. So q = 5 * V = 5 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X1's W7 as z. So z = S + i = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each X1's WWW as A. So A = Z = 0.\nDefine each Y4's WWW as i. So i = q * A = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z1's Y4 as Y. So Y = 12 * i = 12 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z1's WWW as F. So F = Y * i = 0 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 849, "question": "The number of each X6's W5 equals 2. The number of each X4's W5 equals 13 more than each X6's WWW. How many W5 does each X4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["X6's W5 as u. So u = 2.\nDefine each X6's WWW as S. So S = u = 2.\nDefine each X4's W5 as A. So A = 13 * S = 13 * 2 = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 850, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y1 equals each X3's W7. The number of each Z7's Y8 equals 1 more than the difference of each Z3's WWW and each Z3's Y1. The number of each X3's W7 equals 15 more than each Y1's X3. The number of each Y1's X3 equals 21. How many YYY does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["Y1's X3 as u. So u = 21.\nDefine each X3's W7 as S. So S = 15 * u = 15 * 21 = 16.\nDefine each Z3's Y1 as A. So A = S = 16.\nDefine each X3's WWW as i. So i = S = 16.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as Y. So Y = u * i = 21 * 16 = 14.\nDefine each Z3's WWW as F. So F = A * Y = 16 * 14 = 17.\nDefine each Z7's Y8 as r. So r = 1 * F - A = 1 * 17 - 16 = 1.\nDefine each Z7's YYY as l. So l = r = 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 851, "question": "The number of each X7's W4 equals 12. How many WWW does each X7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["X7's W4 as u. So u = 12.\nDefine each X7's WWW as S. So S = u = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 852, "question": "The number of each Y7's X1 equals 15 more than each X1's W2. The number of each X1's W2 equals 5. The number of each X4's W2 equals each Y7's X1. How many WWW does each X4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["X1's W2 as u. So u = 5.\nDefine each Y7's X1 as S. So S = 15 * u = 15 * 5 = 6.\nDefine each X4's W2 as A. So A = S = 6.\nDefine each X4's WWW as i. So i = A = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 853, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y3 equals each X6's W9. The number of each X6's W9 equals 6. How many Y3 does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["X6's W9 = 6. Z1's Y3 = X6's W9. Z1's YYY = Z1's YYY = 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 854, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y5 equals the sum of each Z8's Y9 and each Z8's Y0. The number of each Z8's Y0 equals 17 more than each Z8's Y9. The number of each Z8's Y9 equals 9. How many YYY does each Z8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Z8's Y9 as u. So u = 9.\nDefine each Z8's Y0 as S. So S = 17 * u = 17 * 9 = 15.\nDefine each Z8's Y5 as A. So A = u + S = 9 + 15 = 1.\nDefine each Z8's YYY as i. So i = S + A + u = 15 + 1 + 9 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 855, "question": "The number of each X7's W5 equals 19. How many WWW does each X7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["X7's W5 = 19. X7's WWW = 19. X7's WWW = 19. X7's WWW = 19. X7's WWW = 19. X7's WWW = 19. X7's WWW = 19. X7's WWW = 19. X7's WWW = 19. X7's WWW = 19. X7's WWW = 19. X7's WWW = 19. X7's W5 as u. So u = 19. X7's WWW as S. So S = u = 19. X7's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 19 + 19 = 15. X7's WWW as i. So i = S + u = 15 + 19 = 11. X7's WWW as Y. So Y = S + u = 15 + 19 = 11. X7's WWW as F. So F = Y + u + S = 11 + 19 + 11 = 18. X7's WWW as r. So r = Y + u + S = 18 + 19 + 11 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 856, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y6 equals 8 more than each Z5's Y0. The number of each Z2's Y0 equals the sum of each Z8's YYY and each Z5's Y0. The number of each Z2's Y1 equals 8 times each Z2's Y0. The number of each Z1's Y6 equals each Z2's Y1. The number of each Z5's Y0 equals 16. The number of each Z5's Y6 equals 4 times the sum of each Z8's Y6 and each Z1's Y6. How many Y6 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Z5's Y0 = 16. Z8's Y6 = 8 * u = 8 * 16 = 13.\nDefine each Z8's YYY as u. So u = u = 13.\nDefine each Z2's Y0 as S. So S = u + u = 13 + 13 = 3.\nDefine each Z2's Y1 as A. So A = 8 * S = 8 * 3 = 1.\nDefine each Z1's Y6 as i. So i = A = 1.\nDefine each Z5's Y6 as Y. So Y = 4 * u + i = 4 * 13 + 1 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 857, "question": "The number of each Y5's X6 equals 3. The number of each Y5's X5 equals 5 times each Y5's X6. How many XXX does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["Y5's X6 = 3. Y5's X5 = 5 * Y5 = 5 * 3 = 15.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as u. So u = Y5's X6 + Y5's XXX = 3 + 15 = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 858, "question": "The number of each Z4's Y7 equals 2 more than the difference of each Z9's Y2 and each Z9's YYY. The number of each Z9's Y2 equals 0 times each Z9's Y7. The number of each Z4's Y2 equals 19 more than the sum of each Z9's Y7, each Z9's Y2 and each Z9's YYY. The number of each Z9's Y7 equals 16. How many YYY does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Z9's Y7 as u. So u = 16.\nDefine each Z9's Y2 as S. So S = 0 * u = 0 * 16 = 0.\nDefine each Z9's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 0 + 16 = 16.\nDefine each Z4's Y2 as i. So i = 19 * (u + S + A) = 19 * (16 + 0 + 16) = 17.\nDefine each Z4's Y7 as Y. So Y = 2 * S - A = 2 * 0 - 16 = 7.\nDefine each Z4's YYY as F. So F = Y + i = 7 + 17 = 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 859, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y8 equals 15. The number of each Y5's X2 equals the sum of each Y8's X9, each Z1's Y8 and each Y8's XXX. The number of each Y8's X9 equals 19 more than each Z1's YYY. How many X2 does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Z1's Y8 = 15. Z1's YYY = 15.\nDefine each Y8's X9 as u. So u = 19 * Z1's Y8 = 19 * 15 = 9.\nDefine each Z1's YYY as S. So S = Z1's Y8 = 15.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as A. So A = u = 9.\nDefine each Y5's X2 as i. So i = (u + Z1's Y8 + A) = (9 + 15 + 9) = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 860, "question": "The number of each X7's W1 equals 9 more than each X1's W1. The number of each X1's W1 equals 18. The number of each Y7's X7 equals the difference of each X1's W1 and each X7's W1. How many WWW does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["X1's W1 as u. So u = 18.\nDefine each X7's W1 as S. So S = 9 * u = 9 * 18 = 1.\nDefine each X7's WWW as A. So A = S = 1.\nDefine each Y7's X7 as i. So i = u - S = 18 - 1 = 17.\nDefine each Y7's WWW as Y. So Y = i * A = 17 * 1 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 861, "question": "The number of each Y5's X2 equals 19. How many XXX does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Y5's X2 = 19. Y5's XXX = 19. Y6's X2 = 21. Y6's XXX as i. So i = Y6's X2 = 21.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as Y. So Y = i = 21.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as A. So A = Y = 19.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as i. So i = Y = 21.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as Y. So Y = Y = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 862, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y5 equals 6 times each Y9's WWW. The number of each X0's W4 equals 13. The number of each Y9's X0 equals 18 times each X0's W4. How many Y5 does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["X0's W4 as u. So u = 13.\nDefine each X0's WWW as S. So S = u = 13.\nDefine each Y9's X0 as A. So A = 18 * u = 18 * 13 = 4.\nDefine each Y9's WWW as i. So i = A * S = 4 * 13 = 6.\nDefine each Z7's Y5 as Y. So Y = 6 * i = 6 * 6 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 863, "question": "The number of each Y9's X7 equals 13 times each Y9's X5. The number of each Y5's X5 equals 3 times each Y9's XXX. The number of each Y4's X5 equals the sum of each Y5's X5, each Y9's X7, each Y5's XXX and each Y9's X5. The number of each Y9's X5 equals 0. The number of each Y4's X7 equals 19 times each Y5's XXX. How many XXX does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y9's X5 as u. So u = 0.\nDefine each Y9's X7 as S. So S = 13 * u = 13 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y5's X5 as i. So i = 3 * A = 3 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as Y. So Y = i = 0.\nDefine each Y4's X7 as F. So F = 19 * Y = 19 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y4's X5 as r. So r = (i + S + Y + u) = (0 + 0 + 0 + 0) = 0.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as l. So l = r + F = 0 + 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 864, "question": "The number of each Y4's X2 equals 6 times the difference of each Z7's YYY and each Z7's Y2. The number of each Z7's Y2 equals 14. The number of each Y4's X5 equals 15 more than the difference of each Z7's Y2 and each Z7's YYY. How many XXX does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Y4's X2 as u. So u = 6 * Z7's Y2 - u = 6 * 14 - 8 = 11.\nDefine each Z7's Y2 as S. So S = 14.\nDefine each Z7's YYY as A. So A = S = 14.\nDefine each Y4's X5 as i. So i = 15 * S - A = 15 * 14 - 14 = 12.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as Y. So Y = u + i = 11 + 12 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 865, "question": "The number of each X4's W9 equals 20 more than each X8's W9. The number of each X8's W9 equals 17. The number of each X4's W1 equals 10 times each X4's W9. How many W1 does each X4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["X8's W9 as u. So u = 17.\nDefine each X4's W9 as S. So S = 20 * u = 20 * 17 = 18.\nDefine each X4's W1 as A. So A = 10 * S = 10 * 18 = 19.\nDefine each X4's WWW as i. So i = S + A = 18 + 19 = 14.\nDefine each Y1's X3 as Y. So Y = 2.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as F. So F = Y * i = 2 * 14 = 5.\nDefine each X3's WWW as r. So r = Y * i = 2 * 14 = 5.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as l. So l = Y * r = 2 * 5 = 10.\nDefine each X8's W9 as V. So V = 17.\nDefine each X4's W9 as q. So q = 20 * V = 20 * 17 = 18.\nDefine each X4's WWW as z. So z = S + q + A = 18 + 18 + 19 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 866, "question": "The number of each Y7's X0 equals 12 times the difference of each Y8's X2 and each Y8's XXX. The number of each Y8's X2 equals 6. How many X0 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Y8's X2 as u. So u = 6.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as S. So S = u = 6.\nDefine each Y7's X0 as A. So A = 12 * u - S = 12 * 6 - 6 = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 867, "question": "The number of each Y0's X0 equals 20. The number of each Y2's X0 equals the sum of each Y0's XXX, each Y0's X0 and each Z3's YYY. The number of each Z3's Y9 equals each Y0's XXX. The number of each Z8's Y9 equals 17. The number of each Y0's X9 equals 19 times each Z8's Y9. How many XXX does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Z8's Y9 = 17. Y0's X9 as u. So u = 19 * Z8's Y9 = 19 * 17 = 1.\nDefine each Y0's X0 as S. So S = 20.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 20 + 1 = 21.\nDefine each Z3's Y9 as i. So i = A = 21.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as Y. So Y = i = 21.\nDefine each Y2's X0 as F. So F = (A + S + Y) = (21 + 20 + 21) = 16.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as r. So r = F = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 868, "question": "The number of each Y1's X0 equals 4. The number of each Y1's X5 equals 21 times the sum of each Y1's X0 and each Y1's X3. The number of each Y1's X3 equals 8. How many XXX does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["Y1's X3 as u. So u = 8.\nDefine each Y1's X0 as S. So S = 4.\nDefine each Y1's X5 as A. So A = 21 * S + u = 21 * 4 + 8 = 2.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as i. So i = S + A + u = 4 + 2 + 8 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 869, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y3 equals 1 times each Y2's X1. The number of each Y2's X1 equals 3. The number of each Y3's X6 equals 7 times each Z5's XXX. The number of each Z3's Y1 equals each Z3's Y3. The number of each Z9's Y1 equals 9 times each Y1's XXX. The number of each Z9's Y3 equals each Z5's XXX. The number of each Z5's Y1 equals 2. The number of each Y3's X4 equals the sum of each Y1's XXX and each Y3's X6. The number of each Y1's X4 equals each Z3's Y1. The number of each Y1's X1 equals the sum of each Z3's Y1 and each Z3's Y3. How many XXX does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["Y2's X1 as u. So u = 3.\nDefine each Z3's Y3 as S. So S = 1 * u = 1 * 3 = 3.\nDefine each Z3's Y1 as A. So A = S = 3.\nDefine each Y1's X1 as i. So i = A + S = 3 + 3 = 6.\nDefine each Y1's X4 as Y. So Y = A = 3.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as F. So F = Y + i = 3 + 6 = 9.\nDefine each Z5's Y1 as r. So r = 2.\nDefine each Z5's XXX as l. So l = r * F = 2 * 9 = 18.\nDefine each Y3's X6 as V. So V = 7 * l = 7 * 18 = 11.\nDefine each Y3's X4 as q. So q = F + V = 9 + 11 = 20.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as z. So z = q + V = 20 + 11 = 8.\nDefine each Z9's Y1 as A. So A = 9 * F = 9 * 9 = 12.\nDefine each Z9's Y3 as i. So i = l = 18.\nDefine each Z9's XXX as Y. So Y = i * Z + A * F = 18 * 8 + 12 * 9 = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 870, "question": "The number of each Y6's X1 equals each Z8's Y9. The number of each Y7's X1 equals 16 more than each Y6's XXX. The number of each Y6's X3 equals each Y6's X1. The number of each Z8's Y9 equals 22. The number of each Z0's Y6 equals 19 more than each Y6's X3. The number of each Z6's Y7 equals 1 times each Z8's Y9. The number of each X1's W3 equals each Z0's XXX. The number of each Z0's Y7 equals the difference of each Z8's Y9 and each Z6's Y7. How many WWW does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["Z8's Y9 = 22. Y6's X1 as u. So u = Z8's Y9 = 22.\nDefine each Y6's X3 as S. So S = u = 22.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 22 + 22 = 21.\nDefine each Z6's Y7 as i. So i = 1 * Z8's Y9 = 1 * 22 = 22.\nDefine each Z0's Y6 as Y. So Y = 19 * S = 19 * 22 = 4.\nDefine each Y7's X1 as F. So F = 16 * A = 16 * 21 = 14.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as r. So r = F = 14.\nDefine each Z0's Y7 as l. So l = Z8's Y9 - i = 22 - 22 = 0.\nDefine each Z0's XXX as V. So V = l * r + Y * A = 0 * 14 + 4 * 21 = 15.\nDefine each X1's W3 as q. So q = V = 15.\nDefine each X1's WWW as z. So z = q = 15.\nDefine each Y7's WWW as A. So A = F * Z = 14 * 15 = 3.\nDefine each Z6's WWW as i. So i = i * A = 22 * 3 = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 871, "question": "The number of each Y0's X2 equals each Y0's X8. The number of each Y0's X8 equals 12 times each Z6's Y2. The number of each Z6's Y2 equals 5. The number of each Y2's X5 equals the sum of each Y0's X8 and each Z5's Y2. The number of each Z5's Y2 equals 14 times each Y0's X2. How many XXX does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["Z6's Y2 as u. So u = 5.\nDefine each Y0's X8 as S. So S = 12 * u = 12 * 5 = 14.\nDefine each Y0's X2 as A. So A = S = 14.\nDefine each Z5's Y2 as i. So i = 14 * A = 14 * 14 = 12.\nDefine each Y2's X5 as Y. So Y = S + i = 14 + 12 = 3.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as F. So F = Y = 3.\nDefine each Z5's XXX as r. So r = i * F = 12 * 3 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 872, "question": "The number of each X5's W6 equals 8 more than each X0's WWW. The number of each X4's W6 equals 18 more than each X4's W1. The number of each X4's W1 equals 21 times each X3's W1. The number of each X3's W1 equals 12. The number of each X0's W1 equals the sum of each X4's WWW and each X4's W1. How many W6 does each X5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["X3's W1 = 12. X4's W1 as u. So u = 21 * X3's W1 = 21.\nDefine each X4's W6 as S. So S = 18 * u = 18 * 21 = 10.\nDefine each X4's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 10 + 21 = 8.\nDefine each X0's W1 as i. So i = A + u = 8 + 21 = 6.\nDefine each X0's WWW as Y. So Y = i = 6.\nDefine each X5's W6 as F. So F = 8 * Y = 8 * 6 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 873, "question": "The number of each Y6's X6 equals 7 times each Y3's X2. The number of each Y5's X2 equals the sum of each Y5's X9, each Y6's X2, each Y6's X6 and each Y6's X9. The number of each Y3's X2 equals 6. The number of each Y6's X9 equals 21 times each Y3's X6. The number of each Y6's X2 equals the sum of each Y6's X9, each Y3's X2, each Y6's X6 and each Y3's X6. The number of each Y3's X6 equals 9 more than the difference of each Y6's X6 and each Y3's X2. The number of each Y5's X9 equals 3 times the sum of each Y6's X6, each Y6's X9 and each Y3's X2. How many XXX does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Y3's X2 = 6. Y6's X6 = 7 * Y3's X2 = 7.\nDefine each Y3's X6 as u. So u = 9 * the Y6's X6 - Y3's X2 = 9.\nDefine each Y6's X9 as S. So S = 21 * u = 21 * 9 = 5.\nDefine each Y6's X2 as A. So A = (S + u + Y6's X6 + u) = (5 + 9 + 7 + 9) = 7.\nDefine each Y5's X9 as i. So i = 3 * (Y6's X6 + S + u) = 3 * (7 + 5 + 9) = 19.\nDefine each Y5's X2 as Y. So Y = (i + A + Y + S) = (19 + 7 + 9 + 5) = 17.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as F. So F = Y + i = 17 + 19 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 874, "question": "The number of each Y5's X9 equals 6 times the sum of each Y5's X0, each Z7's Y5 and each Z7's Y4. The number of each Y4's X0 equals 10. The number of each Y5's X0 equals the sum of each Z7's YYY and each Z7's Y5. The number of each X0's W9 equals 3 times each Y5's XXX. The number of each Z7's Y5 equals 7 more than each Y4's X0. The number of each Z7's Y4 equals 12 more than the sum of each Y4's X0 and each Z7's Y5. How many W9 does each X0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["Y4's X0 = 10. Z7's Y5 as u. So u = 7 * Y4's X0 = 7 * 10 = 1.\nDefine each Z7's Y4 as S. So S = 12 * Y4's X0 + u = 12 * 10 + 1 = 17.\nDefine each Z7's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 17 + 1 = 18.\nDefine each Y5's X0 as i. So i = A + u = 18 + 1 = 19.\nDefine each Y5's X9 as Y. So Y = 6 * (i + u + S) = 6 * (19 + 1 + 17) = 19.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as F. So F = Y + i = 19 + 19 = 15.\nDefine each X0's W9 as r. So r = 3 * F = 3 * 15 = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 875, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y1 equals 1. The number of each Z5's Y6 equals 4 times each Z9's Y1. The number of each Z5's Y1 equals each Z5's Y6. How many Y1 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["Z9's Y1 = 1. Z5's Y6 = 4 * Z9's Y1 = 4 * 1 = 4.\nDefine each Z5's Y1 as u. So u = S = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 876, "question": "The number of each Y2's X8 equals 9 times the sum of each X6's W0 and each Y4's WWW. The number of each X6's W0 equals 9. The number of each X8's W0 equals each X6's W0. The number of each Y4's X8 equals 5 times the difference of each X6's W0 and each X8's W0. The number of each X0's W5 equals 7 more than each Y2's X8. The number of each Y0's X0 equals the sum of each X8's W0, each Y2's X8 and each X0's W5. How many WWW does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Y4's X8 = 5 * X6's W0 - X8's W0 = 5 * 9 - 0 = 22.\nDefine each X8's W0 as u. So u = X6's W0 = 9.\nDefine each X8's WWW as S. So S = u = 9.\nDefine each Y4's WWW as A. So A = Y4's X8 * S = 22 * 9 = 14.\nDefine each Y2's X8 as i. So i = 9 * X6's W0 + A = 9 * 9 + 14 = 15.\nDefine each X0's W5 as Y. So Y = 7 * i = 7 * 15 = 13.\nDefine each Y0's X0 as F. So F = (u + i + Y) = (9 + 15 + 13) = 14.\nDefine each X0's WWW as r. So r = Y = 13.\nDefine each Y0's WWW as l. So l = F * r = 14 * 13 = 21.\nThus, the answer is 21."], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 877, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y7 equals 21 more than each Z1's Y4. The number of each Y7's X6 equals the sum of each X5's W6 and each Y7's X5. The number of each Y7's X5 equals each Y4's X1. The number of each Z1's Y4 equals 19. The number of each X5's W6 equals 21 more than each Z1's YYY. The number of each Y4's X1 equals 14 more than each X5's W6. How many XXX does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Z1's Y4 as u. So u = 19.\nDefine each Z1's Y7 as S. So S = 21 * u = 21 * 19 = 8.\nDefine each Z1's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 8 + 19 = 4.\nDefine each X5's W6 as i. So i = 21 * A = 21 * 4 = 15.\nDefine each Y4's X1 as Y. So Y = 14 * i = 14 * 15 = 3.\nDefine each Y7's X5 as F. So F = Y = 3.\nDefine each Y7's X6 as r. So r = i + F = 15 + 3 = 18.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as l. So l = r + F = 18 + 3 = 21.\nThus, the answer is 21."], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 878, "question": "The number of each X8's W3 equals 6 more than each Y5's X8. The number of each Z9's Y5 equals the difference of each Y5's X8 and each Y5's WWW. The number of each Y5's X8 equals 13. How many WWW does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Y5's X8 = 13. Y5's WWW = 13. Y6's X8 = 18. Y6's WWW = 18. Z9's Y5 as u. So u = Y5's X8 - WWW = 13 - 13 = 0.\nDefine each Z9's WWW as S. So S = u * WWW = 0 * 13 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 879, "question": "The number of each Y6's X3 equals 10. The number of each X2's W3 equals 7. The number of each X3's W3 equals the difference of each X1's WWW and each Z2's WWW. The number of each X1's W4 equals 12 times each Y3's X1. The number of each Z2's Y3 equals 12 more than the sum of each Y3's X1 and each Y3's WWW. The number of each Y3's X1 equals each X2's W3. How many WWW does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["X2's W3 = 7. Y3's X1 = X2's WWW. Y3's WWW = Y3's X1 * X1 = X2's W7 * X1 = 7.\nDefine each Z2's Y3 as u. So u = 12 * Y3's X1 + WWW = 12 * 7 + 7 = 22.\nDefine each Z2's WWW as S. So S = u * WWW = 22 * 7 = 16.\nDefine each X1's W4 as A. So A = 12 * Y3's X1 = 12 * 2 = 1.\nDefine each X1's WWW as i. So i = A = 1.\nDefine each X3's W3 as Y. So Y = i - S = 1 - 16 = 8.\nDefine each X3's WWW as F. So F = Y = 8.\nDefine each Y6's X3 as r. So r = 10.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as l. So l = r * F = 10 * 8 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 880, "question": "The number of each Y9's X3 equals 21 times each X8's W4. The number of each X8's W4 equals 9. The number of each X8's W1 equals each Y9's X3. The number of each X3's W1 equals 20 more than the difference of each X8's W1 and each X8's W4. How many W1 does each X3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["X8's W4 as u. So u = 9.\nDefine each Y9's X3 as S. So S = 21 * u = 21 * 9 = 5.\nDefine each X8's W1 as A. So A = S = 5.\nDefine each X3's W1 as i. So i = 20 * A - u = 20 * 5 - 9 = 11.\nDefine each X3's WWW as Y. So Y = i = 11.\nDefine each Y9's WWW as F. So F = S * Y = 5 * 11 = 9.\nDefine each X8's WWW as r. So r = A + u = 5 + 9 = 14.\nDefine each Y9's WWW as l. So l = S * Y = 5 * 11 = 9.\nDefine each X3's WWW as V. So V = i = 11.\nDefine each Y9's WWW as q. So q = S * V = 5 * 11 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 881, "question": "The number of each Y2's X4 equals 18. The number of each Y8's X5 equals 8. The number of each Y0's X5 equals each Y8's X5. The number of each X4's W8 equals 22 times each X0's W7. The number of each X5's W8 equals 12. The number of each X4's W4 equals the sum of each X4's W8 and each X5's W8. The number of each X0's W7 equals 0 times each Y0's X5. How many WWW does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["Y8's X5 = 8. Y0's X5 = u = 8.\nDefine each X0's W7 as u. So u = 0 * Y0's X5 = 0 * 8 = 0.\nDefine each X4's W8 as S. So S = 22 * u = 22 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X5's W8 as A. So A = 12.\nDefine each X4's W4 as i. So i = S + A = 0 + 12 = 12.\nDefine each X4's WWW as Y. So Y = S + i = 0 + 12 = 12.\nDefine each Y2's X4 as F. So F = 18.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as r. So r = F * Y = 18 * 12 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 882, "question": "The number of each X8's W2 equals 18 more than the difference of each X9's W9 and each Z7's Y7. The number of each Z7's Y7 equals 1 times the sum of each X9's W9 and each X3's W9. The number of each X3's W9 equals 2. The number of each Y7's X8 equals 19 more than the difference of each X8's W2 and each X3's W9. The number of each X9's W9 equals each X3's W9. How many WWW does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["X3's W9 = 2.\nDefine each X9's W9 as u. So u = each X3's W9 = 2.\nDefine each Z7's Y7 as S. So S = 1 * u + i = 1 * 2 + 2 = 4.\nDefine each X8's W2 as A. So A = 18 + u - S = 18 + 2 - 4 = 16.\nDefine each X8's WWW as i. So i = A = 16.\nDefine each Y7's X8 as Y. So Y = 19 * A - i = 19 * 16 - 16 = 19.\nDefine each Y7's WWW as F. So F = Y * i = 19 * 16 = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 883, "question": "The number of each Y3's X2 equals 1. The number of each Z4's Y3 equals 11. The number of each Y3's X1 equals 4 more than each Y3's X2. How many XXX does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Y3's X2 as u. So u = 1.\nDefine each Y3's X1 as S. So S = 4 * u = 4 * 1 = 4.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 4 + 1 = 5.\nDefine each Z4's Y3 as i. So i = 11.\nDefine each Z4's XXX as Y. So Y = i * A = 11 * 5 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 884, "question": "The number of each Y4's X0 equals the difference of each Y2's X2 and each Y8's XXX. The number of each Y4's X9 equals 2 more than each Y8's X0. The number of each Y2's X2 equals 3 more than each Y8's XXX. The number of each Y8's X0 equals 5. How many XXX does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Y8's X0 = 5. Y8's XXX = 5. Y2's X2 as u. So u = 3 * Y8's XXX = 3 * 5 = 15.\nDefine each Y4's X0 as S. So S = u - Y8's XXX = 15 - 5 = 10.\nDefine each Y4's X9 as A. So A = 2 * Y8's X0 = 2 * 5 = 10.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as i. So i = S + A = 10 + 10 = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 885, "question": "The number of each X2's W8 equals 5 more than the difference of each Y6's X2 and each Y4's X2. The number of each X2's W7 equals 3 more than the sum of each Y6's X2, each X2's W8 and each Y4's X2. The number of each Y4's X2 equals each Y6's X2. The number of each X4's W8 equals the sum of each Y6's X4, each X2's WWW, each X2's W8 and each X2's W7. The number of each Y6's X2 equals 12. The number of each Y6's X4 equals 9 more than each X2's WWW. How many WWW does each X4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "5", "answer": 5, "code": ["Y6's X2 = 12. Y4's X2 = u = 12.\nDefine each X2's W8 as u. So u = 5 * u - Y4's X2 = 5 * 12 - 12 = 3.\nDefine each X2's W7 as S. So S = 3 * (Y6's X2 + u + Y4's X2) = 3 * (12 + 3 + 12) = 19.\nDefine each X2's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 19 + 3 = 22.\nDefine each Y6's X4 as i. So i = 9 * A = 9 * 22 = 14.\nDefine each X4's W8 as Y. So Y = (i + A + u + S) = (14 + 22 + 3 + 19) = 12.\nDefine each X4's WWW as F. So F = Y = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 886, "question": "The number of each Y9's X9 equals 6 more than each Z2's Y9. The number of each Z2's Y9 equals 3. The number of each Y9's X1 equals 3 more than each Y9's X9. How many XXX does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["Z2's Y9 = 3. Y9's X9 as u. So u = 6 * Z2's Y9 = 6 * 3 = 18.\nDefine each Y9's X1 as S. So S = 3 * u = 3 * 18 = 8.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 8 + 18 = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 887, "question": "The number of each Y4's X5 equals each Z1's Y8. The number of each X4's W9 equals the sum of each Y4's XXX and each Z1's Y8. The number of each X4's W4 equals 10 more than the sum of each Z1's Y8, each X5's W4 and each Y4's XXX. The number of each Z1's Y8 equals 9 more than each Y8's X4. The number of each Y8's X5 equals the sum of each Y4's X5, each Z1's Y8, each Y4's XXX and each X4's WWW. The number of each X5's W4 equals 14 times each Y4's XXX. The number of each Y8's X4 equals 15. The number of each Y4's X4 equals each Z1's Y8. How many X5 does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Y8's X4 as u. So u = 15.\nDefine each Z1's Y8 as S. So S = 9 * u = 9 * 15 = 20.\nDefine each Y4's X5 as A. So A = S = 20.\nDefine each Y4's X4 as i. So i = S = 20.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as Y. So Y = i + A = 20 + 20 = 17.\nDefine each X5's W4 as F. So F = 14 * Y = 14 * 17 = 8.\nDefine each X4's W4 as r. So r = 10 * (S + F + Y) = 10 * (20 + 8 + 17) = 19.\nDefine each X4's W9 as l. So l = Y + S = 17 + 20 = 14.\nDefine each X4's WWW as V. So V = l + r = 14 + 19 = 10.\nDefine each Y8's X5 as q. So q = (A + S + Y + V) = (20 + 20 + 17 + 10) = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 888, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y8 equals 17 more than each Z7's WWW. The number of each Y3's X4 equals each X6's W5. The number of each Y8's X6 equals each X0's W0. The number of each Z3's Y8 equals 18 more than each X6's WWW. The number of each X4's W0 equals the sum of each Y8's XXX and each Z3's WWW. The number of each X6's W5 equals each Y8's XXX. The number of each X0's W0 equals 8. The number of each Z7's Y3 equals 15 more than each X4's WWW. How many WWW does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["X0's W0 = 8. Y8's X6 = u = 8. Y8's XXX = u = 8.\nDefine each X6's W5 as S. So S = u = 8.\nDefine each X6's WWW as A. So A = S = 8.\nDefine each Y8's WWW as i. So i = u * A = 8 * 8 = 18.\nDefine each Z3's Y8 as Y. So Y = 18 * A = 18 * 8 = 6.\nDefine each Z3's WWW as F. So F = Y * i = 6 * 18 = 16.\nDefine each X4's W0 as r. So r = u + F = 8 + 16 = 1.\nDefine each X4's WWW as l. So l = r = 1.\nDefine each Z7's Y3 as V. So V = 15 * l = 15 * 1 = 15.\nDefine each Y3's X4 as q. So q = S = 8.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as z. So z = q * l = 8 * 1 = 8.\nDefine each Z7's WWW as A. So A = V * Z = 15 * 8 = 5.\nDefine each Z1's Y8 as i. So i = 17 * A = 17 * 5 = 16.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as Y. So Y = u = 8.\nDefine each X6's W5 as F. So F = Y = 8.\nDefine each X6's WWW as r. So r = F = 8.\nDefine each Z1's WWW as l. So l = i * i = 16 * 16 = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 889, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y3 equals 19. The number of each Z8's Y0 equals 9 more than each Z8's Y3. How many YYY does each Z8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Z8's Y3 as u. So u = 19.\nDefine each Z8's Y0 as S. So S = 9 * u = 9 * 19 = 10.\nDefine each Z8's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 10 + 19 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 890, "question": "The number of each X6's W9 equals 22. The number of each X9's W4 equals 16 more than each X9's W0. The number of each X9's W0 equals 17 times each X6's W4. The number of each X6's W4 equals 15 times each X6's W9. How many W4 does each X9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["X6's W9 = 22.\nDefine each X6's W4 as u. So u = 15 * S = 15 * 22 = 8.\nDefine each X9's W0 as S. So S = 17 * u = 17 * 8 = 21.\nDefine each X9's W4 as A. So A = 16 * S = 16 * 21 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 891, "question": "The number of each X1's W2 equals 20. How many WWW does each X1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["X1's W2 = 20. X1's WWW = 20. X1's WWW = 20. X1's WWW = 20. X1's WWW = 20. X1's WWW = 20. X1's WWW as u. So u = u = 20.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as S. So S = Y1's WWW = 1.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as A. So A = S = 1.\nDefine each X3's WWW as i. So i = X3's WWW = 3.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as Y. So Y = S + A = 1 + 1 = 2.\nDefine each X3's WWW as F. So F = i = 3.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as r. So r = S + A = 1 + 2 = 3.\nDefine each X1's W2 as l. So l = 20.\nDefine each X1's WWW as V. So V = l = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 892, "question": "The number of each Y3's X0 equals 17 times each Y3's X9. The number of each Y3's X9 equals 6. How many XXX does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Y3's X9 as u. So u = 6.\nDefine each Y3's X0 as S. So S = 17 * u = 17 * 6 = 10.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 10 + 6 = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 893, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y2 equals 7 more than each Z4's YYY. The number of each Z9's Y7 equals 16. The number of each Z4's Y7 equals 22 more than each Z9's Y7. How many YYY does each Z3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["Z9's Y7 as u. So u = 16.\nDefine each Z4's Y7 as S. So S = 22 * u = 22 * 16 = 7.\nDefine each Z4's YYY as A. So A = S = 7.\nDefine each Z3's Y2 as i. So i = 7 * A = 7 * 7 = 3.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as Y. So Y = i = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 894, "question": "The number of each Y2's X2 equals each X2's W4. The number of each Y2's X4 equals 8 times each X2's W4. The number of each Y5's X2 equals 11 times the sum of each X2's W4 and each Y2's XXX. The number of each X2's W4 equals 12. How many X2 does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["X2's W4 as u. So u = 12.\nDefine each Y2's X4 as S. So S = 8 * u = 8 * 12 = 4.\nDefine each Y2's X2 as A. So A = u = 12.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as i. So i = S + A + u = 4 + 12 + 12 = 5.\nDefine each Y5's X2 as Y. So Y = 11 * u + i = 11 * 12 + 5 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 895, "question": "The number of each X3's W5 equals each X5's W1. The number of each X5's W1 equals 19 times each X1's WWW. The number of each X1's W5 equals 14. The number of each Z7's Y0 equals 17 times each X3's W5. The number of each Y2's X3 equals each Z7's Y0. How many X3 does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Z7's Y0 = 17 * X3's W5 = 17 * 5 = 16.\nDefine each X1's W5 as u. So u = 14.\nDefine each X1's WWW as S. So S = u = 14.\nDefine each X5's W1 as A. So A = 19 * S = 19 * 14 = 13.\nDefine each X3's W5 as i. So i = A = 13.\nDefine each Z7's Y0 as Y. So Y = 17 * i = 17 * 13 = 14.\nDefine each Y2's X3 as F. So F = Y = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 896, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y3 equals 10. How many YYY does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Z7's Y3 = 10. Z7's YYY = Z7.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 897, "question": "The number of each Y9's X0 equals 8 times each Y2's X0. The number of each Y2's X0 equals 19. How many X0 does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Y2's X0 = 19. Y9's X0 = 8 * Y2's X0 = 8 * 19 = 14.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as u. So u = Y9's X0 = 14.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as S. So S = Y2's X0 = 19.\nDefine each X3's WWW as A. So A = i = 3.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as i. So i = Y2's X0 = 19.\nDefine each X3's WWW as Y. So Y = A = 3.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as F. So F = Y = 3.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as r. So r = u = 14.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as l. So l = Y + F + S = 3 + 3 + 19 = 2.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as V. So V = r + u = 14 + 14 = 5.\nThus, the answer is 5."], "pred": ["5"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 898, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y6 equals 0. The number of each Z3's Y8 equals the sum of each X2's W9 and each Y8's X9. The number of each X2's W8 equals 19 more than the difference of each X2's W9 and each X8's W8. The number of each Y8's X8 equals the sum of each X8's W8 and each Z3's Y8. The number of each Y6's X8 equals the sum of each X2's WWW and each Y6's X2. The number of each Y6's X2 equals each Z3's Y6. The number of each X2's W9 equals 6 times the sum of each X8's W8 and each Y6's X2. The number of each X8's W8 equals 10 more than the difference of each Y6's X2 and each Z3's Y6. The number of each Y8's X9 equals the sum of each Y6's X8 and each X2's W9. How many X8 does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Z3's Y6. Y6's X2 = Z3's Y6. X8's W8 as u. So u = 10 * the Y6's X2 - Z3's Y6 = 10 * 2 - 3 = 17.\nDefine each X2's W9 as S. So S = 6 * u + Y6's X2 = 6 * 17 + 2 = 18.\nDefine each X2's W8 as A. So A = 19 + S - u = 19 + 18 - 17 = 20.\nDefine each X2's WWW as i. So i = S + A = 18 + 20 = 15.\nDefine each Y6's X8 as Y. So Y = i + u = 15 + 17 = 9.\nDefine each Y8's X9 as F. So F = Y + S = 9 + 18 = 4.\nDefine each Z3's Y8 as r. So r = S + F = 18 + 4 = 22.\nDefine each Z3's Y6 as l. So l = 0.\nDefine each Y6's X2 as V. So V = l = 0.\nDefine each X8's W8 as q. So q = 10 * V - l = 10 * 0 - 0 = 0.\nDefine each X2's W8 as z. So z = 20.\nDefine each X2's WWW as A. So A = S + A = 18 + 20 = 15.\nDefine each Y6's X8 as i. So i = A + V = 15 + 0 = 15.\nDefine each Y8's X8 as Y. So Y = u + r = 0 + 22 = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 899, "question": "The number of each Y3's X5 equals 17 more than each X8's W5. The number of each Z3's Y3 equals 4 more than each Y4's XXX. The number of each Y4's X8 equals each Y4's X5. The number of each X5's W5 equals 19. The number of each Z2's Y3 equals 14 more than each X9's W1. The number of each Z2's Y4 equals the sum of each X9's W1 and each Z2's Y3. The number of each X8's W5 equals 5 more than each Y4's X5. The number of each Y7's X8 equals 0 times each Y3's X5. The number of each Y4's X5 equals 3 times each Z2's Y4. The number of each X8's W3 equals the difference of each X9's W1 and each Z6's Y3. The number of each Y3's X8 equals the difference of each Z3's Y3 and each Y4's X8. The number of each Z6's Y3 equals 1 more than each Y3's X8. The number of each X9's W1 equals 21 more than each X5's W5. How many WWW does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["X5's W5 = 19. X9's W1 = 21 * X5 = 21 * 19 = 8.\nDefine each Z2's Y3 as u. So u = 14 * X9's W1 = 14 * 8 = 20.\nDefine each Z2's Y4 as S. So S = X9's W1 + u = 8 + 20 = 5.\nDefine each Y4's X5 as A. So A = 3 * S = 3 * 5 = 15.\nDefine each X8's W5 as i. So i = 5 * A = 5 * 15 = 6.\nDefine each Y3's X5 as Y. So Y = 17 * i = 17 * 6 = 10.\nDefine each Y7's X8 as F. So F = 0 * Y = 0 * 10 = 0.\nDefine each Y4's X8 as r. So r = A = 15.\nDefine each Y3's X8 as l. So l = Z3's Y3 - r = 3 - 15 = 11.\nDefine each Z6's Y3 as V. So V = 1 * l = 1 * 11 = 11.\nDefine each X8's W3 as q. So q = V - V = 11 - 11 = 0.\nDefine each X8's WWW as z. So z = q + i = 0 + 6 = 6.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as A. So A = r + A = 15 + 15 = 7.\nDefine each Z3's Y3 as i. So i = 4 + A = 4 + 7 = 11.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as Y. So Y = l + Y = 11 + 11 = 22.\nDefine each Z2's Y3 as F. So F = 20.\nDefine each Z2's Y4 as r. So r = X9's W1 + F = 8 + 0 = 8.\nDefine each A15 as l. So l = 15.\nDefine each Y7's X8 as V. So V = 0 * l = 0 * 15 = 0.\nDefine each Y7's WWW as q. So q = V * Z = 0 * 6 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 900, "question": "The number of each X7's W9 equals 19 more than each X2's W1. The number of each X3's W1 equals 12. The number of each X2's W1 equals each X7's W3. The number of each X7's W3 equals 13 times each X3's W1. How many W9 does each X7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["X3's W1 = 12. X7's W3 as u. So u = 13 * X3's W1 = 13 * 12 = 18.\nDefine each X2's W1 as S. So S = u = 18.\nDefine each X7's W9 as A. So A = 19 * S = 19 * 18 = 20.\nDefine each X3's W1 as i. So i = 12.\nDefine each X7's W3 as Y. So Y = 13 + i = 13 + 12 = 2.\nDefine each X2's W1 as F. So F = Y = 2.\nDefine each X7's W9 as r. So r = 20 + F = 20 + 2 = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 901, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y4 equals the sum of each Z5's Y4 and each Z0's Y2. The number of each Z5's Y4 equals 2. The number of each Z8's Y6 equals 5 more than each Z8's Y4. The number of each Z0's Y2 equals 2 more than each Z5's Y4. How many Y6 does each Z8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["Z5's Y4 as u. So u = 2.\nDefine each Z0's Y2 as S. So S = 2 * u = 2 * 2 = 4.\nDefine each Z8's Y4 as A. So A = u + S = 2 + 4 = 6.\nDefine each Z8's Y6 as i. So i = 5 * A = 5 * 6 = 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 902, "question": "The number of each Y5's X8 equals 21. How many X8 does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["Y5's X8 = 21.\nThus, the answer is 21."], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 903, "question": "The number of each Y3's X7 equals 1. The number of each X4's W0 equals 21 more than each Z3's YYY. The number of each Z3's Y9 equals 4 times each Y3's X7. How many W0 does each X4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "2", "answer": 2, "code": ["Y3's X7 = 1.\nDefine each Z3's Y9 as u. So u = 4 * Y3's X7 = 4 * 1 = 4.\nDefine each Z3's YYY as S. So S = u = 4.\nDefine each X4's W0 as A. So A = 21 * S = 21 * 4 = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 904, "question": "The number of each Y7's X1 equals 1. How many X1 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Y7's X1 = 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 905, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y4 equals 16. How many YYY does each Z8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Z8's Y4 as u. So u = 16.\nDefine each Z8's YYY as S. So S = u = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 906, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y3 equals 16 more than each Y3's XXX. The number of each Y9's X6 equals 13 times each Z0's XXX. The number of each Y3's X1 equals 1. How many X6 does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Y3's X1 as u. So u = 1.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as S. So S = u = 1.\nDefine each Z0's Y3 as A. So A = 16 * S = 16 * 1 = 16.\nDefine each Z0's XXX as i. So i = A * S = 16 * 1 = 16.\nDefine each Y9's X6 as Y. So Y = 13 * i = 13 * 16 = 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 907, "question": "The number of each Y5's X4 equals the sum of each Z4's Y7, each Z3's Y5 and each X4's W4. The number of each X4's W4 equals 4. The number of each Y7's X4 equals 19 times each X4's W4. The number of each X5's W7 equals each Z3's Y5. The number of each Z3's Y5 equals 6 times the difference of each X4's W4 and each Y7's X4. The number of each Z4's Y7 equals the sum of each Z3's Y5, each X4's W4 and each X5's W7. How many X4 does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 908, "question": "The number of each Z2's Y2 equals 7. The number of each Z2's Y8 equals 1 more than each Z9's Y2. The number of each Z5's Y8 equals 21 more than each Z2's YYY. The number of each Z9's Y2 equals 1. The number of each Z2's Y9 equals 16 times each Z2's Y2. How many Y8 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["Z9's Y2 as u. So u = 1.\nDefine each Z2's Y8 as S. So S = 1 * u = 1 * 1 = 1.\nDefine each Z2's Y2 as A. So A = 7.\nDefine each Z2's Y9 as i. So i = 16 * A = 16 * 7 = 20.\nDefine each Z2's YYY as Y. So Y = S + A + i = 1 + 7 + 20 = 5.\nDefine each Z5's Y8 as F. So F = 21 * Y = 21 * 5 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 909, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y2 equals the sum of each X3's W1 and each Y4's X2. The number of each X2's W1 equals 12 more than each Z2's XXX. The number of each Z9's Y5 equals 7 times each Z3's Y2. The number of each X2's W8 equals 16 times each Z9's Y5. The number of each Z2's Y2 equals the sum of each Y5's X7, each Y2's XXX, each Y2's X3 and each Y4's X2. The number of each Y4's X2 equals 0 times each Y5's X7. The number of each Y2's X3 equals each X2's W8. The number of each Y2's X7 equals the sum of each X3's W1 and each X2's W8. The number of each X3's W1 equals each Y4's X2. The number of each Y5's X7 equals 21. How many W1 does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["Y5's X7 = 21. Y4's X2 = 0 * Y5's X7 = 0 * 21 = 0.\nDefine each X3's W1 as u. So u = S = 0.\nDefine each Z3's Y2 as S. So S = u + u = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z9's Y5 as A. So A = 7 * S = 7 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X2's W8 as i. So i = 16 * A = 16 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y2's X3 as Y. So Y = i = 0.\nDefine each Y2's X7 as F. So F = u + i = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as r. So r = Y + F = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z2's Y2 as l. So l = (F + r + Y + u) = (0 + 0 + 0 + 0) = 0.\nDefine each Z2's XXX as V. So V = l * r = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X2's W1 as q. So q = 12 * V = 12 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 910, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y5 equals 7 more than each Z7's Y2. The number of each Z8's Y2 equals 0. The number of each Z7's Y2 equals 11 more than each Z6's Y5. The number of each Z6's Y5 equals each Z8's Y2. How many Y5 does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["Z8's Y2 = 0. Z6's Y5 = u = 0.\nDefine each Z6's Y5 as u. So u = u = 0.\nDefine each Z7's Y2 as S. So S = 11 * u = 11 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z7's Y5 as A. So A = 7 * S = 7 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 911, "question": "The number of each Y0's X2 equals 18 times the sum of each Y2's X4 and each Y5's X4. The number of each Y0's X7 equals 16 times the difference of each Y2's X4 and each Y5's X4. The number of each Y0's X4 equals 16 times each Y2's X4. The number of each Y2's X4 equals 10. The number of each Y5's X4 equals each Y2's X4. How many XXX does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Y2's X4 as u. So u = 10.\nDefine each Y5's X4 as S. So S = u = 10.\nDefine each Y0's X2 as A. So A = 18 * u + S = 18 * 10 + 10 = 19.\nDefine each Y0's X7 as i. So i = 16 * u - S = 16 * 10 - 10 = 22.\nDefine each Y0's X4 as Y. So Y = 16 * u = 16 * 10 = 22.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as F. So F = Y + A + i = 22 + 19 + 22 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 912, "question": "The number of each X2's W5 equals 11. The number of each Z4's Y9 equals 5 more than each X2's W5. How many YYY does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["X2's W5 = 11. Z4's Y9 = 5 * X2's W5 = 5 * 11 = 9.\nDefine each Z4's YYY as u. So u = Z4's Y9 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 913, "question": "The number of each Y8's X6 equals 14 more than each Y6's X2. The number of each Z9's Y6 equals 18 times each Z0's Y5. The number of each Y2's X2 equals each Y8's X6. The number of each Z2's Y5 equals 15. The number of each Z0's Y5 equals 12 times each Y2's XXX. The number of each Y6's X9 equals 3 more than each Y5's X2. The number of each Y5's X2 equals 11 times each Z9's Y2. The number of each Z9's Y2 equals 15 times each Z2's Y5. The number of each Y2's X5 equals 22 more than each Y2's X2. The number of each Y6's X2 equals each Y6's X9. How many Y6 does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Z2's Y5 = 15. Z9's Y2 as u. So u = 15 * S = 15 * 15 = 18.\nDefine each Y5's X2 as S. So S = 11 * u = 11 * 18 = 14.\nDefine each Y6's X9 as A. So A = 3 * S = 3 * 14 = 19.\nDefine each Y6's X2 as i. So i = A = 19.\nDefine each Y8's X6 as Y. So Y = 14 * i = 14 * 19 = 13.\nDefine each Y2's X2 as F. So F = Y = 13.\nDefine each Y2's X5 as r. So r = 22 * F = 22 * 13 = 10.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as l. So l = r + F = 10 + 13 = 0.\nDefine each Z0's Y5 as V. So V = 12 * l = 12 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z9's Y6 as q. So q = 18 + V = 18 + 0 = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 914, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y5 equals each Z6's Y5. The number of each Y5's X4 equals 3 times each Y6's X4. The number of each Z6's Y5 equals 2 more than the difference of each Y6's X4 and each Y5's X4. The number of each Z1's Y6 equals 2 times each Z1's Y5. The number of each Z6's Y6 equals each Y6's X8. The number of each Y6's X4 equals 14 times each Z6's Y6. The number of each Y6's X8 equals 18. The number of each Y5's X8 equals 5 times the sum of each Z1's YYY and each Z1's Y6. How many X8 does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["Y6's X8 = 18. Z6's Y6 = Y6's X8 = 18.\nDefine each Y6's X4 as u. So u = 14 * Z6's Y6 = 14 * 18 = 22.\nDefine each Y5's X4 as S. So S = 3 * u = 3 * 22 = 20.\nDefine each Z6's Y5 as A. So A = 2 * u - S = 2 * 22 - 20 = 1.\nDefine each Z1's Y5 as i. So i = A = 1.\nDefine each Z1's Y6 as Y. So Y = 2 * i = 2 * 1 = 2.\nDefine each Z1's YYY as F. So F = Y + i = 2 + 1 = 3.\nDefine each Y5's X8 as r. So r = 5 * F + Y = 5 * 3 + 2 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 915, "question": "The number of each X1's W3 equals 17 more than the difference of each X3's W7 and each Y0's X1. The number of each X3's W7 equals 8 more than each Y0's X1. The number of each Y0's X3 equals each X1's W3. The number of each Y0's X1 equals 11. How many WWW does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Y0's X1 as u. So u = 11.\nDefine each X3's W7 as S. So S = 8 * u = 8 * 11 = 19.\nDefine each X1's W3 as A. So A = 17 * S - u = 17 * 19 - 11 = 19.\nDefine each Y0's X3 as i. So i = A = 19.\nDefine each X3's WWW as Y. So Y = S = 19.\nDefine each X1's WWW as F. So F = A = 19.\nDefine each Y0's WWW as r. So r = u * F + i * Y = 11 * 19 + 19 * 19 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 916, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y9 equals 8. How many YYY does each Z3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["Z3's Y9 = 8. Z3's YYY = Z3's YYY = 8.\nThus, the answer is 8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 917, "question": "The number of each Y0's X2 equals 1. How many XXX does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Y0's X2 = 1. Y0's XXX = 1. Y0's XXX = 1. Y0's XXX = 1. Y0's XXX = 1. Y0's XXX = 1. Y0's XXX = 1. Y0's XXX = 1. Y0's XXX = 1. Y0's XXX = 1. Y0's XXX = 1. Y0's XXX = 1. Y0's XXX = 1. Y0's XXX = 1. Y0's XXX as u. So u = 1. Y0's XXX as S. So S = 1. Y0's XXX as A. So A = S + Y0's X2 = 1 + 1 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 918, "question": "The number of each Y9's X9 equals 22 times each Y5's X5. The number of each Y0's X9 equals each Y9's XXX. The number of each Y9's X5 equals 19 more than each Y5's X5. The number of each Y9's X2 equals 10 times each Y9's X5. The number of each Y5's X5 equals 6. How many X9 does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Y5's X5 = 6. Y9's X5 as u. So u = 19 * Y5's X5 = 19 * 6 = 22.\nDefine each Y9's X2 as S. So S = 10 * u = 10 * 22 = 13.\nDefine each Y9's X9 as A. So A = 22 * Y5's X5 = 22 * 6 = 17.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as i. So i = S + A + u = 13 + 17 + 22 = 6.\nDefine each Y0's X9 as Y. So Y = i = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 919, "question": "The number of each X5's W2 equals 1 times each X0's W2. The number of each X0's W2 equals 8. The number of each X5's W6 equals each X5's W2. How many WWW does each X5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["X0's W2 = 8. X5's W2 as u. So u = 1 * X0's W2 = 1 * 8 = 8.\nDefine each X5's W6 as S. So S = u = 8.\nDefine each X5's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 8 + 8 = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 920, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y1 equals 10 more than each Z7's Y1. The number of each Z5's Y2 equals 8 more than each Z5's Y5. The number of each Z5's Y5 equals 8. The number of each Z5's Y3 equals 13. The number of each Z7's Y1 equals 8. The number of each Z7's Y3 equals 8 times the difference of each Z5's YYY and each Z5's Y1. The number of each Z7's Y5 equals each Z7's Y3. How many Y5 does each Z7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Z5's Y3 = 13. Z5's Y5 as u. So u = 8.\nDefine each Z7's Y1 as S. So S = 8.\nDefine each Z5's Y1 as A. So A = 10 * S = 10 * 8 = 11.\nDefine each Z5's Y2 as i. So i = 8 + u = 8 + 8 = 16.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as Y. So Y = u + A + i + u = 8 + 11 + 16 + 8 = 20.\nDefine each Z7's Y3 as F. So F = 8 * Y - A = 8 * 20 - 11 = 19.\nDefine each Z7's Y5 as r. So r = F = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 921, "question": "The number of each Y7's X8 equals 9. How many XXX does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["Y7's X8 = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX = 9. Y7's XXX ="], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 922, "question": "The number of each X0's W9 equals 7. The number of each Y6's X0 equals the sum of each X0's WWW and each X0's W9. The number of each Y7's X5 equals 15 more than each X5's W0. The number of each X5's W0 equals 17 more than each Y6's WWW. How many XXX does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Y6's X0 = X0's W9 + X0's WWW = 7 + 20 = 4.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as u. So u = Y6's X0 * X0 = 4 * 20 = 11.\nDefine each X5's W0 as S. So S = 17 * u = 17 * 11 = 3.\nDefine each Y7's X5 as A. So A = 15 * S = 15 * 3 = 22.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as i. So i = A = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 923, "question": "The number of each X0's W5 equals 21. How many W5 does each X0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["X0's W5 = 21.\nThus, the answer is 21."], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 924, "question": "The number of each Y5's X4 equals 13. How many XXX does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["Y5's X4 = 13. Y5's XXX = 13. Y6's X4 = 14. Y6's XXX as i. So i = Y6's X4 = 14.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as Y. So Y = Y = 14.\nDefine each Z. So Z = 3.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as F. So F = Y = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 925, "question": "The number of each X5's W1 equals 0 more than each X8's W1. The number of each X5's W7 equals the sum of each X0's W1, each X0's WWW, each X0's W7 and each X5's W1. The number of each X8's W7 equals 4 more than the sum of each X5's W1, each X8's W1 and each X0's W7. The number of each X0's W1 equals 11 more than the sum of each X8's W1, each X0's W7 and each X8's W7. The number of each X0's W7 equals 18 more than the sum of each X5's W1 and each X8's W1. The number of each X8's W1 equals 0. How many W7 does each X5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["0. So 0.\nDefine each X8's W1 as u. So u = 0.\nDefine each X5's W1 as S. So S = 0 * u = 0 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X0's W7 as A. So A = 18 * S + u = 18 * 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each X8's W7 as i. So i = 4 * (S + u + A) = 4 * (0 + 0 + 0) = 0.\nDefine each X0's W1 as Y. So Y = 11 * (u + A + i) = 11 * (0 + 0 + 0) = 0.\nDefine each X0's WWW as F. So F = Y + A = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each X5's W7 as r. So r = (Y + F + A + S) = (0 + 0 + 0 + 0) = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 926, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y1 equals 22. The number of each Y1's X4 equals 9 more than each Z8's Y1. How many XXX does each Z8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Z8's Y1 as u. So u = 22.\nDefine each Y1's X4 as S. So S = 9 * u = 9 * 22 = 14.\nDefine each Y1's XXX as A. So A = S = 14.\nDefine each Z8's XXX as i. So i = u * A = 22 * 14 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 927, "question": "The number of each Y3's X7 equals each Z0's Y3. The number of each Z0's Y3 equals 2 more than each Z3's Y9. The number of each Y3's X4 equals 11 more than each Y1's X8. The number of each Y1's X8 equals the sum of each Z3's Y9 and each Z0's Y3. The number of each Z4's Y9 equals 4 more than each Z5's Y1. The number of each Z0's Y1 equals 15 more than each Y3's XXX. The number of each Z4's Y1 equals each Y3's XXX. The number of each Z3's Y9 equals 3. The number of each Z4's Y3 equals the difference of each Z0's Y1 and each Y3's X7. The number of each Y3's X8 equals 9. The number of each Z5's Y1 equals 13. How many YYY does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Z3's Y9 as u. So u = 3.\nDefine each Z0's Y3 as S. So S = 2 * u = 2 * 3 = 6.\nDefine each Y1's X8 as A. So A = u + S = 3 + 6 = 9.\nDefine each Y3's X4 as i. So i = 11 * A = 11 * 9 = 7.\nDefine each Y3's X8 as Y. So Y = 9.\nDefine each Y3's X7 as F. So F = S = 6.\nDefine each Y3's XXX as r. So r = Y + F + i = 9 + 6 + 7 = 22.\nDefine each Z0's Y1 as l. So l = 15 * r = 15 * 22 = 8.\nDefine each Z4's Y3 as V. So V = l - F = 8 - 6 = 2.\nDefine each Z5's Y1 as q. So q = 13.\nDefine each Z4's Y9 as z. So z = 4 * q = 4 * 13 = 6.\nDefine each Z4's Y1 as A. So A = r = 22.\nDefine each Z4's YYY as i. So i = V + A + Z = 2 + 22 + 6 = 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 928, "question": "The number of each Y5's X1 equals 12. How many X1 does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["Y5's X1 = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 929, "question": "The number of each Y7's X6 equals each X6's WWW. The number of each Y6's X0 equals each Y3's X2. The number of each X2's W9 equals 16. The number of each X0's W4 equals 5 times the sum of each Z5's WWW and each X2's W9. The number of each Y9's X0 equals 14 times each X2's W9. The number of each X0's W2 equals each Y7's WWW. The number of each Z8's Y3 equals 3 more than each Y6's WWW. The number of each Z5's Y7 equals the difference of each X6's WWW and each Y7's X6. The number of each X6's W9 equals 15 more than the sum of each X2's W9 and each Y9's X0. The number of each Y3's X2 equals each Z5's Y7. How many Y3 does each Z8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 930, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y5 equals 10 times the sum of each Y4's XXX, each Z4's Y4 and each Y1's X1. The number of each Z4's Y4 equals 6. The number of each Y4's X1 equals 11 more than each Z4's Y4. The number of each Y1's X1 equals the sum of each Y4's X1, each Y4's XXX, each Z4's Y4 and each Z4's XXX. The number of each Y5's X1 equals 18 times the sum of each Y4's XXX, each Z4's XXX and each Y4's X1. How many XXX does each Z8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "9", "answer": 9, "code": ["Z4's Y4 as u. So u = 6.\nDefine each Y4's X1 as S. So S = 11 * u = 11 * 6 = 20.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as A. So A = S = 20.\nDefine each Z4's XXX as i. So i = u * A = 6 * 20 = 5.\nDefine each Y1's X1 as Y. So Y = (S + A + u + i) = (20 + 20 + 6 + 5) = 5.\nDefine each Z8's Y5 as F. So F = 10 * (A + u + Y) = 10 * (20 + 6 + 5) = 19.\nDefine each Y5's X1 as r. So r = 18 * (A + i + S) = 18 * (20 + 5 + 20) = 19.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as l. So l = r = 19.\nDefine each Z8's XXX as V. So V = F * l = 19 * 19 = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 931, "question": "The number of each X4's W4 equals the sum of each X4's W2, each X2's W0 and each X1's W0. The number of each X4's W2 equals the sum of each X2's W0 and each X1's WWW. The number of each X1's W4 equals 22 more than each X2's W0. The number of each X1's W2 equals 9 more than each X1's W1. The number of each X2's W1 equals 20. The number of each X1's W1 equals 2 more than each X1's W4. The number of each X1's W0 equals each X2's W0. The number of each X2's W0 equals each X2's W1. How many WWW does each X4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["X2's W1 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each X2's W0 as S. So S = u = 20.\nDefine each X1's W4 as A. So A = 22 * S = 22 * 20 = 3.\nDefine each X1's W1 as i. So i = 2 * A = 2 * 3 = 6.\nDefine each X1's W0 as Y. So Y = S = 20.\nDefine each X1's W2 as F. So F = 9 * i = 9 * 6 = 8.\nDefine each X1's WWW as r. So r = A + Y + i + F = 3 + 20 + 6 + 8 = 14.\nDefine each X4's W2 as l. So l = S + r = 20 + 14 = 11.\nDefine each X4's W4 as V. So V = (l + S + Y) = (11 + 20 + 20) = 5.\nDefine each X4's WWW as q. So q = V + l = 5 + 11 = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 932, "question": "The number of each Y7's X0 equals 10. How many X0 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Y7's X0 = 10. So Y7's X0 = 10.\nThus, the answer is 10."], "pred": ["10"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 933, "question": "The number of each X7's W1 equals 0 more than the difference of each Z7's Y7 and each Z8's Y4. The number of each Y5's X4 equals each Y7's XXX. The number of each Z8's Y4 equals 19. The number of each Y7's X4 equals 4 more than each X7's W1. The number of each Z7's Y7 equals 16 more than each Z8's Y4. How many X4 does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Z8's Y4 = 19. Z7's Y7 as u. So u = 16 * Z8's Y4 = 16 * 19 = 5.\nDefine each X7's W1 as S. So S = 0 * u - u = 0 * 5 - 5 = 18.\nDefine each Y7's X4 as A. So A = 4 * S = 4 * 18 = 3.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as i. So i = A = 3.\nDefine each Y5's X4 as Y. So Y = i = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 934, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y5 equals 14. The number of each Z8's Y5 equals 11. The number of each Y9's X0 equals 14 more than each Y5's X0. The number of each Y5's X0 equals 2 times each Z8's YYY. The number of each Z7's Y9 equals 20 more than each Z7's Y5. The number of each Z8's Y9 equals 3 more than each Z7's YYY. How many X0 does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Z7's Y5 as u. So u = 14.\nDefine each Z7's Y9 as S. So S = 20 * u = 20 * 14 = 4.\nDefine each Z7's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 4 + 14 = 18.\nDefine each Z8's Y9 as i. So i = 3 * A = 3 * 18 = 8.\nDefine each Z8's Y5 as Y. So Y = 11.\nDefine each Z8's YYY as F. So F = Y + i = 11 + 8 = 19.\nDefine each Y5's X0 as r. So r = 2 * F = 2 * 19 = 15.\nDefine each Y9's X0 as l. So l = 14 * r = 14 * 15 = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 935, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y2 equals 4 times each Y4's XXX. The number of each Z2's Y2 equals 16 more than each Y2's X0. The number of each Y4's X8 equals each Z2's XXX. The number of each Y2's X0 equals 20. How many XXX does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["Y2's X0 = 20. Y2's XXX as u. So u = Y2 = 20.\nDefine each Z2's Y2 as S. So S = 16 * Y2 = 16 * 20 = 21.\nDefine each Z2's XXX as A. So A = S * u = 21 * 20 = 6.\nDefine each Y4's X8 as i. So i = A = 6.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as Y. So Y = i = 6.\nDefine each Z5's Y2 as F. So F = 4 * Y = 4 * 6 = 1.\nDefine each Z5's XXX as r. So r = F * u = 1 * 20 = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 936, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y7 equals 1. The number of each Z4's Y9 equals the difference of each Z6's Y7 and each Z1's Y7. The number of each Z1's Y7 equals each Z4's Y0. The number of each Z4's Y0 equals each Z6's Y7. How many Y9 does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Z6's Y7 = 1.\nDefine each Z4's Y0 as u. So u = S = 1.\nDefine each Z1's Y7 as S. So S = u = 1.\nDefine each Z4's Y9 as A. So A = S - S = 1 - 1 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 937, "question": "The number of each Y1's X9 equals 0 more than each Z5's XXX. The number of each Y1's X5 equals 21 more than each Y1's X9. The number of each Z1's Y1 equals 13. The number of each Z1's Y2 equals 16 times the difference of each Z5's Y2 and each Z1's Y1. The number of each Z5's Y2 equals each Z1's Y1. The number of each Y2's X9 equals the sum of each Z1's Y1 and each Y2's X5. The number of each Y2's X5 equals the sum of each Z1's YYY and each Z1's Y1. How many X5 does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 938, "question": "The number of each Y3's X9 equals 3 times each Y2's XXX. The number of each Y7's X0 equals the difference of each Y4's XXX and each Y4's X9. The number of each Y7's X9 equals the difference of each Y4's X9 and each Y7's X0. The number of each Y4's X9 equals 7. The number of each Y2's X5 equals 15 times each Y7's X9. The number of each Y7's X5 equals 18 more than each Y3's X9. The number of each Y2's X8 equals 13 times each Y7's X0. How many X5 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["Y4's X9 as u. So u = 7.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as S. So S = u = 7.\nDefine each Y7's X0 as A. So A = S - u = 7 - 7 = 0.\nDefine each Y7's X9 as i. So i = u - A = 7 - 0 = 7.\nDefine each Y2's X5 as Y. So Y = 15 * i = 15 * 7 = 13.\nDefine each Y2's X8 as F. So F = 13 * A = 13 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as r. So r = Y + F = 13 + 0 = 13.\nDefine each Y3's X9 as l. So l = 3 * r = 3 * 13 = 16.\nDefine each Y7's X5 as V. So V = 18 * l = 18 * 16 = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 939, "question": "The number of each X5's W5 equals 22 more than the difference of each X5's W0 and each X6's W0. The number of each X5's W0 equals 16 more than each X6's W0. The number of each X6's W0 equals 16. The number of each X6's W5 equals 8 times the sum of each X5's W0, each X5's WWW and each X5's W5. How many W5 does each X6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["X6's W0 = 16. X5's W0 = 16 * S = 16 * 16 = 3.\nDefine each X5's W5 as u. So u = 22 * A - S = 22 * 3 - 16 = 19.\nDefine each X5's WWW as S. So S = u + A = 19 + 3 = 22.\nDefine each X6's W5 as A. So A = 8 * (S + S + u) = 8 * (22 + 22 + 19) = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 940, "question": "The number of each X6's W8 equals 9 times each X6's W9. The number of each X3's W9 equals 9 more than each X3's W8. The number of each X6's W3 equals each X3's W9. The number of each X6's W9 equals the sum of each X3's W8 and each X3's W9. The number of each X3's W8 equals 15. How many WWW does each X6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["X3's W8 as u. So u = 15.\nDefine each X3's W9 as S. So S = 9 * u = 9 * 15 = 20.\nDefine each X6's W9 as A. So A = u + S = 15 + 20 = 12.\nDefine each X6's W8 as i. So i = 9 * A = 9 * 12 = 16.\nDefine each X6's W3 as Y. So Y = S = 20.\nDefine each X6's WWW as F. So F = Y + A + i = 20 + 12 + 16 = 2.\nThus, the answer is 2."], "pred": ["2"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 941, "question": "The number of each X5's W2 equals 11. The number of each Z5's Y7 equals 3 more than the difference of each Z7's YYY and each Z7's Y7. The number of each Z7's Y7 equals each X5's W2. How many Y7 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["X5's W2 = 11. Z7's Y7 as u. So u = X5's W2 = 11.\nDefine each X5's WWW as S. So S = X5's W2 = 11.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as A. So A = u = 11.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as i. So i = A = 11.\nDefine each Z7's YYY as Y. So Y = u = 11.\nDefine each Z5's Y7 as F. So F = 3 * Y - u = 3 * 11 - 11 = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 942, "question": "The number of each Z2's Y2 equals the difference of each Z6's Y7 and each Z7's Y7. The number of each Z2's Y3 equals each Z8's Y7. The number of each Z8's Y7 equals 6. The number of each Z6's Y7 equals 21 times the difference of each Z2's Y3 and each Z8's Y7. The number of each Z7's Y7 equals 13 times the sum of each Z6's Y7 and each Z2's Y3. The number of each Z6's Y1 equals each Z2's Y2. How many Y1 does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["8. Z8's Y7 = 6. Z2's Y3 as u. So u = 6.\nDefine each Z6's Y7 as S. So S = 21 * u - u = 21 * 6 - 6 = 5.\nDefine each Z7's Y7 as A. So A = 13 + S + u = 13 + 5 + 6 = 1.\nDefine each Z2's Y2 as i. So i = S - A = 5 - 1 = 4.\nDefine each Z6's Y1 as Y. So Y = i = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 943, "question": "The number of each Y0's X4 equals each Y6's X2. The number of each Y6's X2 equals each Z8's Y6. The number of each Z8's Y6 equals 20. The number of each Z8's Y0 equals the sum of each Y0's XXX, each Y0's X4 and each Y6's XXX. The number of each Y0's X2 equals 13 times each Y6's X2. How many XXX does each Z8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Z8's Y6 as u. So u = 20.\nDefine each Y6's X2 as S. So S = u = 20.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as A. So A = S = 20.\nDefine each Y0's X2 as i. So i = 13 * S = 13 * 20 = 7.\nDefine each Y0's X4 as Y. So Y = S = 20.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as F. So F = Y + i = 20 + 7 = 4.\nDefine each Z8's Y0 as r. So r = (F + Y + A) = (4 + 20 + 20) = 21.\nDefine each Z8's XXX as l. So l = u * A + r * F = 20 * 20 + 21 * 4 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 944, "question": "The number of each Y7's X3 equals 4. The number of each Y7's X6 equals 2. The number of each Y9's X3 equals each Y7's XXX. How many X3 does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Y7's X6 as u. So u = 2.\nDefine each Y7's X3 as S. So S = 4.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 4 + 2 = 6.\nDefine each Y9's X3 as i. So i = A = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 945, "question": "The number of each Y8's X6 equals 7 more than each Y1's X6. The number of each Y1's X6 equals 5. How many XXX does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["Y1's X6 = 5. Y8's X6 = 7 * Y1's X6 = 7 * 5 = 12.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as u. So u = Y8's XXX as S. So S = u = 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 946, "question": "The number of each X6's W0 equals 5. The number of each X6's W5 equals 8 times each X6's W0. How many WWW does each X6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "22", "answer": 22, "code": ["X6's W0 as u. So u = 5.\nDefine each X6's W5 as S. So S = 8 * u = 8 * 5 = 17.\nDefine each X6's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 17 + 5 = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 947, "question": "The number of each Y5's X4 equals 11 more than each Z9's Y5. The number of each Z9's Y5 equals 19 more than each Z9's Y4. The number of each Y4's X4 equals 3 times each Z9's YYY. The number of each X8's W9 equals each Z9's Y4. The number of each X8's W5 equals 21 more than each X4's WWW. The number of each Z9's Y4 equals 0. The number of each X4's W9 equals 15. The number of each Y5's X8 equals 7. How many WWW does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["Z9's Y4 as u. So u = 0.\nDefine each Z9's Y5 as S. So S = 19 * u = 19 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z9's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 0 + 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y4's X4 as i. So i = 3 * A = 3 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X4's W9 as Y. So Y = 15.\nDefine each X4's WWW as F. So F = Y = 15.\nDefine each X8's W5 as r. So r = 21 * F = 21 * 15 = 16.\nDefine each X8's W9 as l. So l = u = 0.\nDefine each X8's WWW as V. So V = l + r = 0 + 16 = 16.\nDefine each Y5's X4 as q. So q = 11 * S = 11 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y5's X8 as z. So z = 7.\nDefine each Y5's WWW as A. So A = q * F + z * V = 0 * 15 + 7 * 16 = 20.\nDefine each Z9's WWW as i. So i = S * A + u * V = 0 * 20 + 0 * 16 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 948, "question": "The number of each Y1's X4 equals the difference of each X4's W8 and each X4's W6. The number of each Y5's X3 equals 11. The number of each X4's W8 equals 15 more than each Y5's X3. The number of each X4's W6 equals the difference of each X4's W8 and each Y5's X3. How many WWW does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Y5's X3 = 11. X4's W8 as u. So u = 15 * Y5's X3 = 15 * 11 = 4.\nDefine each X4's W6 as S. So S = u - Y5's X3 = 4 - 11 = 16.\nDefine each X4's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 16 + 4 = 20.\nDefine each Y1's X4 as i. So i = u - S = 4 - 16 = 11.\nDefine each Y1's WWW as Y. So Y = i * A = 11 * 20 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 949, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y6 equals 20 more than the difference of each Z6's Y2 and each Z8's Y2. The number of each Z8's Y4 equals 16. The number of each Z5's Y2 equals the sum of each Z8's Y6, each Z8's Y4 and each Z6's Y2. The number of each Z8's Y2 equals 18 more than the sum of each Z8's Y6, each Z5's Y2 and each Z6's Y2. The number of each Z6's Y2 equals 21 times each Z8's Y6. The number of each Z8's Y6 equals 21 times each Z8's Y4. The number of each Z5's Y4 equals 12 times each Z6's Y6. How many Y4 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Z8's Y4 as u. So u = 16.\nDefine each Z8's Y6 as S. So S = 21 * u = 21 * 16 = 14.\nDefine each Z6's Y2 as A. So A = 21 * S = 21 * 14 = 18.\nDefine each Z5's Y2 as i. So i = (S + u + A) = (14 + 16 + 18) = 2.\nDefine each Z8's Y2 as Y. So Y = 18 * (S + i + A) = 18 * (14 + 2 + 18) = 19.\nDefine each Z6's Y6 as F. So F = 20 * A - Y = 20 * 18 - 19 = 19.\nDefine each Z5's Y4 as r. So r = 12 * F = 12 * 19 = 21.\nThus, the answer is 21."], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 950, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y2 equals 1. How many Y2 does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Z0's Y2 = 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 951, "question": "The number of each Y0's X6 equals 16. How many X6 does each Y0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Y0's X6 = 16. So 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 952, "question": "The number of each X5's W1 equals 4. The number of each X4's W4 equals 12 more than each X5's W1. The number of each X5's W4 equals 15 more than the sum of each X4's W4 and each X5's W1. How many W4 does each X5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["X5's W1 = 4. X4's W4 as u. So u = 12 * X5's W1 = 12 * 4 = 2.\nDefine each X5's W4 as S. So S = 15 * u + u = 15 * 2 + 2 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 953, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y2 equals 18 more than each Y8's XXX. The number of each Y8's X1 equals 11. How many Y2 does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Y8's X1 as u. So u = 11.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as S. So S = u = 11.\nDefine each Z1's Y2 as A. So A = 18 * S = 18 * 11 = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 954, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y5 equals each Y5's XXX. The number of each Y5's X3 equals 5 more than each Y5's X9. The number of each Y5's X9 equals 7. The number of each Z0's Y9 equals each Z8's Y5. How many Y9 does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Y5's X9 as u. So u = 7.\nDefine each Y5's X3 as S. So S = 5 * u = 5 * 7 = 12.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 12 + 7 = 19.\nDefine each Z8's Y5 as i. So i = A = 19.\nDefine each Z0's Y9 as Y. So Y = i = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 955, "question": "The number of each Y2's X3 equals each Z3's Y3. The number of each X3's W5 equals 18 more than the sum of each Z6's WWW and each X1's W9. The number of each Z6's Y3 equals 7 times each Y3's WWW. The number of each Y7's X1 equals each Y2's X3. The number of each Y8's X3 equals the difference of each Y7's X1 and each X1's WWW. The number of each Z3's Y3 equals 18. The number of each Y3's X1 equals 18. The number of each X1's W9 equals the difference of each Y7's X1 and each X1's W3. The number of each X1's W3 equals the sum of each Z3's Y3 and each Y7's X1. How many WWW does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["Z3's Y3 as u. So u = 18.\nDefine each Y2's X3 as S. So S = u = 18.\nDefine each Y7's X1 as A. So A = S = 18.\nDefine each X1's W3 as i. So i = u + A = 18 + 18 = 13.\nDefine each X1's W9 as Y. So Y = A - i = 18 - 13 = 5.\nDefine each X1's WWW as F. So F = Y + i = 5 + 13 = 18.\nDefine each Y3's X1 as r. So r = 18.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as l. So l = r * F = 18 * 18 = 2.\nDefine each Z6's Y3 as V. So V = 7 * l = 7 * 2 = 14.\nDefine each Z6's WWW as q. So q = V * l = 14 * 2 = 5.\nDefine each X3's W5 as z. So z = 18 * q + Y = 18 * 5 + 5 = 22.\nDefine each Y8's X3 as A. So A = A - F = 18 - 18 = 0.\nDefine each X3's WWW as i. So i = Z = 22.\nDefine each Y8's WWW as Y. So Y = A * i = 0 * 22 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 956, "question": "The number of each X4's W4 equals 13. The number of each X0's W8 equals 22 times each X0's W1. The number of each X4's W8 equals 9. The number of each X8's W4 equals each X4's WWW. The number of each X4's W1 equals 21 more than each X0's W4. The number of each X0's W1 equals 11. The number of each X0's W4 equals 7 more than each X0's W8. How many W4 does each X8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["X0's W1 as u. So u = 11.\nDefine each X0's W8 as S. So S = 22 * u = 22 * 11 = 12.\nDefine each X0's W4 as A. So A = 7 * S = 7 * 12 = 15.\nDefine each X4's W1 as i. So i = 21 * A = 21 * 15 = 16.\nDefine each X4's W4 as Y. So Y = 13.\nDefine each X4's W8 as F. So F = 9.\nDefine each X4's WWW as r. So r = Y + F + i = 13 + 9 + 16 = 15.\nDefine each X8's W4 as l. So l = r = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 957, "question": "The number of each Y5's X3 equals 14 more than each Y6's XXX. The number of each Y5's X9 equals 18 more than each Y6's X3. The number of each Y6's X0 equals 2. The number of each Y6's X9 equals the difference of each Y6's X3 and each Y5's X9. The number of each Y6's X4 equals the sum of each Y6's X3 and each Y6's X9. The number of each Y5's X4 equals 5 more than each Y5's X9. The number of each Y6's X3 equals 10. How many XXX does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Y6's X3 as u. So u = 10.\nDefine each Y5's X9 as S. So S = 18 * u = 18 * 10 = 19.\nDefine each Y6's X9 as A. So A = u - S = 10 - 19 = 14.\nDefine each Y6's X4 as i. So i = u + A = 10 + 14 = 1.\nDefine each Y6's X0 as Y. So Y = 2.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as F. So F = Y + A + u + i = 2 + 14 + 10 + 1 = 4.\nDefine each Y5's X3 as r. So r = 14 * F = 14 * 4 = 10.\nDefine each Y5's X4 as l. So l = 5 * S = 5 * 19 = 3.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as V. So V = l + S + r = 3 + 19 + 10 = 9.\nThus, the answer is 9."], "pred": ["9"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 958, "question": "The number of each X3's W7 equals 12 times each Y3's WWW. The number of each X5's W4 equals the difference of each Y5's X3 and each X8's WWW. The number of each X8's W3 equals 8 times each Y5's X8. The number of each Y5's X3 equals 3. The number of each Y8's X3 equals the sum of each Y3's WWW, each X3's W7 and each X5's W4. The number of each Y5's X8 equals 19 times each Y5's X3. The number of each Y3's X5 equals 10 more than the sum of each X8's W3, each X5's WWW and each X8's WWW. How many WWW does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Y5's X3 = 3. Y5's X8 = 19 * u = 19 * 3 = 11.\nDefine each X8's W3 as u. So u = 8 * u = 8 * 11 = 19.\nDefine each X8's WWW as S. So S = u = 19.\nDefine each X5's W4 as A. So A = u - S = 19 - 19 = 0.\nDefine each X5's WWW as i. So i = A = 0.\nDefine each Y3's X5 as Y. So Y = 10 * (u + i + S) = 10 * (19 + 0 + 19) = 11.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as F. So F = Y * i = 11 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each X3's W7 as r. So r = 12 * F = 12 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Y8's X3 as l. So l = (F + r + A) = (0 + 0 + 0) = 0.\nDefine each X3's WWW as V. So V = r = 0.\nDefine each Y8's WWW as q. So q = l * V = 0 * 0 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 959, "question": "The number of each Y8's X6 equals 21. The number of each X5's W4 equals 10 times each X6's W6. The number of each X5's W6 equals 9 more than each Y8's X5. The number of each Y8's X5 equals 19 more than each Y8's X6. The number of each X6's W6 equals 17 more than each Y8's XXX. How many WWW does each X5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Y8's X6 as u. So u = 21.\nDefine each Y8's X5 as S. So S = 19 * u = 19 * 21 = 8.\nDefine each Y8's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 8 + 21 = 6.\nDefine each X6's W6 as i. So i = 17 * A = 17 * 6 = 10.\nDefine each X5's W4 as Y. So Y = 10 * i = 10 * 10 = 8.\nDefine each X5's W6 as F. So F = 9 * S = 9 * 8 = 3.\nDefine each X5's WWW as r. So r = Y + F = 8 + 3 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 960, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y2 equals 12 more than each Y2's XXX. The number of each Y6's X6 equals 14. The number of each Y2's X6 equals 12 more than each Y2's X4. The number of each Y2's X4 equals 2. The number of each Y6's X4 equals each Z8's Y2. How many XXX does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Y2's X4 as u. So u = 2.\nDefine each Y2's X6 as S. So S = 12 * u = 12 * 2 = 1.\nDefine each Y2's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 1 + 2 = 3.\nDefine each Z8's Y2 as i. So i = 12 * A = 12 * 3 = 13.\nDefine each Y6's X4 as Y. So Y = i = 13.\nDefine each Y6's X6 as F. So F = 14.\nDefine each Y6's XXX as r. So r = Y + F = 13 + 14 = 4.\nThus, the answer is 4."], "pred": ["4"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 961, "question": "The number of each X0's W4 equals 12. How many W4 does each X0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "12", "answer": 12, "code": ["X0's W4 = 12. So 12.\nThus, the answer is 12."], "pred": ["12"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 962, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y4 equals 10. The number of each Y4's X4 equals 18 more than the sum of each Z8's Y4, each Y9's X4 and each Z1's Y4. The number of each X2's W7 equals 0 more than the difference of each Z1's WWW and each Y9's X4. The number of each X4's W7 equals 9 more than each Z8's Y4. The number of each Z1's Y4 equals 5 more than the sum of each Z8's Y4 and each X4's WWW. The number of each Y9's X4 equals 2 more than the sum of each X4's WWW and each X4's W7. How many W7 does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 963, "question": "The number of each X4's W1 equals 6 times the sum of each Y2's X7 and each X4's W5. The number of each Y0's X4 equals 1 times each X4's WWW. The number of each Y7's X7 equals 5 more than the difference of each Y0's X4 and each X7's W5. The number of each Y7's X4 equals the sum of each Y0's X4, each X7's W5 and each X4's W1. The number of each X7's W5 equals 5 more than each Y0's XXX. The number of each Y2's X7 equals 4 more than each X4's W5. The number of each Y0's X7 equals 22 more than the difference of each Y0's X4 and each X4's WWW. The number of each X4's W5 equals 15. The number of each X7's W3 equals the sum of each Y7's XXX and each X4's W1. How many W3 does each X7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "0", "answer": 0, "code": ["X4's W5 as u. So u = 15.\nDefine each Y2's X7 as S. So S = 4 * u = 4 * 15 = 14.\nDefine each X4's W1 as A. So A = 6 * S + u = 6 * 14 + 15 = 16.\nDefine each X4's WWW as i. So i = u + A = 15 + 16 = 8.\nDefine each Y0's X4 as Y. So Y = 1 * i = 1 * 8 = 8.\nDefine each Y0's X7 as F. So F = 22 * Y - i = 22 * 8 - 8 = 7.\nDefine each Y0's XXX as r. So r = Y + F = 8 + 7 = 15.\nDefine each X7's W5 as l. So l = 5 * r = 5 * 15 = 6.\nDefine each Y7's X4 as V. So V = (Y + l + A) = (8 + 6 + 16) = 7.\nDefine each Y7's X7 as q. So q = 5 * Y - l = 5 * 8 - 6 = 19.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as z. So z = q + V = 19 + 7 = 3.\nDefine each X7's W3 as A. So A = S + A = 14 + 16 = 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 964, "question": "The number of each Y7's X5 equals each X4's W8. The number of each X4's W8 equals 19 times each X4's W2. The number of each Y7's X4 equals each X4's W2. The number of each X4's W2 equals 1. The number of each Y7's X3 equals the sum of each X4's W8 and each Y7's X4. How many XXX does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["X4's W2 as u. So u = 1.\nDefine each X4's W8 as S. So S = 19 * u = 19 * 1 = 19.\nDefine each Y7's X4 as A. So A = u = 1.\nDefine each Y7's X3 as i. So i = S + A = 19 + 1 = 20.\nDefine each Y7's X5 as Y. So Y = S = 19.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as F. So F = Y + i + A = 19 + 20 + 1 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 965, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y4 equals 14. The number of each Y7's X5 equals 15. The number of each Y7's X4 equals the difference of each Z3's Y1 and each Z3's Y4. The number of each Z3's Y1 equals 3 times each Z3's Y4. How many XXX does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "20", "answer": 20, "code": ["Z3's Y4 as u. So u = 14.\nDefine each Z3's Y1 as S. So S = 3 * u = 3 * 14 = 19.\nDefine each Y7's X4 as A. So A = S - u = 19 - 14 = 5.\nDefine each Y7's X5 as i. So i = 15.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as Y. So Y = A + i = 5 + 15 = 20.\nThus, the answer is 20."], "pred": ["20"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 966, "question": "The number of each Y7's X1 equals the sum of each Y1's X1, each Y4's XXX, each Y4's X9 and each Y1's X9. The number of each Y1's X9 equals 7. The number of each Y1's X1 equals 8 more than each Y1's X9. The number of each Y5's X5 equals 9 times the difference of each Y7's XXX and each Y1's X5. The number of each Y1's X5 equals the sum of each Y1's X1 and each Y1's X7. The number of each Y5's X7 equals 10 more than each Y4's X5. The number of each Y4's X5 equals 13 times each Y1's X5. The number of each Y4's X9 equals 11 times the difference of each Y1's X9 and each Y1's X5. The number of each Y1's X7 equals the sum of each Y1's X1 and each Y1's X9. How many XXX does each Y5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Y1's X9 as u. So u = 7.\nDefine each Y1's X1 as S. So S = 8 * u = 8 * 7 = 10.\nDefine each Y1's X7 as A. So A = S + u = 10 + 7 = 17.\nDefine each Y1's X5 as i. So i = S + A = 10 + 17 = 4.\nDefine each Y4's X5 as Y. So Y = 13 * i = 13 * 4 = 6.\nDefine each Y4's X9 as F. So F = 11 * u - i = 11 * 7 - 4 = 19.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as r. So r = Y + F = 6 + 19 = 2.\nDefine each Y7's X1 as l. So l = (S + r + F + u) = (10 + 2 + 19 + 7) = 15.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as V. So V = l = 15.\nDefine each Y5's X5 as q. So q = 9 * V - i = 9 * 15 - 4 = 15.\nDefine each Y5's X7 as z. So z = 10 * Y = 10 * 6 = 14.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as A. So A = q + z = 15 + 14 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 967, "question": "The number of each X5's W4 equals 5. The number of each X5's W5 equals 12 more than each X8's W2. The number of each X9's W5 equals 12 more than the sum of each X8's W2 and each X5's W4. The number of each X8's W2 equals 20 times each X5's W4. The number of each X9's W1 equals 20 times each X5's W5. How many WWW does each X9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["X5's W4 = 5. X8's W2 = 20 * X5's W4 = 20 * 5 = 8.\nDefine each X5's W5 as u. So u = 12 * X8's W2 = 12 * 8 = 4.\nDefine each X9's W1 as S. So S = 20 * u = 20 * 4 = 11.\nDefine each X9's W5 as A. So A = 12 * the X8's W2 + X5's W4 = 12 * 8 + 5 = 10.\nDefine each X9's WWW as i. So i = S + A = 11 + 10 = 21.\nThus, the answer is 21."], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 968, "question": "The number of each X0's W0 equals each Y6's X0. The number of each Y6's X0 equals 14. The number of each Y1's X9 equals each X0's WWW. How many X9 does each Y1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Y6's X0 = 14. X0's W0 = Y6's X0. X0's WWW = Y6's X0. X9's WWW as i. So i = X9's WWW as Y. So Y = i = 19.\nDefine each Y6's X0 as F. So F = 14.\nDefine each X0's WWW as r. So r = F = 14.\nDefine each Y1's X9 as l. So l = r = 14.\nThus, the answer is 14."], "pred": ["14"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 969, "question": "The number of each Y7's X1 equals each Y7's X4. The number of each Y9's X4 equals each Y7's X1. The number of each Y7's X4 equals 19. The number of each X1's W9 equals each Y9's X4. The number of each Y9's X1 equals each X1's W9. How many X1 does each Y9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["Y7's X4 as u. So u = 19.\nDefine each Y7's X1 as S. So S = u = 19.\nDefine each Y9's X4 as A. So A = S = 19.\nDefine each X1's W9 as i. So i = A = 19.\nDefine each Y9's X1 as Y. So Y = i = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 970, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y7 equals 11 times each Y7's X1. The number of each X0's W4 equals 1 times the sum of each Z0's YYY and each Z8's Y3. The number of each Z8's Y3 equals 1. The number of each Y7's X1 equals 4 more than each Z8's Y3. How many W4 does each X0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["Z8's Y3 = 1. Y7's X1 as u. So u = 4 * Z8's Y3 = 4 * 1 = 4.\nDefine each Z0's Y7 as S. So S = 11 * u = 11 * 4 = 21.\nDefine each Z0's YYY as A. So A = S = 21.\nDefine each X0's W4 as i. So i = 1 * A + Z8's Y3 = 1 * 21 + 1 = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 971, "question": "The number of each Y5's X6 equals the difference of each Z4's YYY and each Z4's Y4. The number of each Y5's X7 equals each Y5's X6. The number of each Z4's Y5 equals 9. The number of each Y5's X1 equals the difference of each Z4's Y4 and each Y5's X7. The number of each X1's W7 equals 21. The number of each X1's W3 equals each Y5's XXX. The number of each Z4's Y4 equals 7 times each Z4's Y5. How many WWW does each X1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Z4's Y5 as u. So u = 9.\nDefine each Z4's Y4 as S. So S = 7 * u = 7 * 9 = 17.\nDefine each Z4's YYY as A. So A = S + u = 17 + 9 = 3.\nDefine each Y5's X6 as i. So i = A - S = 3 - 17 = 9.\nDefine each Y5's X7 as Y. So Y = i = 9.\nDefine each Y5's X1 as F. So F = S - Y = 17 - 9 = 8.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as r. So r = Y + F + i = 9 + 8 + 9 = 3.\nDefine each X1's W3 as l. So l = r = 3.\nDefine each X1's W7 as V. So V = 21.\nDefine each X1's WWW as q. So q = V + l = 21 + 3 = 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 972, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y6 equals 9 more than the sum of each X4's WWW and each X9's W4. The number of each X4's W4 equals 12 times the difference of each X3's W2 and each X9's W4. The number of each Z8's Y0 equals the sum of each X3's W2 and each X4's W4. The number of each X3's W2 equals 19. The number of each Y6's X9 equals 9 times the sum of each X9's W4, each X3's W2 and each X4's WWW. The number of each Y0's X4 equals the sum of each X4's W4 and each X9's W4. The number of each X9's W4 equals 6 more than each X3's W2. How many WWW does each Z8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["X3's W2 = 19. X9's W4 as u. So u = 6 * X3's W2 = 6 * 19 = 22.\nDefine each X4's W4 as S. So S = 12 * X3's W2 - u = 12 * 19 - 22 = 19.\nDefine each X4's WWW as A. So A = S = 19.\nDefine each Y6's X9 as i. So i = 9 * (u + X3's W2 + A) = 9 * (22 + 19 + 19) = 11.\nDefine each Y6's WWW as Y. So Y = i * u = 11 * 22 = 12.\nDefine each Z8's Y0 as F. So F = X3's W2 + S = 19 + 19 = 15.\nDefine each Z8's Y6 as r. So r = 9 * A + u = 9 * 19 + 22 = 19.\nDefine each Z8's WWW as l. So l = r * Y + F * A = 19 * 12 + 15 * 19 = 19.\nThus, the answer is 19."], "pred": ["19"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 973, "question": "The number of each Y4's X9 equals 11 more than the sum of each Y5's XXX and each Y4's X2. The number of each Y5's X2 equals 1 more than the sum of each Y4's X2 and each Y9's X8. The number of each Y5's X8 equals 15 more than the difference of each Y9's X8 and each Y4's X2. The number of each Y4's X8 equals 0 times each Y9's X9. The number of each Y5's X9 equals the sum of each Y9's X9 and each Y9's X8. The number of each Y9's X9 equals 1. The number of each Y4's X2 equals each Y9's XXX. The number of each Y9's X8 equals each Y4's X8. How many X9 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["Y9's X9 as u. So u = 1.\nDefine each Y4's X8 as S. So S = 0 * u = 0 * 1 = 0.\nDefine each Y9's X8 as A. So A = S = 0.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as i. So i = A + u = 0 + 1 = 1.\nDefine each Y4's X2 as Y. So Y = i = 1.\nDefine each Y5's X2 as F. So F = 1 * Y + A = 1 * 1 + 0 = 1.\nDefine each Y5's X9 as r. So r = u + A = 1 + 0 = 1.\nDefine each Y5's X8 as l. So l = 15 + A - Y = 15 + 0 - 1 = 14.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as V. So V = l + r + F = 14 + 1 + 1 = 16.\nDefine each Y4's X9 as q. So q = 11 * V + Y = 11 * 16 + 1 = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 974, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y4 equals 5. The number of each Y4's X2 equals 2 more than each Z3's Y4. How many X2 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["Z3's Y4 as u. So u = 5.\nDefine each Y4's X2 as S. So S = 2 * u = 2 * 5 = 10.\nDefine each Y4's XXX as A. So A = S = 10.\nDefine each Z3's XXX as i. So i = u * A = 5 * 10 = 4.\nDefine each lollip0 as Y. So Y = 20.\nDefine each lollip1 as F. So F = 20.\nDefine each lollip2 as r. So r = 2.\nDefine each lollip3 as l. So l = 3.\nDefine each l. So l = 3.\nDefine each l. So l = 3.\nDefine each V. So V = 23.\nThus, the answer is 23."], "pred": ["23"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 975, "question": "The number of each X5's W7 equals each X6's WWW. The number of each Z5's Y5 equals 15. The number of each Z5's Y6 equals 2 times each Z5's Y8. The number of each X6's W7 equals 14 times the sum of each Z5's Y6 and each Z5's YYY. The number of each Z5's Y8 equals 14 times each Z5's Y5. The number of each X6's W8 equals the sum of each Z5's Y8, each Z5's Y5 and each X6's W7. How many W7 does each X5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "7", "answer": 7, "code": ["Z5's Y5 = 15. Z5's Y8 = 14 * Z5's Y5 = 14 * 15 = 3.\nDefine each Z5's Y6 as u. So u = 2 * u = 2 * 3 = 6.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as S. So S = u + S + Y = 6 + 15 + 6 = 4.\nDefine each X6's W7 as A. So A = 14 * u + S = 14 * 6 + 4 = 15.\nDefine each X6's W8 as i. So i = (u + S + A) = (6 + 4 + 15) = 2.\nDefine each X6's WWW as Y. So Y = i + A = 2 + 15 = 17.\nDefine each X5's W7 as F. So F = Y = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 976, "question": "The number of each X4's W9 equals 9 times each Z4's Y9. The number of each X4's W6 equals the sum of each Z4's Y9 and each X4's W9. The number of each X6's W6 equals 2. The number of each Y9's X6 equals 20 times each X6's WWW. The number of each Y2's X4 equals 22 times each X4's W9. The number of each Z4's Y9 equals the difference of each Y9's WWW and each X6's W6. The number of each Z7's Y7 equals 16. The number of each Z8's Y2 equals 15 more than each Z7's Y7. How many WWW does each Z8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "6", "answer": 6, "code": ["X6's W6 as u. So u = 2.\nDefine each X6's WWW as S. So S = u = 2.\nDefine each Y9's X6 as A. So A = 20 * S = 20 * 2 = 17.\nDefine each Y9's WWW as i. So i = A * S = 17 * 2 = 11.\nDefine each Z4's Y9 as Y. So Y = i - u = 11 - 2 = 9.\nDefine each X4's W9 as F. So F = 9 * Y = 9 * 9 = 12.\nDefine each Y2's X4 as r. So r = 22 * F = 22 * 12 = 11.\nDefine each X4's W6 as l. So l = Y + F = 9 + 12 = 21.\nDefine each X4's WWW as V. So V = l + F = 21 + 12 = 10.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as q. So q = r * V = 11 * 10 = 18.\nDefine each Z7's Y7 as z. So z = 16.\nDefine each Z8's Y2 as A. So A = 15 * S = 15 * 2 = 7.\nDefine each Z8's WWW as i. So i = A * q = 7 * 18 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 977, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y2 equals 16. How many Y2 does each Z6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "16", "answer": 16, "code": ["Z6's Y2 = 16. So 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 978, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y2 equals 2 times the sum of each Y2's X6, each Z4's Y2 and each X1's W9. The number of each Z1's Y9 equals the sum of each Y2's X6 and each X6's W7. The number of each X6's W7 equals 1 more than each X1's W7. The number of each X6's W9 equals each Z4's Y2. The number of each Z4's Y2 equals 6. The number of each Y2's X6 equals the sum of each X6's W7 and each X6's W9. The number of each X1's W7 equals 11 times the sum of each X1's W9, each X6's W9 and each Z4's Y2. The number of each X1's W9 equals each X6's W9. The number of each Y9's X1 equals the sum of each X1's W7 and each X6's W9. How many XXX does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "13", "answer": 13, "code": ["Z4's Y2 = 6. X6's W9 = Z4's Y2 = 6. X1's W9 = X6's W9 = 6.\nDefine each X1's W7 as u. So u = 11 * (i + X6's W9 + Z4's Y2) = 11 * (6 + 6 + 6) = 19.\nDefine each X6's W7 as Y. So Y = 1 * u = 1 * 19 = 19.\nDefine each Y2's X6 as F. So F = Y + X6's W9 = 19 + 6 = 2.\nDefine each Z1's Y9 as r. So r = F + Y = 2 + 19 = 21.\nDefine each Z1's Y2 as l. So l = 2 * (F + Z4's Y2 + i) = 2 * (2 + 6 + 6) = 14.\nDefine each Y9's X1 as V. So V = u + S = 19 + 6 = 2.\nDefine each Y9's XXX as q. So q = V = 2.\nDefine each Z1's XXX as z. So z = l * q + r * q = 14 * 2 + 21 * 2 = 16.\nThus, the answer is 16."], "pred": ["16"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 979, "question": "The number of each Z6's Y5 equals 18 more than each Y5's X1. The number of each Y4's X1 equals the sum of each Y5's X1, each X1's W8 and each X1's W9. The number of each Z3's Y5 equals 18. The number of each X1's W9 equals 14 more than the sum of each Z6's Y5, each Y5's X1 and each Z3's Y5. The number of each X7's W8 equals the difference of each Y4's WWW and each X1's W9. The number of each X1's W8 equals the sum of each Y5's X1 and each Z3's Y5. The number of each Y5's X1 equals 13 times each Z3's Y5. How many W8 does each X7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Z3's Y5 = 18. Y5's X1 = 13 * Z3's Y5 = 13 * 18 = 4.\nDefine each Z6's Y5 as u. So u = 18 * u = 18 * 4 = 3.\nDefine each X1's W9 as S. So S = 14 * (u + u + Z3's Y5) = 14 * (3 + 3 + 18) = 19.\nDefine each X1's W8 as A. So A = u + Z3's Y5 = 3 + 18 = 21.\nDefine each Y4's X1 as i. So i = (u + A + S) = (3 + 21 + 19) = 20.\nDefine each X1's WWW as Y. So Y = S + A = 19 + 21 = 17.\nDefine each Y4's WWW as F. So F = i * Y = 20 * 17 = 18.\nDefine each X7's W8 as r. So r = F - S = 18 - 19 = 22.\nThus, the answer is 22."], "pred": ["22"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 980, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y4 equals 15. How many Y4 does each Z1 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Z1's Y4 as u. So u = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 981, "question": "The number of each Y7's X6 equals each Y3's X6. The number of each X2's W6 equals 22. The number of each Y3's X7 equals 16 times each X2's WWW. The number of each X2's W4 equals 14 times each X2's W6. The number of each Y3's X6 equals 19 times each Y3's X7. How many X6 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "17", "answer": 17, "code": ["X2's W6 as u. So u = 22.\nDefine each X2's W4 as S. So S = 14 * u = 14 * 22 = 9.\nDefine each X2's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 9 + 22 = 8.\nDefine each Y3's X7 as i. So i = 16 * A = 16 * 8 = 13.\nDefine each Y3's X6 as Y. So Y = 19 * i = 19 * 13 = 17.\nDefine each Y7's X6 as F. So F = Y = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 982, "question": "The number of each Z8's Y2 equals each Y2's XXX. The number of each X0's W5 equals 12 times each Z8's XXX. The number of each Y2's X0 equals 4. The number of each Z4's Y2 equals each X0's W5. How many WWW does each Z4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["Y2's X0 = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX = 4. Y2's XXX as u. So u = 4. Y2's XXX as S. So S = u = 4. Y2's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 4 + 4 = 8. Y2's XXX as i. So i = S + u = 8 + 4 = 12.\nDefine each Z8's Y2 as Y. So Y = i = 12.\nDefine each Z8's XXX as F. So F = Y * i = 12 * 12 = 6.\nDefine each X0's W5 as r. So r = 12 * F = 12 * 6 = 3.\nDefine each Z4's Y2 as l. So l = r = 3.\nDefine each Z4's WWW as V. So V = l * A = 3 * 12 = 13.\nThus, the answer is 13."], "pred": ["13"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 983, "question": "The number of each Y6's X9 equals 11. How many X9 does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "11", "answer": 11, "code": ["Y6's X9 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 984, "question": "The number of each X5's W7 equals 22 more than the sum of each Z6's Y1, each Y1's XXX and each X3's W3. The number of each X3's W3 equals each Z6's Y1. The number of each Y1's X5 equals 16 times the sum of each Z6's Y1 and each X5's W3. The number of each X5's W3 equals 2. The number of each Z6's Y1 equals 7 more than each X5's W3. The number of each Y1's X3 equals 9 more than the difference of each X3's W3 and each Z6's Y1. How many W7 does each X5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 985, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y5 equals 14. The number of each Y5's X9 equals 9 times each Z5's Y5. The number of each Y7's X5 equals 16 more than each Y5's XXX. How many X5 does each Y7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["Y5's X9 = 9 * Z5's Y5 = 9 * 14 = 11.\nDefine each Z5's Y5 as u. So u = 14.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as S. So S = Y5's X9 = 11.\nDefine each Y7's X5 as A. So A = 16 * S = 16 * 11 = 15.\nThus, the answer is 15."], "pred": ["15"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 986, "question": "The number of each Z1's Y8 equals each Z1's Y2. The number of each Z1's Y2 equals the sum of each X1's W0 and each X1's WWW. The number of each X2's W0 equals 3 more than each Y8's X1. The number of each X1's W5 equals each X1's W0. The number of each X1's W0 equals 7. The number of each Y8's X1 equals the sum of each X1's W5 and each Z1's YYY. The number of each X2's W5 equals each Z1's Y8. How many WWW does each X2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["X1's W0 as u. So u = 7.\nDefine each X1's W5 as S. So S = u = 7.\nDefine each X1's WWW as A. So A = S + u = 7 + 7 = 14.\nDefine each Z1's Y2 as i. So i = u + A = 7 + 14 = 21.\nDefine each Z1's Y8 as Y. So Y = i = 21.\nDefine each Z1's YYY as F. So F = Y + i = 21 + 21 = 19.\nDefine each Y8's X1 as r. So r = S + F = 7 + 19 = 3.\nDefine each X2's W0 as l. So l = 3 * r = 3 * 3 = 9.\nDefine each X2's W5 as V. So V = Y = 21.\nDefine each X2's WWW as q. So q = V + l = 21 + 9 = 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 987, "question": "The number of each Z0's Y0 equals 8. How many Y0 does each Z0 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "8", "answer": 8, "code": ["Z0's Y0 = 8.\nThus, the answer is 8."], "pred": ["8"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 988, "question": "The number of each X2's W7 equals 3. The number of each Y2's X2 equals 0 more than each X0's W3. The number of each X0's W3 equals 7 times each Y7's WWW. The number of each Y7's X2 equals 2 times each X2's W7. How many WWW does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "10", "answer": 10, "code": ["X2's W7 = 3. Y7's X2 as u. So u = 2 * X2 = 2 * 3 = 6.\nDefine each X2's WWW as S. So S = X2's W3 = 3.\nDefine each Y7's WWW as A. So A = u * S = 6 * 3 = 18.\nDefine each X0's W3 as i. So i = 7 * A = 7 * 18 = 11.\nDefine each Y2's X2 as Y. So Y = 0 * i = 0 * 11 = 0.\nDefine each Y2's WWW as F. So F = Y * S = 0 * 3 = 0.\nThus, the answer is 0."], "pred": ["0"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 989, "question": "The number of each Z4's Y7 equals 12. The number of each Z7's Y5 equals 15 more than the difference of each Z4's YYY and each Z4's Y7. The number of each Z7's Y7 equals 11 more than the sum of each Z4's YYY, each Z4's Y7 and each Z7's Y5. The number of each Z8's Y7 equals 7 more than the sum of each Z7's YYY, each Z4's Y7 and each Z7's Y7. How many Y7 does each Z8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "19", "answer": 19, "code": ["7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 990, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y2 equals 5. The number of each Y2's X8 equals 9 times the sum of each Z5's Y5 and each Z7's Y2. The number of each Z5's Y5 equals 4 times each Z7's Y2. How many X8 does each Y2 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "18", "answer": 18, "code": ["Z7's Y2 = 5. Z5's Y5 as u. So u = 4 * Z7's Y2 = 4 * 5 = 20.\nDefine each Y2's X8 as S. So S = 9 * u + Z7's Y2 = 9 * 20 + 5 = 17.\nThus, the answer is 17."], "pred": ["17"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 991, "question": "The number of each Y8's X4 equals the sum of each Z1's WWW and each X2's WWW. The number of each Y5's X2 equals 15. The number of each Z1's Y5 equals the sum of each X2's W5 and each Y5's X2. The number of each X2's W5 equals each Y5's X2. How many X4 does each Y8 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["Y5's X2 = 15. X2's W5 = Y5's X2 = 15.\nDefine each X2's WWW as u. So u = X2's W5 = 15.\nDefine each Y5's WWW as S. So S = Y5's X2 * u = 15 * 15 = 18.\nDefine each Z1's Y5 as A. So A = F + Y5 = 15 + 15 = 7.\nDefine each Z1's WWW as i. So i = A * S = 7 * 18 = 11.\nDefine each Y8's X4 as Y. So Y = i + u = 11 + 15 = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 992, "question": "The number of each Z9's Y2 equals 19 times the difference of each Y7's XXX and each Z9's Y7. The number of each Y7's X7 equals 22. The number of each Y8's X7 equals 13 times the sum of each Y7's X9, each Y7's XXX and each Y7's X7. The number of each Y7's X9 equals each Y7's X7. The number of each Z7's Y2 equals 3 times each Y8's X7. The number of each Z9's Y7 equals the difference of each Y7's X9 and each Z7's Y2. How many YYY does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Y7's X7 as u. So u = 22.\nDefine each Y7's X9 as S. So S = u = 22.\nDefine each Y7's XXX as A. So A = S + u = 22 + 22 = 21.\nDefine each Y8's X7 as i. So i = 13 * (S + A + u) = 13 * (22 + 21 + 22) = 19.\nDefine each Z7's Y2 as Y. So Y = 3 * i = 3 * 19 = 11.\nDefine each Z9's Y7 as F. So F = S - Y = 22 - 11 = 11.\nDefine each Z9's Y2 as r. So r = 19 * A - F = 19 * 21 - 11 = 19.\nDefine each Z9's YYY as l. So l = r + F = 19 + 11 = 7.\nThus, the answer is 7."], "pred": ["7"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 993, "question": "The number of each Z3's Y0 equals 5. The number of each Y6's X3 equals 13 times each X1's W7. The number of each Y5's X2 equals each Z3's Y0. The number of each X1's W7 equals each Z2's XXX. The number of each Z2's Y5 equals each Y5's X2. How many X3 does each Y6 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["Z3's Y0 = 5. Y5's X2 = Z3's Y0 = 5.\nDefine each Y5's XXX as u. So u = X2 = 5.\nDefine each Z2's Y5 as S. So S = u = 5.\nDefine each Z2's XXX as A. So A = S * u = 5 * 5 = 2.\nDefine each X1's W7 as i. So i = A = 2.\nDefine each Y6's X3 as Y. So Y = 13 * i = 13 * 2 = 3.\nThus, the answer is 3."], "pred": ["3"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 994, "question": "The number of each Z7's Y4 equals 9 more than each Z5's YYY. The number of each Z5's Y4 equals 5 more than each Z5's Y2. The number of each Z9's Y6 equals the difference of each Z7's YYY and each Z5's Y4. The number of each Z5's Y2 equals 19 times each Z5's Y6. The number of each Z5's Y6 equals 20. The number of each Z9's Y4 equals 1 more than each Z9's Y6. How many YYY does each Z9 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "14", "answer": 14, "code": ["Z5's Y6 = 20. Z5's Y2 as u. So u = 19 * S = 19 * 20 = 12.\nDefine each Z5's Y4 as S. So S = 5 * u = 5 * 12 = 14.\nDefine each Z5's YYY as A. So A = S + u + Y = 14 + 12 + 20 = 0.\nDefine each Z7's Y4 as i. So i = 9 * A = 9 * 0 = 0.\nDefine each Z7's YYY as Y. So Y = i = 0.\nDefine each Z9's Y6 as F. So F = Y - S = 0 - 14 = 9.\nDefine each Z9's Y4 as r. So r = 1 * F = 1 * 9 = 9.\nDefine each Z9's YYY as l. So l = r + F = 9 + 9 = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 995, "question": "The number of each X3's W1 equals 20. The number of each Y4's X8 equals 14 times each X3's WWW. How many X8 does each Y4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "4", "answer": 4, "code": ["X3's W1 = 20. X3's WWW = X2. X2 = 21.\nDefine each Y4's X8 as u. So u = 14 * X2 = 14 * 21 = 18.\nThus, the answer is 18."], "pred": ["18"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 996, "question": "The number of each X7's W3 equals 21. How many W3 does each X7 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "21", "answer": 21, "code": ["X7's W3 = 21.\nThus, the answer is 21."], "pred": ["21"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 997, "question": "The number of each Z5's Y3 equals 1. How many Y3 does each Z5 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "1", "answer": 1, "code": ["Z5's Y3 = 1. So 1.\nThus, the answer is 1."], "pred": ["1"], "report": [null], "score": [true]}
{"idx": 998, "question": "The number of each X4's W5 equals 15 more than each X9's WWW. The number of each X5's W8 equals 10 more than each X8's WWW. The number of each X4's W7 equals 14 times the difference of each X9's W6 and each X4's W5. The number of each X9's W6 equals 14 times each X5's WWW. The number of each X8's W5 equals 9 more than each X8's W6. The number of each X8's W6 equals 10. The number of each X8's W7 equals 9 more than the sum of each X8's W5 and each X8's W6. The number of each X5's W6 equals 5 more than the sum of each X8's W7 and each X8's W5. How many WWW does each X4 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "3", "answer": 3, "code": ["X8's W6 as u. So u = 10.\nDefine each X8's W5 as S. So S = 9 * u = 9 * 10 = 21.\nDefine each X8's W7 as A. So A = 9 * S + u = 9 * 21 + 10 = 14.\nDefine each X8's WWW as i. So i = S + A + u = 21 + 14 + 10 = 22.\nDefine each X5's W6 as Y. So Y = 5 * A + S = 5 * 14 + 21 = 16.\nDefine each X5's W8 as F. So F = 10 * i = 10 * 22 = 13.\nDefine each X5's WWW as r. So r = Y + F = 16 + 13 = 6.\nDefine each X9's W6 as l. So l = 14 * r = 14 * 6 = 15.\nDefine each X9's WWW as V. So V = l = 15.\nDefine each X4's W5 as q. So q = 15 + V = 15 + 15 = 7.\nDefine each X4's W7 as z. So z = 14 + l - q = 14 + 15 - 7 = 22.\nDefine each X4's WWW as A. So A = q + z = 7 + 22 = 6.\nThus, the answer is 6."], "pred": ["6"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
{"idx": 999, "question": "The number of each X6's W1 equals 4. The number of each Y3's X6 equals 15 more than each X6's W1. The number of each X6's W7 equals 7 times each X6's W1. The number of each X1's W1 equals the difference of each Y3's X1 and each X6's W1. The number of each Y3's X1 equals each X6's W7. How many WWW does each Y3 have?", "gt_cot": "", "gt": "15", "answer": 15, "code": ["Y3's X6 as u. So u = 15 * X6's W1 = 15 * 4 = 14.\nDefine each X6's W7 as S. So S = 7 * X6's W1 = 7 * 4 = 5.\nDefine each Y3's X1 as A. So A = S = 5.\nDefine each X1's W1 as i. So i = A - X6's W1 = 5 - 4 = 1.\nDefine each X1's WWW as Y. So Y = i = 1.\nDefine each X6's WWW as F. So F = S + S = 5 + 5 = 10.\nDefine each Y3's WWW as r. So r = u * F + A * Y = 14 * 10 + 5 * 1 = 11.\nThus, the answer is 11."], "pred": ["11"], "report": [null], "score": [false]}
